{
  "title": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to create a service that requires encryption in transit. The traffic must not be decrypted between the client and the backend of the service. The company will implement the service by using the gRPC protocol over TCP port 443. The service will scale up to thousands of simultaneous connections. The backend of the service will be hosted on an Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) duster with the Kubernetes Cluster Autoscaler and the Horizontal Pod Autoscaler configured. The company needs to use mutual TLS for two-way authentication between the client and the backend.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Install the AWS Load Balancer Controller for Kubernetes. Using that controller, configure a Network Load Balancer with a TCP listener on port 443 to forward traffic to the IP addresses of the backend service Pods.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Install the AWS Load Balancer Controller for Kubernetes. Using that controller, configure an Application Load Balancer with an HTTPS listener on port 443 to forward traffic to the IP addresses of the backend service Pods.",
        "Create a target group. Add the EKS managed node group's Auto Scaling group as a target Create an Application Load Balancer with an HTTPS listener on port 443 to forward traffic to the target group.",
        "Create a target group. Add the EKS managed node group’s Auto Scaling group as a target. Create a Network Load Balancer with a TLS listener on port 443 to forward traffic to the target group."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 1"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has deployed an AWS Network Firewall firewall into a VPC. A network engineer needs to implement a solution to deliver Network Firewall flow logs to the company’s Amazon OpenSearch Service (Amazon Elasticsearch Service) cluster in the shortest possible time.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose delivery stream that includes the Amazon OpenSearch Service (Amazon Elasticsearch Service) cluster as the destination. Configure flow logs for the firewall Set the Kinesis Data Firehose delivery stream as the destination for the Network Firewall flow logs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an Amazon S3 bucket. Create an AWS Lambda function to load logs into the Amazon OpenSearch Service (Amazon Elasticsearch Service) cluster. Enable Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) notifications on the S3 bucket to invoke the Lambda function. Configure flow logs for the firewall. Set the S3 bucket as the destination.",
        "Configure flow logs for the firewall. Set the Amazon OpenSearch Service (Amazon Elasticsearch Service) cluster as the destination for the Network Firewall flow logs.",
        "Create an Amazon Kinesis data stream that includes the Amazon OpenSearch Service (Amazon Elasticsearch Service) cluster as the destination. Configure flow logs for the firewall. Set the Kinesis data stream as the destination for the Network Firewall flow logs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 2"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer is designing a hybrid networking environment that will connect a company's corporate network to the company's AWS environment. The AWS environment consists of 30 VPCs in 3 AWS Regions.\n\nThe network engineer needs to implement a solution to centrally filter traffic by using a firewall that the company's security team has approved. The solution must give all the VPCs the ability to connect to each other. Connectivity between AWS and the corporate network must meet a minimum bandwidth requirement of 2 Gbps.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy four 1 Gbps AWS Direct Connect connections in different Direct Connect locations to connect to the corporate network. Build a transit VIF on each connection to a Direct Connect gateway. Associate the Direct Connect gateway with a new transit gateway for each Region. Connect the transit gateways by using a transit gateway peering attachment. Configure the VIFs to use equal-cost multipath (ECMP) routing. Configure transit gateway route tables to route traffic to an inspection VPC. Deploy the approved firewall to the inspection VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy an IPsec VPN connection between the corporate network and a new transit gateway. Connect all VPCs to the transit gateway. Associate the approved firewall with the transit gateway.",
        "Deploy a single 10 Gbps AWS Direct Connect connection between the corporate network and virtual private gateway of each VPC. Connect the virtual private gateways to a Direct Connect gateway. Build an IPsec tunnel to a new transit VPC. Deploy the approved firewall to the transit VPC.",
        "Deploy two 1 Gbps AWS Direct Connect connections in different Direct Connect locations to connect to the corporate network. Build a transit VIF on each connection to a Direct Connect gateway. Associate the Direct Connect gateway with a new transit gateway for each Region. Configure the VIFs to use equal-cost multipath (ECMP) routing. Connect all the VPCs in the three Regions to the transit gateway. Configure the transit gateway route table to route traffic to an inspection VPDeploy the approved firewall to the inspection VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 3"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses an AWS Direct Connect private VIF with a link aggregation group (LAG) that consists of two 10 Gbps connections. The company's security team has implemented a new requirement for external network connections to provide layer 2 encryption. The company's network team plans to use MACsec support for Direct Connect to meet the new requirement.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network team take to implement this functionality? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new Direct Connect LAG with new circuits and ports that support MACsec.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Associate the Internet Key Exchange (IKE) with the existing LAG.",
        "Configure the MACsec encryption mode on the existing LAG.",
        "Configure the MACsec encryption mode on each Direct Connect connection that makes up the existing LAG."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Associate the MACsec Connectivity Association Key (CAK) and the Connection Key Name (CKN) with the new LAG.||Configure the MACsec encryption mode on the new LAG.",
        "code": "Question 4"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company recently implemented a security policy that prohibits developers from launching VPC network infrastructure. The policy states that any time a NAT gateway is launched in a VPC, the company's network security team must immediately receive an alert to terminate the NAT gateway. The network security team needs to implement a solution that can be deployed across AWS accounts with the least possible administrative overhead. The solution also must provide the network security team with a simple way to view compliance history.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a custom AWS Config rule that checks for NAT gateways in an AWS account. Configure the AWS Config rule to perform an AWS Systems Manager Automation remediation action to send an email alert and terminate the NAT gateway if a NAT gateway is detected. Deploy the AWS Config rule and the Systems Manager runbooks to each account by using AWS CloudFormation StackSets",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Develop a script that programmatically checks for NAT gateways in an AWS account, sends an email alert, and terminates the NAT gateway if a NAT gateway is detected. Deploy the script on an Amazon EC2 instance in each account. Use a cron job to run the script every 5 minutes. Log the results of the checks to an Amazon RDS for MySQL database.",
        "Create an AWS Lambda function that programmatically checks for NAT gateways in an AWS account, sends an email alert, and terminates the NAT gateway if a NAT gateway is detected. Deploy the Lambda function to each account by using AWS Serverless Application Model (AWS SAM) templates. Store the results of the checks on an Amazon OpenSearch Service cluster in each account.",
        "Enable Amazon GuardDuty. Create an Amazon EventBridge rule for the Behavior:EC2/NATGatewayCreation GuardDuty finding type. Configure the rule to invoke an AWS Step Functions state machine to send an email alert and terminate a NAT gateway if a NAT gateway is detected. Store the runtime log as a text file in an Amazon S3 bucket."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 5"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is running an online game on AWS. The game is played globally and is gaining popularity. Users are reporting problems with the game's responsiveness. Replay rates are dropping, and the company is losing subscribers. Game servers are located in the us-west-2 Region and use an Elastic Load Balancer to distribute client traffic.\n\nThe company has decided to deploy game servers to 11 additional AWS Regions to reduce the round-trip times of network traffic to game clients. A network engineer must design a DNS solution that uses Amazon Route 53 to ensure that user traffic is delivered to game servers with an optimal response time.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create Route 53 records for the Elastic Load Balancers in each Region. Specify a latency routing policy. Set the Region to the Region where the Elastic Load Balancer is deployed.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create Route 53 records for the Elastic Load Balancers in each Region. Specify a weighted routing policy. Calculate the weight by using the number of clients in each Region.",
        "Create Route 53 records for the Elastic Load Balancers in each Region. Specify a multivalue answer routing policy. Test latency from the game client, and connect to the server with the best response.",
        "Create Route 53 records for the Elastic Load Balancers in each Region. Specify a geolocation routing policy. Set the location to the Region where the Elastic Load Balancer is deployed."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 6"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer needs to build an encrypted connection between an on-premises data center and a VPC. The network engineer attaches the VPC to a virtual private gateway and sets up an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection. The VPN tunnel is UP after configuration and is working. However, during rekey for phase 2 of the VPN negotiation, the customer gateway device is receiving different parameters than the parameters that the device is configured to support.\n\nThe network engineer checks the IPsec configuration of the VPN tunnel. The network engineer notices that the customer gateway device is configured with the most secure encryption algorithms that the AWS Site-to-Site VPN configuration file provides.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to troubleshoot and correct the issue?",
      "correct_answer": "Check the native customer gateway logs. Restrict the VPN tunnel options to the specific VPN parameters that the customer gateway requires.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Check the native virtual private gateway logs. Restrict the VPN tunnel options to the specific VPN parameters that the virtual private gateway requires.",
        "Check Amazon CloudWatch logs of the virtual private gateway. Restrict the VPN tunnel options to the specific VPN parameters that the virtual private gateway requires.",
        "Check Amazon CloudWatch logs of the customer gateway. Restrict the VPN tunnel options to the specific VPN parameters that the customer gateway requires."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 7"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is growing rapidly. Data transfers between the company's on-premises systems and Amazon EC2 instances that run in VPCs are limited by the throughput of a single AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection between the company's on-premises data center firewall and an AWS Transit Gateway.\n\nA network engineer must resolve the throttling by designing a solution that is highly available and secure. The solution also must scale the VPN throughput from on premises to the VPC resources to support the increase in traffic.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure multiple dynamic BGP-based Site-to-Site VPN connections to the transit gateway. Configure equal-cost multi-path routing (ECMP).",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure multiple static routing-based Site-to-Site VPN connections to the transit gateway. Configure equal-cost multi-path routing (ECMP).",
        "Configure a new Site-to-Site VPN connection to the transit gateway. Enable acceleration for the Site-to-Site VPN connection.",
        "Configure a software appliance-based VPN connection over the internet from the on-premises firewall to an EC2 instance that has a large instance size and networking capabilities."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 8"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses Amazon Route 53 to host a public hosted zone for example.com. A network engineer recently reduced the TTL on several records to 60 seconds. The network engineer wants to assess whether the change has increased the number of queries to Route 53 beyond the expected levels that the company identified before the change. The network engineer must obtain the number of queries that have been made to the example.com public hosted zone.\n\nWhich solution will provide this information?",
      "correct_answer": "Use Amazon CloudWatch to access the AWS/Route 53 namespace and to check the DNSQueries metric for the public hosted zone.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new trail in AWS CloudTrail to include Route 53 data events. Send logs to Amazon CloudWatch Logs. Set up a CloudWatch metric filter to count the number of queries and create graphs.",
        "Use Amazon CloudWatch to access the AWS/Route 53 Resolver namespace and to check the InboundQueryVolume metric for a specific endpoint.",
        "Configure logging to Amazon CloudWatch for the public hosted zone. Set up a CloudWatch metric filter to count the number of queries and create graphs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 9"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is establishing connectivity between its on-premises site and an existing VPC on AWS to meet a new security requirement. According to the new requirement, all public DNS queries must use an on-premises DNS security solution. The company's security team has allowed an exception for the AWS service endpoints because the company is using VPC endpoints to access AWS services.\n\nWhich combination of steps should a network engineer take to configure the architecture to meet these requirements? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create an Amazon Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoint. Associate this endpoint with the VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a system rule for the domain name “.” (dot) with a target IP address of the on-premises DNS security solution.",
        "Create a new DHCP options set that provides the IP address of the on-premises DNS security solution. Update the VPC to use this new DHCP options set.",
        "Create an Amazon Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint. Associate this endpoint with the VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create a system rule for the domain name amazonaws.com.||Create a forwarding rule for the domain name “.” (dot) with a target IP address of the on-premises DNS security solution.",
        "code": "Question 10"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer is designing the DNS architecture for a new AWS environment. The environment must be able to resolve DNS names of endpoints on premises, and the on-premises systems must be able to resolve the names of AWS endpoints. The DNS architecture must give individual accounts the ability to manage subdomains.\n\nThe network engineer needs to create a single set of rules that will work across multiple accounts to control this behavior. In addition, the network engineer must use AWS native services whenever possible.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network engineer take to meet these requirements? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create an Amazon Route 53 private hosted zone for the overall cloud domain. Plan to create subdomains that align to other AWS accounts that are associated with the central Route 53 private hosted zone.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create AWS Directory Service for Microsoft Active Directory server endpoints in the central AWS account that hosts the private hosted zone for the overall cloud domain. Create a conditional forwarding rule in Microsoft Active Directory DNS to forward traffic to a DNS resolver endpoint on premises. Create another rule to forward traffic between subdomains to the VPC resolver.",
        "Ensure that networking exists between the other accounts and the central account so that traffic can reach the AWS Directory Service for Microsoft Active Directory DNS endpoints.",
        "Ensure that networking exists between the other accounts and the central account so that traffic can reach the Amazon Route 53 Resolver endpoints."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create Amazon Route 53 Resolver inbound and outbound endpoints in the central AWS account that hosts the private hosted zone for the overall cloud domain. Create a forwarding rule to forward traffic to a DNS resolver endpoint on premises. Create another rule to forward traffic between subdomains to the Resolver inbound endpoint.||Share the Amazon Route 53 Resolver rules between accounts by using AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM). Ensure that networking exists between the other accounts and the central account so that traffic can reach the Route 53 Resolver endpoints.",
        "code": "Question 11"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate its DNS registrar and DNS hosting to Amazon Route 53. The company website receives tens of thousands of visits each day, and the company’s current DNS provider cannot keep up. The company wants to migrate as quickly as possible but cannot tolerate any downtime.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Copy all DNS records from the existing DNS servers to a Route 53 public hosted zone. Update the name servers with the existing registrar to use the Route 53 name servers for the hosted zone. When the changes have propagated, perform a domain name transfer to Route 53.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Transfer the domain name to Route 53. Create a Route 53 private hosted zone, and copy all the existing DNS records. Update the name servers on the domain to use the name servers that are specified in the newly created private hosted zone.",
        "Copy all DNS records from the existing DNS servers to a Route 53 private hosted zone. Update the name servers with the existing registrar to use the private hosted zone name servers. Transfer the domain name to Route 53. Ensure that all the changes have propagated.",
        "Transfer the domain name to Route 53. Create a Route 53 public hosted zone, and copy all the existing DNS records. Set the TTL value on each record to 1 second. Update the name servers on the domain to use the name servers that are specified in the newly created public hosted zone."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 12"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using custom DNS servers that run BIND for name resolution in its VPCs. The VPCs are deployed across multiple AWS accounts that are part of the same organization in AWS Organizations. All the VPCs are connected to a transit gateway. The BIND servers are running in a central VPC and are configured to forward all queries for an on-premises DNS domain to DNS servers that are hosted in an on-premises data center. To ensure that all the VPCs use the custom DNS servers, a network engineer has configured a VPC DHCP options set in all the VPCs that specifies the custom DNS servers to be used as domain name servers.\n\nMultiple development teams in the company want to use Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS). A development team has created a new EFS file system but cannot mount the file system to one of its Amazon EC2 instances. The network engineer discovers that the EC2 instance cannot resolve the IP address for the EFS mount point fs-33444567d.efs.us-east-1.amazonaws.com. The network engineer needs to implement a solution so that development teams throughout the organization can mount EFS file systems.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create an Amazon Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoint in the central VPC. Update all the VPC DHCP options sets to use AmazonProvidedDNS for name resolution.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure the BIND DNS servers in the central VPC to forward queries for efs.us-east-1.amazonaws.com to the Amazon provided DNS server (169.254.169.253).",
        "Create an Amazon Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint in the central VPUpdate all the VPC DHCP options sets to use the Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint in the central VPC for name resolution.",
        "Create an Amazon Route 53 private hosted zone for the efs.us-east-1.amazonaws.com domain. Associate the private hosted zone with the VPC where the EC2 instance is deployed. Create an A record for fs-33444567d.efs.us-east-1.amazonaws.com in the private hosted zone. Configure the A record to return the mount target of the EFS mount point."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create an Amazon Route 53 Resolver rule to forward queries for the on-premises domain to the on-premises DNS servers. Share the rule with the organization by using AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM). Associate the rule with all the VPCs.",
        "code": "Question 13"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an AWS account with four VPCs in the us-east-1 Region. The VPCs consist of a development VPC and three production VPCs that host various workloads.\n\nThe company has extended its on-premises data center to AWS with AWS Direct Connect by using a Direct Connect gateway. The company now wants to establish connectivity to its production VPCs and development VPC from on premises. The production VPCs are allowed to route data to each other. However, the development VPC must be isolated from the production VPCs. No data can flow between the development VPC and the production VPCs.\n\nIn preparation to implement this solution, a network engineer creates a transit gateway with a single transit gateway route table. Default route table association and default route table propagation are turned off. The network engineer attaches the production VPCs, the development VPC, and the Direct Connect gateway to the transit gateway. For each VPC route table, the network engineer adds a route to 0.0.0.0/0 with the transit gateway as the next destination.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network engineer take next to complete this solution? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Associate the production VPC attachments with the existing transit gateway route table. Propagate the routes from these attachments.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Associate all the attachments with the existing transit gateway route table. Propagate the routes from these attachments.",
        "Change the security group inbound rules on the existing transit gateway network interfaces in the development VPC to allow connections to and from the on-premises CIDR range only.",
        "Create a new transit gateway with default route table association and default route table propagation turned on. Attach the Direct Connect gateway and development VPC to the new transit gateway."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Associate the Direct Connect gateway attachment with the existing transit gateway route table. Propagate the Direct Connect gateway attachment to this route table.||Create a new transit gateway route table. Associate the new route table with the development VPC attachment. Propagate the Direct Connect gateway and development VPC attachment to the new route table.",
        "code": "Question 14"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer needs to provide dual-stack connectivity between a company's office location and an AWS account. The company's on-premises router supports dual-stack connectivity, and the VPC has been configured with dual-stack support. The company has set up two AWS Direct Connect connections to the office location. This connectivity must be highly available and must be reliable for latency-sensitive traffic.\n\nWhich solutions will meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Configure a single private VIF on each Direct Connect connection. Add both IPv4 and IPv6 peering to each private VIF. Configure the on- premises equipment with the AWS provided BGP neighbors to advertise IPv4 routes on the IPv4 peering and IPv6 routes on the IPv6 peering. Enable Bidirectional Forwarding Detection (BFD) on all peering sessions.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure a single private VIF and IPv4 peering on each Direct Connect connection. Configure the on-premises equipment with this peering to advertise the IPv6 routes in the same BGP neighbor configuration. Enable Bidirectional Forwarding Detection (BFD) on all peering sessions.",
        "Configure two private VIFs on each Direct Connect connection: one private VIF with the IPv4 address family and one private VIF with the IPv6 address family. Configure the on-premises equipment with the AWS provided BGP neighbors to advertise all IPv4 routes and IPv6 routes on all peering sessions. Keep the Bidirectional Forwarding Detection (BFD) configuration unchanged.",
        "Configure two private VIFs on each Direct Connect connection: one private VIF with the IPv4 address family and one private VIF with the IPv6 address family. Configure the on-premises equipment with the AWS provided BGP neighbors to advertise IPv4 routes on the IPv4 peering and IPv6 routes on the IPv6 peering. Reduce the BGP hello timer to 5 seconds on both the on-premises equipment and the Direct Connect configuration."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Configure two private VIFs on each Direct Connect connection: one private VIF with the IPv4 address family and one private VIF with the IPv6 address family. Configure the on-premises equipment with the AWS provided BGP neighbors to advertise IPv4 routes on the IPv4 peering and IPv6 routes on the IPv6 peering. Enable Bidirectional Forwarding Detection (BFD) on all peering sessions.",
        "code": "Question 15"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company recently started using AWS Client VPN to give its remote users the ability to access resources in multiple peered VPCs and resources in the company's on-premises data center. The Client VPN endpoint route table has a single entry of 0.0.0.0/0. The Client VPN endpoint is using a new security group that has no inbound rules and a single outbound rule that allows all traffic to 0.0.0.0/0.\n\nMultiple remote users report that web search results are showing incorrect geographic location information for the users.\n\nWhich combination of steps should a network engineer take to resolve this issue with the LEAST amount of service interruption? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Enable the split-tunnel option on the Client VPN endpoint.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Switch users to AWS Site-to-Site VPNs.",
        "Remove the 0.0.0.0/0 outbound rule from the security group that the Client VPN endpoint uses.",
        "Delete and recreate the Client VPN endpoint in a different VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Add routes for the peered VPCs and for the on-premises data center to the Client VPN route table.||Remove the 0.0.0.0/0 entry from the Client VPN endpoint route table.",
        "code": "Question 16"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has set up hybrid connectivity between its VPCs and its on-premises data center. The company has the on-premises.example.com subdomain configured at its DNS server in the on-premises data center. The company is using the aws.example.com subdomain for workloads that run on AWS across different VPCs and accounts. Resources in both environments can access each other by using IP addresses. The company wants workloads in the VPCs to be able to access resources on premises by using the on-premises.example.com DNS names.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with MINIMUM management of resources?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an Amazon Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoint. Configure a Resolver rule that conditionally forwards DNS queries for on-premises.example.com to the on-premises DNS server. Associate the rule with the VPCs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an Amazon Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint and a Resolver outbound endpoint. Configure a Resolver rule that conditionally forwards DNS queries for on-premises.example.com to the on-premises DNS server. Associate the rule with the VPCs.",
        "Launch an Amazon EC2 instance. Install and configure BIND software to conditionally forward DNS queries for on-premises.example.com to the on-premises DNS server. Configure the EC2 instance's IP address as a custom DNS server in each VPC.",
        "Launch an Amazon EC2 instance in each VPC. Install and configure BIND software to conditionally forward DNS queries for on-premises.example.com to the on-premises DNS server. Configure the EC2 instance's IP address as a custom DNS server in each VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 17"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is in the early stage of AWS Cloud adoption. The company has an application that is running in an on-premises data center in Asia. The company needs to deploy new applications in the us-east-1 Region. The applications in the cloud need connectivity to the on-premises data center.\n\nThe company needs to set up a communication channel between AWS and the data center. The solution must improve latency, minimize the possibility of performance impact from transcontinental routing over the public internet, and encrypt data in transit.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements in the LEAST amount of time?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection with acceleration turned on. Create a transit gateway. Attach the Site-to-Site VPN connection to the transit gateway. Create a transit gateway attachment to the VPC where the applications will be deployed.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection with acceleration turned on. Create a virtual private gateway. Attach the Site-to-Site VPN connection to the virtual private gateway. Attach the virtual private gateway to the VPC where the applications will be deployed.",
        "Create an AWS Direct Connect connection. Create a virtual private gateway. Create a public VIF and a private VIF that use the virtual private gateway. Create an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection over the public VIF.",
        "Create an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection with acceleration turned off. Create a transit gateway. Attach the Site-to-Site VPN connection to the transit gateway. Create a transit gateway attachment to the VPC where the applications will be deployed."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 18"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is moving its record-keeping application to the AWS Cloud. All traffic between the company's on-premises data center and AWS must be encrypted at all times and at every transit device during the migration.\n\nThe application will reside across multiple Availability Zones in a single AWS Region. The application will use existing 10 Gbps AWS Direct Connect dedicated connections with a MACsec capable port. A network engineer must ensure that the Direct Connect connection is secured accordingly at every transit device.\n\nThe network engineer creates a Connection Key Name and Connectivity Association Key (CKN/CAK) pair for the MACsec secret key.\n\nWhich combination of additional steps should the network engineer take to meet the requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Configure the on-premises router with the MACsec secret key.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Update the connection's MACsec encryption mode to must_encrypt. Then associate the CKN/CAK pair with the connection.",
        "Update the connection's MACsec encryption mode to should encrypt. Then associate the CKN/CAK pair with the connection.",
        "Associate the CKN/CAK pair with the connection. Then update the connection’s MACsec encryption mode to should_encrypt."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Associate the CKN/CAK pair with the connection. Then update the connection's MACsec encryption mode to must_encrypt.",
        "code": "Question 19"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer is designing hybrid connectivity with AWS Direct Connect and AWS Transit Gateway. A transit gateway is attached to a Direct Connect gateway and 19 VPCs across different AWS accounts. Two new VPCs are being attached to the transit gateway. The IP address administrator has assigned 10.0.32.0/21 to the first VPC and 10.0.40.0/21 to the second VPC. The prefix list has one CIDR block remaining before the prefix list reaches the quota for the maximum number of entries.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to advertise the routes from AWS to on premises to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Add 10.0.32.0/20 to the allowed prefix list.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Add 10.0.32.0/21 and 10.0.40.0/21 to both AWS managed prefix lists.",
        "Add 10.0.32.0/21 and 10.0.40.0/21 to the allowed prefix list.",
        "Add 10.0.32.0/20 to both AWS managed prefix lists."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 20"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Two companies are merging. The companies have a large AWS presence with multiple VPCs and are designing connectivity between their AWS networks. Both companies are using AWS Direct Connect with a Direct Connect gateway. Each company also has a transit gateway and multiple AWS Site-to-Site VPN connections from its transit gateway to on-premises resources. The new solution must optimize network visibility, throughput, logging, and monitoring.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure transit gateway peering between each company's transit gateway. Configure VPC Flow Logs for all VPCs. Publish the flow logs to Amazon CloudWatch. Use AWS Transit Gateway Network Manager to monitor the transit gateways, their respective connections, and the transit gateway peering link.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure a Site-to-Site VPN connection between each company's transit gateway to establish reachability between the respective networks. Configure VPC Flow Logs for all VPCs. Publish the flow logs to Amazon CloudWatch. Use VPC Reachability Analyzer to monitor connectivity.",
        "Configure a Site-to-Site VPN connection between each company's transit gateway to establish reachability between the respective networks. Configure VPC Flow Logs for all VPCs. Publish the flow logs to Amazon CloudWatch. Use AWS Transit Gateway Network Manager to monitor the transit gateways and their respective connections.",
        "Configure transit gateway peering between each company's transit gateway. Configure VPC Flow Logs for all VPCs. Publish the flow logs to Amazon CloudWatch. Use VPC Reachability Analyzer to monitor connectivity."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 21"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a single VPC in the us-east-1 Region. The company is planning to set up a new VPC in the us-east-2 Region. The existing VPC has an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection to the company's on-premises environment and uses a virtual private gateway.\n\nA network engineer needs to implement a solution to establish connectivity between the existing VPC and the new VPC. The solution also must implement support for IPv6 for the new VPC. The company has new on-premises resources that need to connect to VPC resources by using IPv6 addresses.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a transit gateway in us-east-1 and in us-east-2. Attach the existing VPC and the new VPC to each transit gateway. Create a new Site-to-Site VPN connection to each transit gateway with IPv4 and IPv6 support. Configure transit gateway peering. Configure routing between the VPCs and the on-premises environment.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new virtual private gateway in us-east-1. Attach the new virtual private gateway to the new VPC. Create two new Site-to-Site VPN connections to the new virtual private gateway with IPv4 and IPv6 support. Configure routing between the VPCs by using VPC peering.",
        "Create a new virtual private gateway in us-east-2. Attach the new virtual private gateway to the new VPCreate two new Site-to-Site VPN connections to the new virtual private gateway with IPv4 and IPv6 support. Configure routing between the VPCs by using VPC peering.",
        "Create a transit gateway in us-east-1. Attach the existing VPC and the new VPC to the transit gateway. Create two new Site-to-Site VPN connections to the transit gateway with IPv4 and IPv6 support. Configure transit gateway peering. Configure routing between the VPCs and the on-premises environment."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 22"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer is working on a private DNS design to integrate AWS workloads and on-premises resources. The AWS deployment consists of five VPCs in the eu-west-1 Region that connect to the on-premises network over AWS Direct Connect. The VPCs communicate with each other by using a transit gateway. Each VPC is associated with a private hosted zone that uses the aws.example.internal domain. The network engineer creates an Amazon Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoint in a shared services VPC and attaches the shared services VPC to the transit gateway.\n\nThe network engineer is implementing a solution for DNS resolution. Queries for hostnames that end with aws.example.internal must use the private hosted zone. Queries for hostnames that end with all other domains must be forwarded to a private on-premises DNS resolver.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Add a forwarding rule for “.” that targets the Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoint.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Add a forwarding rule for “*” that targets the on-premises server's DNS IP address. Add a system rule for aws.example.internal that targets Route 53 Resolver.",
        "Add a forwarding rule for aws.example.internal that targets Route 53 Resolver. Add a system rule for “.” that targets the Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoint.",
        "Add a forwarding rule for “*” that targets the Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoint."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 23"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An ecommerce company is hosting a web application on Amazon EC2 instances to handle continuously changing customer demand. The EC2 instances are part of an Auto Scaling group. The company wants to implement a solution to distribute traffic from customers to the EC2 instances. The company must encrypt all traffic at all stages between the customers and the application servers. No decryption at intermediate points is allowed.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a Network Load Balancer (NLB). Add a TCP listener to the NLB. Configure the Auto Scaling group to register instances with the NLB's target group.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an Application Load Balancer (ALB). Add an HTTPS listener to the ALB. Configure the Auto Scaling group to register instances with the ALB's target group.",
        "Create an Amazon CloudFront distribution. Configure the distribution with a custom SSL/TLS certificate. Set the Auto Scaling group as the distribution's origin.",
        "Create a Gateway Load Balancer (GLB). Configure the Auto Scaling group to register instances with the GLB's target group."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 24"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A global film production company uses the AWS Cloud to encode and store its video content before distribution. The company's three global offices are connected to the us-east-1 Region through AWS Site-to-Site VPN links that terminate on a transit gateway with BGP routing activated.\n\nThe company recently started to produce content at a higher resolution to support 8K streaming. The size of the content files has increased to three times the size of the content files from the previous format. Uploads of files to Amazon EC2 instances are taking 10 times longer than they did with the previous format.\n\nWhich actions should a network engineer recommend to reduce the upload times? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create a second VPN tunnel from each office location to the transit gateway. Activate equal-cost multi-path (ECMP) routing.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Modify the transit gateway to activate Jumbo MTU on the VPN tunnels to each office location.",
        "Upgrade each EC2 instance to a modern instance type. Activate Jumbo MTU in the operating system.",
        "Replace the existing VPN tunnels with new tunnels that have IGMP activated."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Replace the existing VPN tunnels with new tunnels that have acceleration activated.",
        "code": "Question 25"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An application team for a startup company is deploying a new multi-tier application into the AWS Cloud. The application will be hosted on a fleet of Amazon EC2 instances that run in an Auto Scaling group behind a publicly accessible Network Load Balancer (NLB). The application requires the clients to work with UDP traffic and TCP traffic.\n\nIn the near term, the application will serve only users within the same geographic location. The application team plans to extend the application to a global audience and will move the deployment to multiple AWS Regions around the world to bring the application closer to the end users. The application team wants to use the new Regions to deploy new versions of the application and wants to be able to control the amount of traffic that each Region receives during these rollouts. In addition, the application team must minimize first-byte latency and jitter (randomized delay) for the end users.\n\nHow should the application team design the network architecture for the application to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an AWS Global Accelerator accelerator and listeners for the required ports. Configure endpoint groups for each Region. Configure a traffic dial for the endpoint groups to control traffic to the newer Regional deployments. Register the NLBs with the endpoint groups.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an Amazon CloudFront distribution to align to each Regional deployment. Set the NLB for each Region as the origin for each CloudFront distribution. Use an Amazon Route 53 weighted routing policy to control traffic to the newer Regional deployments.",
        "Use Amazon S3 Transfer Acceleration for the application in each Region. Adjust the amount of traffic that each Region receives from the Transfer Acceleration endpoints to the Regional NLBs.",
        "Create an Amazon CloudFront distribution that includes an origin group. Set the NLB for each Region as the origins for the origin group. Use an Amazon Route 53 latency routing policy to control traffic to the new Regional deployments."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 26"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is deploying a new stateless web application on AWS. The web application will run on Amazon EC2 instances in private subnets behind an Application Load Balancer. The EC2 instances are in an Auto Scaling group. The web application has a stateful management application for administration that will run on EC2 instances that are in a separate Auto Scaling group.\n\nThe company wants to access the management application by using the same URL as the web application, with a path prefix of/management. The protocol, hostname, and port number must be the same for the web application and the management application. Access to the management application must be restricted to the company's on-premises IP address space. An SSL/TLS certificate from AWS Certificate Manager (ACM) will protect the web application.\n\nWhich combination of steps should a network engineer take to meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Insert a rule for the load balancer HTTPS listener. Configure the rule to check the path-pattern condition type for the /management prefix and to check the source-ip condition type for the on-premises IP address space. Forward requests to the management application target group if there is a match. Edit the management application target group and enable stickiness.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Modify the default rule for the load balancer HTTPS listener. Configure the rule to check the path-pattern condition type for the /management prefix and to check the source-ip condition type for the on-premises IP address space. Forward requests to the management application target group if there is not a match. Enable group-level stickiness in the rule attributes.",
        "Insert a rule for the load balancer HTTPS listener. Configure the rule to check the path-pattern condition type for the /management prefix and to check the X-Forwarded-For HTTP header for the on-premises IP address space. Forward requests to the management application target group if there is a match. Enable group-level stickiness in the rule attributes.",
        "Modify the default rule for the load balancer HTTPS listener. Configure the rule to check the path-pattern condition type for the /management prefix and to check the source-ip condition type for the on-premises IP address space. Forward requests to the web application target group if there is not a match."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Forward all requests to the web application target group. Edit the web application target group and disable stickiness.",
        "code": "Question 27"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company deploys a software solution on Amazon EC2 instances that are in a cluster placement group. The solution's UI is a single HTML page. The HTML file size is 1,024 bytes. The software processes files that exceed 1,024 MB in size. The software shares files over the network to clients upon request. The files are shared with the Don't Fragment flag set. Elastic network interfaces of the EC2 instances are set up with jumbo frames.\n\nThe UI is always accessible from all allowed source IP addresses, regardless of whether the source IP addresses are within a VPC, on the internet, or on premises. However, clients sometimes do not receive files that they request because the files fail to travel successfully from the software to the clients.\n\nWhich options provide a possible root cause of these failures? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "The source IP addresses are from on-premises hosts that are routed over AWS Site-to-Site VPN.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The source IP addresses are from on-premises hosts that are routed over AWS Direct Connect.",
        "The security group of the EC2 instances does not allow ICMP traffic.",
        "The operating system of the EC2 instances does not support jumbo frames."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "The source IP addresses are from hosts that connect over the public internet.",
        "code": "Question 28"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has users who work from home. The company wants to move these users to Amazon WorkSpaces for additional security visibility.\n\nThe company has deployed WorkSpaces in its own AWS account in VPC A. A network engineer decides to provide the security visibility by using two firewall appliances behind a Gateway Load Balancer (GWLB). The network engineer provisions another VPC, VPC B, in a separate account and deploys the two firewall appliances in separate Availability Zones.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to configure the network connectivity for this solution?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a GWLB in VPC B with the firewall appliance instances as targets. Use the GWLB to create a GWLB endpoint. Add the AWS principal ARN of the WorkSpaces account to the principal allow list of the GWLB endpoint. In the WorkSpaces account, create a VPC endpoint and specify the service name that the AWS Management Console provides for the GWLB endpoint. Modify the route tables of VPC A to point the default route to the GWLB endpoint.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a GWLB in VPC A with the firewall appliance instances as targets. Use the GWLB to create a GWLB endpoint. Add the AWS principal ARN of the WorkSpaces account to the principal allow list of the GWLB endpoint. In the WorkSpaces account, create a VPC endpoint and specify the service name that the AWS Management Console provides for the GWLB endpoint. Modify the route tables of VPC A to point the default route to the VPC endpoint.",
        "Create a GWLB in VPC B with the firewall appliance instances as targets. Use the GWLB to create a GWLB endpoint. Add the AWS principal ARN of the WorkSpaces account to the principal allow list of the GWLB endpoint. In the WorkSpaces account, create a VPC endpoint and specify the service name that the AWS Management Console provides for the GWLB endpoint. Modify the route tables of VPC A to point the WorkSpaces subnet to the VPC endpoint.",
        "Create a GWLB in VPC B with the firewall appliance instances as targets. Use the GWLB to create a GWLB endpoint. Add the AWS principal ARN of the account that contains the firewall appliances to the principal allow list of the GWLB endpoint. In the WorkSpaces account, create a VPC endpoint and specify the service name that the AWS Management Console provides for the GWLB endpoint. Modify the route tables of VPC A to point the default route to the VPC endpoint."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 29"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company plans to run a computationally intensive data processing application on AWS. The data is highly sensitive. The VPC must have no direct internet access, and the company has applied strict network security to control access.\n\nData scientists will transfer data from the company's on-premises data center to the instances by using an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection. The on-premises data center uses the network range 172.31.0.0/20 and will use the network range 172.31.16.0/20 in the application VPC.\n\nThe data scientists report that they can start new instances of the application but that they cannot transfer any data from the on-premises data center. A network engineer enables VPC flow logs and sends a ping to one of the instances to test reachability. The flow logs show the following:\n\nThe network engineer must recommend a solution that will give the data scientists the ability to transfer data from the on-premises data center.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Modify the network ACLs for the VPC subnet. Add an outbound rule to allow traffic from the VPC subnet range to the on-premises data center network range.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Modify the security group for the application. Add an inbound rule to allow traffic from the on-premises data center network range to the application.",
        "Modify the network ACLs for the VPC subnet. Add an inbound rule to allow traffic from the on-premises data center network range to the VPC subnet range.",
        "Modify the security group for the application. Add an outbound rule to allow traffic from the application to the on-premises data center network range."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 30"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to temporarily scale out capacity for an on-premises application and wants to deploy new servers on Amazon EC2 instances. A network engineer must design the networking solution for the connectivity and for the application on AWS.\n\nThe EC2 instances need to share data with the existing servers in the on-premises data center. The servers must not be accessible from the internet. All traffic to the internet must route through the firewall in the on-premises data center. The servers must be able to access a third-party web application.\n\nWhich configuration will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a VPC that has private subnets. Create a customer gateway, a virtual private gateway, and an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection. Create a route table, and associate the private subnets with the route table. Add a default route to the virtual private gateway. Deploy the application to the private subnets.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a VPC that has public subnets and private subnets. Create a customer gateway, a virtual private gateway, and an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection. Create a NAT gateway in a public subnet. Create a route table, and associate the public subnets with the route table. Add a default route to the internet gateway. Create a route table, and associate the private subnets with the route table. Add a default route to the NAT gateway. Add routes for the data center subnets to the virtual private gateway. Deploy the application to the private subnets.",
        "Create a VPC that has public subnets. Create a customer gateway, a virtual private gateway, and an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection. Create a route table, and associate the public subnets with the route table. Add a default route to the internet gateway. Add routes for the on-premises data center subnets to the virtual private gateway. Deploy the application to the public subnets.",
        "Create a VPC that has public subnets and private subnets. Create a customer gateway, a virtual private gateway, and an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection. Create a route table, and associate the public subnets with the route table. Add a default route to the internet gateway. Create a route table, and associate the private subnets with the route table. Add routes for the on-premises data center subnets to the virtual private gateway. Deploy the application to the private subnets."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 31"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is deploying a web application into two AWS Regions. The company has one VPC in each Region. Each VPC has three Amazon EC2 instances as web servers behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). The company already has configured an Amazon Route 53 public hosted zone for example.com. Users will access the application by using the fully qualified domain name (FQDN) of app.example.com.\n\nThe company needs a DNS solution that allows global users to access the application. The solution must route the users' requests to the Region that provides the lowest response time. The solution must fail over to the Region that provides the next-lowest response time if the application is unavailable in the initially intended Region.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "For each ALB, create an A record that has a latency-based routing policy to route app.example.com as an alias to the ALB. Set the value for Evaluate Target Health to Yes for the records.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "For each ALB, create an A record that has a geolocation routing policy to route app.example.com to the IP addresses of the ALB. Configure a Route 53 HTTP health check that monitors each ALB by IP address. Associate the health check with the A records.",
        "Create an A record that has a geolocation routing policy to route app.example.com to the IP addresses for both ALBs. Configure a Route 53 health check that monitors TCP port 80 for each ALB by IP address. Associate the health check with the A records.",
        "Create an A record that has a latency-based routing policy to route app.example.com as an alias to one of the ALBs. Configure a Route 53 health check that monitors TCP port 80 for each ALB by IP address. Associate the health check with the A records."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 32"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A consulting company manages AWS accounts for its customers. One of the company's customers needs to add intrusion prevention for its environment without having to re-architect the environment. The customer's environment includes five VPCs in two AWS Regions in the United States. VPC-to-VPC connectivity is achieved through VPC peering. The customer does not plan to increase the number of VPCs within the next 2 years. The solution must accommodate unencrypted traffic.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use an AWS Network Firewall distributed deployment model in each VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure VPC security groups and network ACLs.",
        "Use an AWS Network Firewall centralized deployment model in each VPC.",
        "Deploy AWS Shield in each VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 33"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company hosts its IT infrastructure in an on-premises data center. The company wants to migrate the infrastructure to the AWS Cloud in phases. A network engineer wants to set up a 10 Gbps AWS Direct Connect dedicated connection between the on-premises data center and VPCs. The company's network provider needs 3 months to provision the Direct Connect connection.\n\nIn the meantime, the network engineer implements a temporary solution by deploying an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection that terminates to a virtual private gateway. The network engineer observes that the bandwidth of the Site-to-Site VPN connection is capped at 1.25 Gbps despite a powerful customer gateway device.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to improve the VPN connection bandwidth before the implementation of the Direct Connect connection?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a transit gateway. Attach the VPCs to the transit gateway. Create several additional Site-to-Site VPN connections that terminate on the transit gateway. Configure equal-cost multi-path (ECMP) routing to use all the VPN connections simultaneously.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Contact AWS Support to request a bandwidth quota increase for the existing Site-to-Site VPN connection.",
        "Discuss the issue with the hardware vendor. Buy a bigger and more powerful customer gateway device that has faster encryption and decryption capabilities.",
        "Create several additional Site-to-Site VPN connections that terminate on the same virtual gateway. Configure equal-cost multi-path (ECMP) routing to use all the VPN connections simultaneously."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 34"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has two on-premises data center locations. There is a company-managed router at each data center. Each data center has a dedicated AWS Direct Connect connection to a Direct Connect gateway through a private virtual interface. The router for the first location is advertising 110 routes to the Direct Connect gateway by using BGP, and the router for the second location is advertising 60 routes to the Direct Connect gateway by using BGP. The Direct Connect gateway is attached to a company VPC through a virtual private gateway.\n\nA network engineer receives reports that resources in the VPC are not reachable from various locations in either data center. The network engineer checks the VPC route table and sees that the routes from the first data center location are not being populated into the route table. The network engineer must resolve this issue in the most operationally efficient manner.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Change the router configurations to summarize the advertised routes.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Remove the Direct Connect gateway, and create a new private virtual interface from each company router to the virtual private gateway of the VPC.",
        "Open a support ticket to increase the quota on advertised routes to the VPC route table.",
        "Create an AWS Transit Gateway. Attach the transit gateway to the VPC, and connect the Direct Connect gateway to the transit gateway."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 35"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has business operations in the United States and in Europe. The company's public applications are running on AWS and use three transit gateways. The transit gateways are located in the us-west-2, us-east-1, and eu-central-1 Regions. All the transit gateways are connected to each other in a full mesh configuration.\n\nThe company accidentally removes the route to the eu-central-1 VPCs from the us-west-2 transit gateway route table. The company also accidentally removes the route to the us-west-2 VPCs from the eu-central-1 transit gateway route table.\n\nHow can a network engineer identify the misconfiguration with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Use the Route Analyzer feature for AWS Transit Gateway Network Manager.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use the AWSSupport-SetupIPMonitoringFromVPC AWS Systems Manager Automation runbook. Push network telemetry data to Amazon CloudWatch Logs for analysis.",
        "Use VPC flow logs in eu-central-1 and us-west-2 to analyze the missing routes.",
        "Use Amazon VPC Traffic Mirroring in eu-central-1 or us-west-2 to take packet captures and troubleshoot the connectivity issues."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 36"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A marketing company is using hybrid infrastructure through AWS Direct Connect links and a software-defined wide area network (SD-WAN) overlay to connect its branch offices. The company connects multiple VPCs to a third-party SD-WAN appliance transit VPC within the same account by using AWS Site-to-Site VPNs.\n\nThe company is planning to connect more VPCs to the SD-WAN appliance transit VPC. However, the company faces challenges of scalability, route table limitations, and higher costs with the existing architecture. A network engineer must design a solution to resolve these issues and remove dependencies.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST amount of operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure a transit gateway to attach the VPCs. Configure a transit gateway Connect attachment for the third-party SD-WAN appliance transit VPC. Use transit gateway Connect native integration of SD-WAN virtual hubs with AWS Transit Gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure a transit gateway to attach the VPCs. Configure a Site-to-Site VPN connection between the transit gateway and the third-party SD-WAN appliance transit VPC. Use the SD-WAN overlay links to connect to the branch offices.",
        "Configure a transit gateway to attach the VPCs. Configure VPC peering between the VPCs and the third-party SD-WAN appliance transit VPUse the SD-WAN overlay links to connect to the branch offices.",
        "Configure VPC peering between the VPCs and the third-party SD-WAN appliance transit VPC. Use transit gateway Connect native integration of SD-WAN virtual hubs with AWS Transit Gateway."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 37"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is running a hybrid cloud environment. The company has multiple AWS accounts as part of an organization in AWS Organizations. The company needs a solution to manage a list of IPv4 on-premises hosts that will be allowed to access resources in AWS. The solution must provide version control for the list of IPv4 addresses and must make the list available to the AWS accounts in the organization.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a customer-managed prefix list. Add entries for the initial list of on-premises IPv4 hosts. Create a resource share in AWS Resource Access Manager. Add the managed prefix list to the resource share. Share the resource with the organization.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a customer-managed prefix list. Add entries for the initial list of on-premises IPv4 hosts. Use AWS Firewall Manager to share the managed prefix list with the organization.",
        "Create a security group. Add inbound rule entries for the initial list of on-premises IPv4 hosts. Create a resource share in AWS Resource Access Manager. Add the security group to the resource share. Share the resource with the organization.",
        "Create an Amazon DynamoDB table. Add entries for the initial list of on-premises IPv4 hosts. Create an AWS Lambda function that assumes a role in each AWS account in the organization to authorize inbound rules on security groups based on entries from the DynamoDB table."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 38"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company's application is deployed on Amazon EC2 instances in a single VPC in an AWS Region. The EC2 instances are running in two Availability Zones. The company decides to use a fleet of traffic inspection instances from AWS Marketplace to inspect traffic between the VPC and the internet. The company is performing tests before the company deploys the architecture into production.\n\nThe fleet is located in a shared inspection VPC behind a Gateway Load Balancer (GWLB). To minimize the cost of the solution, the company deployed only one inspection instance in each Availability Zone that the application uses.\n\nDuring tests, a network engineer notices that traffic inspection works as expected when the network is stable. However, during maintenance of the inspection instances, the internet sessions time out for some application instances. The application instances are not able to establish new sessions.\n\nWhich combination of steps will remediate these issues? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy one additional inspection instance in each Availability Zone where the inspection instances are deployed.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy one inspection instance in the Availability Zones that do not have inspection instances deployed.",
        "Deploy inspection instances in an Auto Scaling group. Define a scaling policy that is based on CPU load.",
        "Attach the GWLB to all Availability Zones in the Region."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Enable the cross-zone load balancing attribute for the GWLB.",
        "code": "Question 39"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has developed a new web application on AWS. The application runs on Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) on AWS Fargate behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB) in the us-east-1 Region. The application uses Amazon Route 53 to host the DNS records for the domain. The content that is served from the website is mostly static images and files that are not updated frequently. Most of the traffic to the website from end users will originate from the United States. Some traffic will originate from Canada and Europe.\n\nA network engineer needs to design a solution that will reduce latency for end users at the lowest cost. The solution also must ensure that all traffic is encrypted in transit until the traffic reaches the ALB.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure the ALB to use a secure HTTPS listener. Create an Amazon CloudFront distribution. Set the origin domain name to point to the DNS record that is assigned to the ALB. Configure the CloudFront distribution to use an SSL certificate and redirect HTTP to HTTPS. Create an alias record in Amazon Route 53 for the custom domain name. Configure the alias record to route to the CloudFront distribution.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure the ALB to use an AWS Global Accelerator accelerator in us-east-1. Create a secure HTTPS listener. Create an alias record in Amazon Route 53 for the custom domain name. Configure the alias record to route to the DNS name that is assigned to the accelerator for the ALB.",
        "Configure the ALB to use a secure HTTPS listener. Create an Amazon CloudFront distribution. Set the origin domain name to point to the DNS record that is assigned to the ALConfigure the CloudFront distribution to use an SSL certificate. Set all behaviors to force HTTPS. Create an alias record in Amazon Route 53 for the custom domain name. Configure the alias record to route to the DNS name that is assigned to the ALB.",
        "Configure the ALB to use an AWS Global Accelerator accelerator in us-east-1. Create a secure HTTPS listener. Create a second application stack on Amazon ECS on Fargate in the eu-west-1 Region. Create another secure HTTPS listener. Create an alias record in Amazon Route 53 for the custom domain name. Configure the alias record to use a latency-based routing policy to route to the DNS name that is assigned to the accelerator for the ALBs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 40"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company deploys an internal website behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB) in a VPC. The VPC has a CIDR block of 172.31.0.0/16. The company creates a private hosted zone for the domain example.com for the website in Amazon Route 53. The company establishes an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection between its office network and the VPC.\n\nA network engineer needs to set up a DNS solution so that employees can visit the internal webpage by accessing a private domain URL (https://example.com) from the office network.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet this requirement? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create an alias record that points to the ALB in the Route 53 private hosted zone.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a CNAME record that points to the ALB internal domain in the Route 53 private hosted zone.",
        "Create a Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoint. On the office DNS server, configure a conditional forwarder to forward the DNS queries to the Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoint.",
        "On the office DNS server, configure a conditional forwarder for the private domain to the VPC DNS at 172.31.0.2."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create a Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint. On the office DNS server, configure a conditional forwarder to forward the DNS queries to the Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint.",
        "code": "Question 41"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is deploying AWS Cloud WAN with edge locations in the us-east-1 Region and the ap-southeast-2 Region. Individual AWS Cloud WAN segments are configured for the development environment, the production environment, and the shared services environment at each edge location. Many new VPCs will be deployed for the environments and will be configured as attachments to the AWS Cloud WAN core network.\n\nThe company's network team wants to ensure that VPC attachments are configured for the correct segment. The network team will tag the VPC attachments by using the Environment key with a value of the corresponding environment segment name. The segment for the production environment in us-east-1 must require acceptance for attachment requests. All other attachment requests must not require acceptance.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a rule with a number of 100 that requires acceptance for attachments to the production segment. In the rule, set the condition logic to the \"and\" value. Include conditions that require a tag:Environment value of Production and a Region value of us-east-1. Create a rule with a number of 200 that does not require acceptance to map any tag.Environment values to their respective segments.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a rule with a number of 100 that requires acceptance for attachments to the production segment. In the rule, set the condition logic to the \"or\" value. Include conditions that require a tag:Environment value of Production or a Region value of us-east-1. Create a rule with a number of 200 that does not require acceptance to map any tag:Environment values to their respective segments.",
        "Create a rule with a number of 100 that does not require acceptance to map any tag:Environment values to their respective segments. Create a rule with a number of 200 that requires acceptance for attachments to the production segment. In the rule, set the condition logic to the \"and\" value. Include conditions that require a tag:Environment value of Production and a Region value of us-east-1.",
        "Create a rule with a number of 100 that does not require acceptance to map any tag:Environment values to their respective segments. Create a rule with a number of 200 that requires acceptance for attachments to the production segment. In the rule, set the condition logic to the \"or\" value. Include conditions that require a tag:Environment value of Production or a Region value of us-east-1."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 42"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is migrating applications from a data center to AWS. Many of the applications will need to exchange data with the company's on-premises mainframe.\n\nThe company needs to achieve 4 Gbps transfer speeds to meet peak traffic demands. A network engineer must design a highly available solution that maximizes resiliency. The solution must be able to withstand the loss of circuits or routers.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Order four 10 Gbps AWS Direct Connect connections that are evenly spread over two locations. Terminate one connection from each Direct Connect location to a router at the company location. Terminate the other connection from each Direct Connect location to a different router at the company location.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Order two 10 Gbps AWS Direct Connect connections that are evenly spread over two locations. Terminate the connection from each Direct Connect location to a different router at the company location.",
        "Order four 1 Gbps AWS Direct Connect connections that are evenly spread over two locations. Terminate one connection from each Direct Connect location to a router at the company location. Terminate the other connection from each Direct Connect location to a different router at the company location.",
        "Order two 1 Gbps AWS Direct Connect connections that are evenly spread over two locations. Terminate the connection from each Direct Connect location to a different router at the company location."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 43"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has 10 web server Amazon EC2 instances that run in an Auto Scaling group in a production VPC. The company has 10 other web servers that run in an on-premises data center. The company has a 10 Gbps AWS Direct Connect connection between the on-premises data center and the production VPC.\n\nThe company needs to implement a load balancing solution that receives HTTPS traffic from thousands of external users. The solution must distribute the traffic across the web servers on AWS and the web servers in the on-premises data center. Regardless of the location of the web servers, HTTPS requests must go to the same web server throughout the entire session.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an Application Load Balancer (ALB) in the production VPC. Create a target group Specify ip as the target type. Register the EC2 instances and the on-premises servers with the target group. Enable application-based session affinity (sticky sessions) on the ALB.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a Network Load Balancer (NLB) in the production VPC. Create a target group. Specify ip as the target type. Register the EC2 instances and the on-premises servers with the target group Enable connection draining on the NLB",
        "Create a Network Load Balancer (NLB) in the production VPCreate a target group. Specify instance as the target type. Register the EC2 instances and the on-premises servers with the target group. Enable session affinity (sticky sessions) on the NLB.",
        "Create an Application Load Balancer (ALB) in the production VPC. Create a target group. Specify instance as the target type Register the EC2 instances and the on-premises servers with the target group Enable application-based session affinity (sticky sessions) on the ALB."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 44"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an AWS environment that includes multiple VPCs that are connected by a transit gateway. The company has decided to use AWS Site-to-Site VPN to establish connectivity between its on-premises network and its AWS environment.\n\nThe company does not have a static public IP address for its on-premises network. A network engineer must implement a solution to initiate the VPN connection on the AWS side of the connection for traffic from the AWS environment to the on-premises network.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network engineer take to establish VPN connectivity between the transit gateway and the on-premises network? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Configure the Site-to-Site VPN tunnel options to use Internet Key Exchange version 2 (IKEv2).",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure the Site-to-Site VPN tunnel options to use Internet Key Exchange version 1 (IKEv1).",
        "Use a public certificate authority (CA) from AWS Private Certificate Authority to create a certificate.",
        "Create a customer gateway. Specify the current dynamic IP address of the customer gateway device’s external interface."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Use a private certificate authority (CA) from AWS Private Certificate Authority to create a certificate.||Create a customer gateway without specifying the IP address of the customer gateway device.",
        "code": "Question 45"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has expanded its network to the AWS Cloud by using a hybrid architecture with multiple AWS accounts. The company has set up a shared AWS account for the connection to its on-premises data centers and the company offices. The workloads consist of private web-based services for internal use. These services run in different AWS accounts. Office-based employees consume these services by using a DNS name in an on-premises DNS zone that is named example.internal.\n\nThe process to register a new service that runs on AWS requires a manual and complicated change request to the internal DNS. The process involves many teams.\n\nThe company wants to update the DNS registration process by giving the service creators access that will allow them to register their DNS records. A network engineer must design a solution that will achieve this goal. The solution must maximize cost-effectiveness and must require the least possible number of configuration changes.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network engineer take to meet these requirements? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create an Amazon Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint in the shared account VPC. Create a conditional forwarder for a domain named aws.example.internal on the on-premises DNS servers. Set the forwarding IP addresses to the inbound endpoint's IP addresses that were created.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a record for each service in its local private hosted zone (serviceA.account1.aws.example.internal). Provide this DNS record to the employees who need access.",
        "Create an Amazon Route 53 Resolver rule to forward any queries made to onprem.example.internal to the on-premises DNS servers.",
        "Launch two Amazon EC2 instances in the shared AWS account. Install BIND on each instance. Create a DNS conditional forwarder on each BIND server to forward queries for each subdomain under aws.example.internal to the appropriate private hosted zone in each AWS account. Create a conditional forwarder for a domain named aws.example.internal on the on-premises DNS servers. Set the forwarding IP addresses to the IP addresses of the BIND servers."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create an Amazon Route 53 private hosted zone named aws.example.internal in the shared AWS account to resolve queries for this domain.||Create a private hosted zone in the shared AWS account for each account that runs the service. Configure the private hosted zone to contain aws.example.internal in the domain (account1.aws.example.internal). Associate the private hosted zone with the VPC that runs the service and the shared account VPC.",
        "code": "Question 46"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company's AWS environment has two VPCs. VPC A has a CIDR block of 192.168.0.0/16. VPC B has a CIDR block of 10.0.0.0/16. Each VPC is deployed in a separate AWS Region. The company has remote users who work outside the company's offices. These users need to connect to an application that is running in the VPCs.\n\nTraffic to and from the VPCs over the internet must be encrypted. A network engineer must set up connectivity between the remote users and the VPCs.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network engineer take to meet these requirements with the LEAST management overhead? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Establish a VPC peering connection between VPC A and VPC B.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Establish an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection between VPC A and VPC B.",
        "Create an AWS Client VPN endpoint in VPC A and VPC B Add an authorization rule to grant access to VPC A and VPC B.",
        "Add a route to the AWS Client VPN endpoint's route table to direct traffic to VPC A."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create an AWS Client VPN endpoint in VPC A Add an authorization rule to grant access to VPC A and VPC B.||Add a route to the AWS Client VPN endpoint’s route table to direct traffic to VPC B.",
        "code": "Question 47"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses Amazon Route 53 to register a public domain, example.com, in an AWS account. A central services group manages the account. The company wants to create a subdomain, test.example.com, in another AWS account to offer name services for Amazon EC2 instances that are hosted in the account. The company does not want to migrate the parent domain to the subdomain account.\n\nA network engineer creates a new Route 53 hosted zone for the subdomain in the second account.\n\nWhich combination of steps must the network engineer take to complete the task? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Add records for the hosts of the new subdomain to the new Route 53 hosted zone.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Update the DNS service for the subdomain by adding name server (NS) records for the parent domain.",
        "Create an alias record from the parent domain that points to the hosted zone for the subdomain in the second account.",
        "Add a start of authority (SOA) record in the parent domain for the subdomain."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Update the DNS service for the parent domain by adding name server (NS) records for the subdomain.",
        "code": "Question 48"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An IoT company collects data from thousands of sensors that are deployed in the Unites States and South Asia. The sensors use a proprietary communication protocol that is built on UDP to send the data to a fleet of Amazon EC2 instances. The instances are in an Auto Scaling group and run behind a Network Load Balancer (NLB). The instances, Auto Scaling group, and NLB are deployed in the us-west-2 Region.\n\nOccasionally, the data from the sensors in South Asia gets lost in transit over the internet and does not reach the EC2 instances.\n\nWhich solutions will resolve this issue? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Use AWS Global Accelerator with the existing NLB.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an Amazon CloudFront distribution. Specify the existing NLB as the origin.",
        "Create a second deployment of the EC2 instances and the NLB in the ap-south-1 Region. Use an Amazon Route 53 failover routing policy to resolve to an alternate Region in case packets are dropped.",
        "Turn on enhanced networking on the EC2 instances by using the most recent Elastic Network Adapter (ENA) drivers."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create a second deployment of the EC2 instances and the NLB in the ap-south-1 Region. Use an Amazon Route 53 latency routing policy to resolve to the Region that provides the least latency.",
        "code": "Question 49"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an application that runs on a fleet of Amazon EC2 instances. A new company regulation mandates that all network traffic to and from the EC2 instances must be sent to a centralized third-party EC2 appliance for content inspection.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a third-party EC2 appliance in an Auto Scaling group fronted by a Network Load Balancer (NLB). Configure a mirror session. Specify the NLB as the mirror target. Specify a mirror filter to capture inbound and outbound traffic. For the source of the mirror session, specify the EC2 elastic network interfaces for all the instances that host the application.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure VPC flow logs on each EC2 network interface. Publish the flow logs to an Amazon S3 bucket. Create a third-party EC2 appliance to acquire flow logs from the S3 bucket. Log in to the appliance to monitor network content.",
        "Configure a mirror session. Specify an Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose delivery stream as the mirror target. Specify a mirror filter to capture inbound and outbound traffic. For the source of the mirror session, specify the EC2 elastic network interfaces for all the instances that host the application. Create a third-party EC2 appliance. Send all traffic to the appliance through the Kinesis Data Firehose delivery stream for content inspection.",
        "Configure VPC flow logs on each EC2 network interface. Send the logs to Amazon CloudWatch. Create a third-party EC2 appliance. Configure a CloudWatch filter to send the flow logs to Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose to load the logs into the appliance."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 50"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has two AWS Direct Connect links. One Direct Connect link terminates in the us-east-1 Region, and the other Direct Connect link terminates in the af-south-1 Region. The company is using BGP to exchange routes with AWS.\n\nHow should a network engineer configure BGP to ensure that af-south-1 is used as a secondary link to AWS?",
      "correct_answer": "• On the Direct Connect link to us-east-1, configure BGP peering to use community tag 7224:7300 • On the Direct Connect link to af-south-1, configure BGP peering to use community tag 7224:7100 • On the Direct Connect BGP peer to us-east-1, set the local preference value to 200 • On the Direct Connect BGP peer to af-south-1, set the local preference value to 50",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "• On the Direct Connect link to us-east-1, configure BGP peering to use community tag 7224:7100 • On the Direct Connect link to af-south-1, configure BGP peering to use community tag 7224:7300 • On the Direct Connect BGP peer to us-east-1, set the local preference value to 200 • On the Direct Connect BGP peer to af-south-1, set the local preference value to 50",
        "• On the Direct Connect link to us-east-1, configure BGP peering to use community tag 7224:7100 • On the Direct Connect link to af-south-1, configure BGP peering to use community tag 7224:7300 • On the Direct Connect BGP peer to us-east-1, set the local preference value to 50 • On the Direct Connect BGP peer to af-south-1, set the local preference value to 200",
        "• On the Direct Connect link to us-east-1, configure BGP peering to use community tag 7224:7300 • On the Direct Connect link to af-south-1, configure BGP peering to use community tag 7224:7100 • On the Direct Connect BGP peer to us-east-1, set the local preference value to 50 • On the Direct Connect BGP peer to af-south-1, set the local preference value to 200"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 51"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A team of infrastructure engineers wants to automate the deployment of Application Load Balancer (ALB) components by using the AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK). The CDK application must deploy an infrastructure stack that is reusable and consistent across multiple environments, AWS Regions, and AWS accounts.\n\nThe lead network architect on the project has already bootstrapped the target accounts. The lead network architect also has deployed core network components such as VPCs and Amazon Route 53 private hosted zones across the multiple environments and Regions. The infrastructure engineers must design the ALB components in the CDK application to use the existing core network components.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet this requirement with the LEAST manual effort between environment deployments? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Design the CDK application to read environment variables that contain account and Region details at runtime. Use these variables as properties of the CDK stack. Use context methods in the CDK stack to retrieve variable values.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Design the CDK application to read AWS CloudFormation parameters for the values that vary across environments and Regions. Reference these variables in the CDK stack for resources that require the variables.",
        "Write a script that automates the deployment of the CDK application across multiple environments and Regions. Distribute the script to engineers who are working on the project.",
        "Use the CDK toolkit locally to deploy stacks to each environment and Region. Use the --context flag to pass in variables that the CDK application can reference at runtime."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create a dedicated account for shared application services in the multi-account environment. Deploy a CDK pipeline to the dedicated account. Create stages in the pipeline that deploy the CDK application across different environments and Regions.",
        "code": "Question 52"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has critical VPC workloads that connect to an on-premises data center through two redundant active-passive AWS Direct Connect connections. However, a recent outage on one Direct Connect connection revealed that it takes more than a minute for traffic to fail over to the secondary Direct Connect connection. The company wants to reduce the failover time from minutes to seconds.\n\nWhich solution will provide the LARGEST reduction in the BGP failover time?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure Bidirectional Forwarding Detection (BFD) on the Direct Connect connections on the on-premises router.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reduce the BGP hold-down timer that is configured on the BGP sessions on the Direct Connect connection VIFs.",
        "Configure an Amazon CloudWatch alarm for the Direct Connect connection state to invoke an AWS Lambda function to fail over the traffic.",
        "Configure Bidirectional Forwarding Detection (BFD) on the Direct Connect connections on the AWS side."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 53"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A European car manufacturer wants to migrate its customer-facing services and its analytics platform from two on-premises data centers to the AWS Cloud. The company has a 50-mile (80.4 km) separation between its on-premises data centers and must maintain that separation between its two locations in the cloud. The company also needs failover capabilities between the two locations in the cloud.\n\nThe company's infrastructure team creates several accounts to separate workloads and responsibilities. The company provisions resources in the eu-west-3 Region and in the eu-central-1 Region. The company selects an AWS Direct Connect Partner in each Region and requests two resilient 1 Gbps fiber connections from each provider.\n\nThe company's network engineer must establish a connection between all VPCs in the accounts and between the on-premises network and the AWS Cloud. The solution must provide access to all services in both Regions in case of network issues.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a Direct Connect gateway. Create a transit gateway in each Region. Attach the transit gateways to the Direct Connect gateway. Create a transit VIF on each of the Direct Connect connections. Attach the transit VIFs to the Direct Connect gateway. Peer the transit gateways. Attach the transit gateways in each Region to the VPCs in the same Region.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a Direct Connect gateway. Create a private VIF on each of the Direct Connect connections. Attach the private VIFs to the Direct Connect gateway. Use equal-cost multi-path (ECMP) routing to aggregate the four connections across the two Regions. Attach the Direct Connect gateway directly to each VPC's virtual private gateway.",
        "Create a Direct Connect gateway. Create a transit gateway. Attach the transit gateway to the Direct Connect gateway. Create a transit VIF on each of the Direct Connect connections. Attach the transit VIFs to the Direct Connect gateway. Use a link aggregation group (LAG) to aggregate the four connections across the two Regions. Attach the transit gateway directly to each VPC.",
        "Create a Direct Connect gateway. Create a private VIF on each of the Direct Connect connections. Attach the private VIFs to the Direct Connect gateway. Use a link aggregation group (LAG) to aggregate the four connections across the two Regions. Create a transit gateway. Attach the transit gateway to the Direct Connect gateway. Attach the transit gateway directly to each VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 54"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to analyze TCP traffic to the internet. The traffic originates from Amazon EC2 instances in the company's VPC. The EC2 instances initiate connections through a NAT gateway. The required information includes source and destination IP addresses, ports, and the first 8 bytes of payload of TCP segments. The company needs to collect, store, and analyze all the required data points.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Set up the EC2 instances as VPC traffic mirror sources. Deploy software on the traffic mirror target to forward the data to Amazon CloudWatch Logs. Analyze the data by using CloudWatch Logs Insights.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set up the NAT gateway as a VPC traffic mirror source. Deploy software on the traffic mirror target to forward the data to an Amazon OpenSearch Service cluster. Analyze the data by using OpenSearch Dashboards.",
        "Turn on VPC Flow Logs on the EC2 instances. Specify the default format and a log destination of Amazon CloudWatch Logs. Analyze the flow log data by using CloudWatch Logs Insights.",
        "Turn on VPC Flow Logs on the EC2 instances. Specify a custom format and a log destination of Amazon S3. Analyze the flow log data by using Amazon Athena."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 55"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has three VPCs in a single AWS Region. Each VPC contains 15 Amazon EC2 instances, and no connectivity exists between the VPCs.\n\nThe company is deploying a new application across all three VPCs. The application requires high bandwidth between the nodes. A network engineer must implement connectivity between the VPCs.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the HIGHEST throughput?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure VPC peering between the three VPCs. Configure static routing to route traffic between the three VPCs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure a transit gateway. Attach each VPC to the transit gateway. Configure static routing in each VPC to route traffic to the transit gateway.",
        "Configure a transit VPConfigure a VPN gateway in each VPCreate an AWS Site-to-Site VPN tunnel from each VPC to the transit VPUse BGP routing to route traffic between the VPCs and the transit VPC.",
        "Configure AWS Site-to-Site VPN connections between each VPC. Enable route propagation for each Site-to-Site VPN connection to route traffic between the VPCs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 56"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has multiple AWS accounts. Each account contains one or more VPCs. A new security guideline requires the inspection of all traffic between VPCs.\n\nThe company has deployed a transit gateway that provides connectivity between all VPCs. The company also has deployed a shared services VPC with Amazon EC2 instances that include IDS services for stateful inspection. The EC2 instances are deployed across three Availability Zones. The company has set up VPC associations and routing on the transit gateway. The company has migrated a few test VPCs to the new solution for traffic inspection.\n\nSoon after the configuration of routing, the company receives reports of intermittent connections for traffic that crosses Availability Zones.\n\nWhat should a network engineer do to resolve this issue?",
      "correct_answer": "Modify the transit gateway VPC attachment on the shared services VPC by enabling appliance mode support.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Modify the transit gateway VPC attachment on the shared services VPC by enabling cross-Availability Zone load balancing.",
        "Modify the transit gateway by selecting VPN equal-cost multi-path (ECMP) routing support.",
        "Modify the transit gateway by selecting multicast support."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 57"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer needs to deploy an AWS Network Firewall firewall into an existing AWS environment. The environment consists of the following:\n\n• A transit gateway with all VPCs attached to it\n\n• Several hundred application VPCs\n\n• A centralized egress internet VPC with a NAT gateway and an internet gateway\n\n• A centralized ingress internet VPC that hosts public Application Load Balancers\n\n• On-premises connectivity through an AWS Direct Connect gateway attachment\n\nThe application VPCs have workloads deployed across multiple Availability Zones in private subnets with the VPC route table s default route (0.0.0.0/0) pointing to the transit gateway. The Network Firewall firewall needs to inspect east-west (VPC-to-VPC) traffic and north-south (internet-bound and on-premises network) traffic by using Suricata compatible rules.\n\nThe network engineer must deploy the firewall by using a solution that requires the least possible architectural changes to the existing production environment.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network engineer take to meet these requirements? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy Network Firewall in all Availability Zones in a centralized inspection VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy Network Firewall in all Availability Zones in each application VPC.",
        "Update the EXTERNAL_NET rule group variable to include all CIDR ranges of the VPCs and on-premises networks.",
        "Configure a single transit gateway route table. Associate all application VPCs and the centralized inspection VPC with this route table."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Update the HOME_NET rule group variable to include all CIDR ranges of the VPCs and on-premises networks.||Configure two transit gateway route tables. Associate all application VPCs with one transit gateway route table. Associate the centralized inspection VPC with the other transit gateway route table.",
        "code": "Question 58"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using a shared services VPC with two domain controllers. The domain controllers are deployed in the company's private subnets. The company is deploying a new application into a new VPC in the account. The application will be deployed onto an Amazon EC2 for Windows Server instance in the new VPC. The instance must join the existing Windows domain that is supported by the domain controllers in the shared services VPC.\n\nA transit gateway is attached to both the shared services VPC and the new VPC. The company has updated the route tables for the transit gateway, the shared services VPC, and the new VPC. The security groups for the domain controllers and the instance are updated and allow traffic only on the ports that are necessary for domain operations. The instance is unable to join the domain that is hosted on the domain controllers.\n\nWhich combination of actions will help identify the cause of this issue with the LEAST operational overhead? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Use AWS Network Manager to perform a route analysis for the transit gateway network. Specify the existing EC2 instance as the source. Specify the first domain controller as the destination. Repeat the route analysis for the second domain controller.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use port mirroring with the existing EC2 instance as the source and another EC2 instance as the target to obtain packet captures of the connection attempts.",
        "Issue a ping command from one of the domain controllers to the existing EC2 instance.",
        "Ensure that route propagation is turned off on the shared services VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Review the VPC flow logs on the shared services VPC and the new VPC.",
        "code": "Question 59"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an order processing system that needs to keep credit card numbers encrypted. The company's customer-facing application runs as an Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) service behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB) in the us-west-2 Region. An Amazon CloudFront distribution is configured with the ALB as the origin. The company uses a third-party trusted certificate authority to provision its certificates.\n\nThe company is using HTTPS for encryption in transit. The company needs additional field-level encryption to keep sensitive data encrypted during processing so that only certain application components can decrypt the sensitive data.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Import the third-party certificate for the ALB into AWS Certificate Manager (ACM) in us-west-2. Associate the certificate with the ALUpload the certificate for the CloudFront distribution into ACM in the us-east-1 Region.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Import the third-party certificate for the ALB. Associate the certificate with the ALB. Upload the certificate for the CloudFront distribution into AWS Certificate Manager (ACM) in us-west-2.",
        "Upload the private key that handles the encryption of the sensitive data to the CloudFront distribution. Create a field-level encryption profile and specify the fields that contain sensitive information. Create a field-level encryption configuration, and choose the newly created profile. Link the configuration to the appropriate cache behavior that is associated with sensitive POST requests.",
        "Upload the public key that handles the encryption of the sensitive data to the CloudFront distribution. Create a field-level encryption configuration, and specify the fields that contain sensitive information. Create a field-level encryption profile, and choose the newly created configuration. Link the profile to the appropriate cache behavior that is associated with sensitive GET requests."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Upload the public key that handles the encryption of the sensitive data to the CloudFront distribution. Create a field-level encryption profile and specify the fields that contain sensitive information. Create a field-level encryption configuration, and choose the newly created profile. Link the configuration to the appropriate cache behavior that is associated with sensitive POST requests.",
        "code": "Question 60"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has deployed a multi-VPC environment in the AWS Cloud. The company uses a transit gateway to connect all the VPCs together. In the past, the company has experienced a loss of connectivity between applications after changes to security groups, network ACLs, and route tables in a VPC. When these changes occur, the company wants to automatically verify that connectivity still exists between different resources in a single VPC.",
      "correct_answer": "Create a list of paths between different resources to check in VPC Reachability Analyzer. Create an Amazon EventBridge rule to monitor when a change is made and logged in AWS. CloudTrail. Configure the rule to invoke an AWS Lambda function to test the different paths in Reachability Analyzer.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a list of paths between different resources to check in VPC Reachability Analyzer. Create an Amazon EventBridge rule to monitor when a change is made and logged in Amazon CloudWatch. Configure the rule to invoke an AWS Lambda function to test the different paths in Reachability Analyzer.",
        "Create a list of paths to check in AWS Transit Gateway Network Manager Route Analyzer. Create an Amazon EventBridge rule to monitor when a change is made and logged in Amazon CloudWatch. Configure the rule to invoke an AWS Lambda function to test the diffident paths in Route Analyzer.",
        "Create a list of paths to check in AWS Transit Gateway Network Manager Route Analyzer. Create an Amazon EventBridge rule to monitor when a change is made and logged in AWS CloudTrail. Configure the rule to invoke an AWS Lambda function to test the different paths in Route Analyzer."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 61"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company hosts a web application that runs on a fleet of Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). The instances are in an Auto Scaling group. The company uses an Amazon CloudFront distribution with the ALB as an origin.\n\nThe application recently experienced an attack. In response, the company associated an AWS WAF web ACL with the CloudFront distribution. The company needs to use Amazon Athena to analyze application attacks that AWS WAF detects.\n\nWhich solution will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure the AWS WAF web ACL to deliver logs to an Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose delivery stream. Configure the stream to deliver the data to an Amazon S3 bucket for log analysis.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure the ALB and the EC2 instance subnets to produce VPC flow logs. Configure the VPC flow logs to deliver logs to an Amazon S3 bucket for log analysis.",
        "Create a trail in AWS CloudTrail to capture data events. Configure the trail to deliver logs to an Amazon S3 bucket for log analysis.",
        "Turn on access logging for the ALB. Configure the access logs to deliver the logs to an Amazon S3 bucket for log analysis."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 62"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A real estate company is using Amazon Workspaces to provide corporate managed desktop service to its real estate agents around the world. These Workspaces are deployed in seven VPCs. Each VPC is in a different AWS Region.\n\nAccording to a new requirement, the company’s cloud-hosted security information and events management (SIEM) system needs to analyze DNS queries generated by the Workspaces to identify the target domains that are connected to the Workspaces. The SIEM system supports poll and push methods for data and log collection.\n\nWhich solution should a network engineer implement to meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure Amazon Route 53 query logging. Set the destination as an Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose delivery stream that is configured to push data to the SIEM system.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create VPC flow logs in each VPC that is connected to the Workspaces instances. Publish the log data to a central Amazon S3 bucket. Configure the SIEM system to poll the S3 bucket periodically.",
        "Configure an Amazon CloudWatch agent to log all DNS requests in Amazon CloudWatch Logs. Configure a subscription filter in CloudWatch Logs. Push the logs to the SIEM system by using Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose.",
        "Configure VPC Traffic Mirroring to copy network traffic from each Workspace and to send the traffic to the SIEM system probes for analysis."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 63"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer needs to design the architecture for a high performance computing (HPC) workload. Amazon EC2 instances will require 10 Gbps flows and an aggregate throughput of up to 100 Gbps across many instances with low-latency communication.\n\nWhich architecture solution will optimize this workload?",
      "correct_answer": "Place nodes in a single subnet of a VPC. Configure a cluster placement group. Ensure that the latest Elastic Fabric Adapter (EFA) drivers are installed on the EC2 instances with a supported operating system.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Place nodes in multiple subnets in a single VPC. Configure a spread placement group. Ensure that the EC2 instances support Elastic Network Adapters (ENAs) and that the drivers are updated on each instance operating system.",
        "Place nodes in multiple VPCs Use AWS Transit Gateway to route traffic between the VPCs. Ensure that the latest Elastic Fabric Adapter (EFA) drivers are installed on the EC2 instances with a supported operating system.",
        "Place nodes in multiple subnets in multiple Availability Zones. Configure a cluster placement group. Ensure that the EC2 instances support Elastic Network Adapters (ENAs) and that the drivers are updated on each instance operating system."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 64"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses multiple AWS accounts and VPCs in a single AWS Region. The company must log all network traffic for Amazon EC2 instances and Amazon RDS databases. The company will use the log information to monitor and identify traffic flows in the event of a security incident. The information must be retained for 12 months but will be accessed infrequently after the first 90 days. The company must be able to view metadata that includes the vpc-id, subnet-id: and tcp-flags fields.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements at the LOWEST cost?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure VPC flow logs with additional custom format fields Store the logs in Amazon S3.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure VPC flow logs with the default fields Store the logs in Amazon CloudWatch Logs.",
        "Configure Traffic Mirroring on all AWS resources to point to a Network Load Balancer that will send the mirrored traffic to monitoring instances.",
        "Configure VPC flow logs with additional custom format fields Store the logs in Amazon CloudWatch Logs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 65"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer is evaluating a network setup for a global retail company. The company has an AWS Direct Connect connection between its on-premises data center and the AWS Cloud. The company has AWS resources in the eu-west-2 Region. These resources consist of multiple VPCs that are attached to a transit gateway.\n\nThe company recently provisioned a few AWS resources in the eu-central-1. Region in a single VPC close to its users in this area. The network engineer must connect the resources in eu-central-1 with the on-premises data center and the resources in eu-west-2. The solution must minimize changes to the Direct Connect connection.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new transit gateway in eu-central-1. Create a peering attachment request to the transit gateway in eu-west-2. Add a static route in the transit gateway route table in eu-central-1 to point to the transit gateway peering attachment. Accept the peering request. Add a static route in the transit gateway route table in eu-west-2 to point to the new transit gateway peering attachment.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new virtual private gateway. Attach the new virtual private gateway to the VPC in eu-central-1. Use a transit VIF to connect the VPC and the Direct Connect router.",
        "Create a new transit gateway in eu-central-1. Use an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection to peer both transit gateways. Add a static route in the transit gateway route table in eu-central-1 to point to the transit gateway VPN attachment. Add a static route in the transit gateway route table in eu-west-2 to point to the new transit gateway peering attachment.",
        "Create a new virtual private gateway. Attach the new virtual private gateway to the VPC in eu-central-1. Use a public VIF to connect the VPC and the Direct Connect router."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 66"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a 2 Gbps AWS Direct Connect hosted connection from the company’s office to a VPC in the ap-southeast-2 Region. A network engineer adds a 5 Gbps Direct Connect hosted connection from a different Direct Connect location in the same Region. The hosted connections are connected to different routers from the office with an iBGP session running in between the routers.\n\nThe network engineer wants to ensure that the VPC uses the 5 Gbps hosted connection to route traffic to the office. Failover to the 2 Gbps hosted connection must occur when the 5 Gbps hosted connection is down.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure an outbound BGP policy from the router that is connected to the 2 Gbps connection. Advertise routes with a longer AS_PATH attribute to AWS.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Advertise a longer prefix route from the router that is connected to the 2 Gbps connection.",
        "Advertise a less specific route from the router that is connected to the 5 Gbps connection.",
        "Configure an outbound BGP policy from the router that is connected to the 5 Gbps connection. Advertise routes with a longer AS_PATH attribute to AWS."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 67"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using a NAT gateway to allow internet connectivity for private subnets in a VPC in the us-west-2 Region. After a security audit, the company needs to remove the NAT gateway.\n\nIn the private subnets, the company has resources that use the unified Amazon CloudWatch agent. A network engineer must create a solution to ensure that the unified CloudWatch agent continues to work after the removal of the NAT gateway.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network engineer take to meet these requirements? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Validate that private DNS is enabled on the VPC by setting the enableDnsHostnames VPC attribute and the enableDnsSupport VPC attribute to true.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new security group with an entry to allow outbound traffic that uses the TCP protocol on port 443 to destination 0.0.0.0/0",
        "Create the following interface VPC endpoint in the VPC: com.amazonaws.us-west-2.cloudwatch. Associate the new security group with the endpoint network interfaces.",
        "Associate the VPC endpoint or endpoints with route tables that the private subnets use."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create a new security group with entries to allow inbound traffic that uses the TCP protocol on port 443 from the IP prefixes of the private subnets.||Create the following interface VPC endpoints in the VPC: com.amazonaws.us-west-2.logs and com.amazonaws.us-west-2.monitoring. Associate the new security group with the endpoint network interfaces.",
        "code": "Question 68"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An ecommerce company needs to implement additional security controls on all its domain names that are hosted in Amazon Route 53. The company's new policy requires data authentication and data integrity verification for all queries to the company’s domain names. The current Route 53 architecture has four public hosted zones.\n\nA network engineer needs to implement DNS Security Extensions (DNSSEC) signing and validation on the hosted zones. The solution must include an alert capability.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet these requirements? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Enable DNSSEC signing for Route 53 Request that Route 53 create a key-signing key (KSK) based on a customer managed key in AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS).",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Enable DNSSEC signing for Route 53 Request that Route 53 create a zone-signing key (ZSK) based on a customer managed key in AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS).",
        "Create a chain of trust for the hosted zones by adding a Delegation Signer (DS) record for each subdomain",
        "Set up an AWS CloudTrail alarm that provides an alert whenever a DNSSECInternalFailure error or DNSSECKeySigningKeysNeedingAction error is detected."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create a chain of trust for the hosted zones by adding a Delegation Signer (DS) record to the parent zone.||Set up an Amazon CloudWatch alarm that provides an alert whenever a DNSSECInternalFailure error or DNSSECKeySigningKeysNeedingAction error is detected.",
        "code": "Question 69"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A financial company that is located in the us-east-1 Region needs to establish secure connectivity to AWS. The company has two on-premises data centers, each located within the same Region. The company's network team needs to establish hybrid connectivity to its AWS environment with reliable and consistent connectivity.\n\nThe connection must provide access to the company's private resources inside its AWS environment. The resources are located in the us-east-1 and us-west-2 Regions. The connection must allow resources from the corporate networks to send large amounts of data to Amazon S3 over the same connection. To meet compliance requirements, the connection must be highly available and must provide encryption for all packets that are sent between the on-premises location and any services on AWS.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network team take to meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Set up an AWS Direct Connect connection to each of the company's data centers.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set up a private VIF to send data to Amazon S3. Use an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection over the private VIF to encrypt data in transit to the VPCs in us-east-1 and us-west-2.",
        "Set up an AWS Direct Connect connection from one of the company's data centers to us-east-1 and us-west-2.",
        "Set up a transit VIF for an AWS Direct Connect gateway to send data to Amazon S3. Create a transit gateway. Associate the transit gateway with the Direct Connect gateway to provide secure communications from the company’s data centers to the VPCs in us-east-1 and us-west-2."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Set up a public VIF to send data to Amazon S3. Use an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection over the public VIF to encrypt data in transit to the VPCs in us-east-1 and us-west-2.",
        "code": "Question 70"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A global company is designing a hybrid architecture to privately access AWS resources in the us-west-2 Region. The company's existing architecture includes a VPC that uses RFC 1918 IP address space. The VPC is connected to an on-premises data center over AWS Direct Connect Amazon Route 53 provides name resolution within the VPC. Locally managed DNS servers in the data center provide DNS services to the on-premises hosts.\n\nThe company has applications in the data center that need to download objects from an Amazon S3 bucket in us-west-2.\n\nWhich solution can the company use to access Amazon S3 without using the public IP address space?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an S3 interface endpoint in the VPC. Configure a Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint in the VPC. Set up the data center DNS servers to forward DNS queries for the S3 domain from on premises to the inbound endpoint.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an S3 interface endpoint in the VPC. Update the on-premises application configuration to use the Regional VPC endpoint DNS hostname that is mapped to the S3 interface endpoint.",
        "Create an S3 gateway endpoint in the VPUpdate the on-premises application configuration to use the hostname that is mapped to the S3 gateway endpoint.",
        "Create an S3 gateway endpoint in the VPC. Configure a Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint in the VPC. Set up the data center DNS servers to forward DNS queries for the S3 domain from on premises to the inbound endpoint."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 71"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is migrating critical applications to AWS. The company has multiple accounts and VPCs that are connected by a transit gateway.\n\nA network engineer must design a solution that performs deep packet inspection for any traffic that leaves a VPC network boundary. All inspected traffic and the actions that are taken on the traffic must be logged in a central log account.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST administrative overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a central network VPC that includes an attachment to the transit gateway. Update the VPC and transit gateway route tables to support the new attachment. Deploy an AWS Gateway Load Balancer that is backed by third-party, next-generation firewall appliances to the central network VPC. Create a policy that contains the rules for deep packet inspection. Attach the policy to the firewall appliances. Create an Amazon S3 bucket in the central log account. Configure the firewall appliances to capture and save the network flow logs to the S3 bucket.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a central network VPC that includes an attachment to the transit gateway. Update the VPC and transit gateway route tables to support the new attachment. Deploy an AWS Application Load Balancer that is backed by third-party, next-generation firewall appliances to the central network VPC. Create a policy that contains the rules for deep packet inspection. Attach the policy to the firewall appliances. Create a syslog server in the central log account. Configure the firewall appliances to capture and save the network flow logs to the syslog server.",
        "Deploy network ACLs and security groups to each VPAttach the security groups to active network interfaces. Associate the network ACLs with VPC subnets. Create rules for the network ACLs and security groups to allow only the required traffic flows between subnets and network interfaces. Create an Amazon S3 bucket in the central log account. Configure a VPC flow log that captures and saves all traffic flows to the S3 bucket.",
        "Create a central log VPC and an attachment to the transit gateway. Update the VPC and transit gateway route tables to support the new attachment. Deploy an AWS Network Load Balancer (NLB) that is backed by third-party, next-generation intrusion detection system (IDS) security appliances to the central VPC. Activate rules on the security appliances to monitor for intrusion signatures. For each network interface, create a VPC Traffic Mirroring session that sends the traffic to the central VPC's NLB."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 72"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an on-premises data center in the United States. The data center is connected to AWS by an AWS Direct Connect connection. The data center has a private VIF that is connected to a Direct Connect gateway.\n\nRecently, the company opened a new data center in Europe and established a new Direct Connect connection between the Europe data center and AWS. A new private VIF connects to the existing Direct Connect gateway.\n\nThe company wants to use Direct Connect SiteLink to set up a private network between the data center in the United States and the data center in Europe.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements in the MOST operationally efficient manner?",
      "correct_answer": "Use the existing VIF from each data center. Enable SiteLink on the existing private VIFs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new public VIF from each data center. Enable SiteLink on the new public VIFs.",
        "Create a new transit VIF from each data center. Enable SiteLink on the new transit VIFs.",
        "Create a new AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection between the data centers. Configure the new connection to use SiteLink."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 73"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a new AWS Direct Connect connection between its on-premises data center and the AWS Cloud. The company has created a new private VIF on this connection. However, the VIF status is DOWN.\n\nA network engineer verifies that the physical connection status is UP and RUNNING based on information from the AWS Management Console. The network engineer checks the customer Direct Connect router and can see the ARP entry for the VLAN interface created for the private VIF at AWS.\n\nWhat could be causing the private VIF to have a DOWN status?",
      "correct_answer": "TCP port 179 is blocked on the customer Direct Connect router.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "ICMP is blocked on the customer Direct Connect router.",
        "The IEEE 802.1Q VLAN identifier is misconfigured on the customer Direct Connect router.",
        "The company has configured IEEE 802.1ad instead of 802.1Q on the customer Direct Connect router."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 74"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "AnyCompany has acquired Example Corp. AnyCompany's infrastructure is all on premises, and Example Corp's infrastructure is completely in the AWS Cloud. The companies are using AWS Direct Connect with AWS Transit Gateway to establish connectivity between each other.\n\nExample Corp has deployed a new application across two Availability Zones in a VPC with no internet gateway. The CIDR range for the VPC is 10.0.0.0/16. Example Corp needs to access an application that is deployed on premises by AnyCompany. Because of compliance requirements, Example Corp must access the application through a limited contiguous block of approved IP addresses (10.1.0.0/24).\n\nA network engineer needs to implement a highly available solution to achieve this goal. The network engineer starts by updating the VPC to add a new CIDR range of 10.1.0.0/24.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do next to meet the requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "In each Availability Zone in the VPC, create a subnet that uses part of the allowed IP address range. Create a private NAT gateway in each of the new subnets. Update the route tables that are associated with other subnets to route application traffic to the private NAT gateway in the corresponding Availability Zone. Add a route to the route table that is associated with the subnets of the private NAT gateways to send traffic destined for the application to the transit gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "In each Availability Zone in the VPC, create a subnet that uses part of the allowed IP address range. Create a public NAT gateway in each of the new subnets. Update the route tables that are associated with other subnets to route application traffic to the public NAT gateway in the corresponding Availability Zone. Add a route to the route table that is associated with the subnets of the public NAT gateways to send traffic destined for the application to the transit gateway.",
        "In the VPC, create a subnet that uses the allowed IP address range. Create a private NAT gateway in the new subnet. Update the route tables that are associated with other subnets to route application traffic to the private NAT gateway. Add a route to the route table that is associated with the subnet of the private NAT gateway to send traffic destined for the application to the transit gateway.",
        "In the VPC, create a subnet that uses the allowed IP address range. Create a public NAT gateway in the new subnet. Update the route tables that are associated with other subnets to route application traffic to the public NAT gateway. Add a route to the route table that is associated with the subnet of the public NAT gateway to send traffic destined for the application to the transit gateway."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 75"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company recently experienced an IP address exhaustion event in its VPCs. The event affected service capacity. The VPCs hold two or more subnets in different Availability Zones.\n\nA network engineer needs to develop a solution that monitors IP address usage across resources in the VPCs. The company needs to receive notification about possible issues so that the company can act before an incident happens.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Set up Amazon VPC IP Address Manager (IPAM) with a new top-level pool. In the top-level pool, create a pool for each VPC. In each VPC pool, create a pool for each subnet in that VPC. Turn on the auto-import option for the VPC pools and the subnet pools. Configure an Amazon CloudWatch alarm to send an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) notification if the availability limit threshold is reached.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set up a log group in Amazon CloudWatch Logs for each subnet. Create an AWS Lambda function that reads each subnet's IP address usage and publishes metrics to the log group. Configure an Amazon CloudWatch alarm to send an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) notification if the availability limit threshold is reached.",
        "Set up a custom Amazon CloudWatch metric for IP address usage for each subnet. Create an AWS Lambda function that reads each subnet's IP address usage and publishes a CloudWatch metric dimension. Schedule the Lambda function to run every 5 minutes. Configure a CloudWatch alarm to send an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) notification if the availability limit threshold is reached.",
        "Set up Amazon VPC IP Address Manager (IPAM) with a new top-level pool. In the top-level pool, create a pool for each VPC. In each VPC pool, create a pool for each subnet in that VPC. Turn on the auto-import option for the VPC pools and the subnet pools. Configure an Amazon EventBridge rule that monitors each pool availability limit threshold and sends an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) notification if the limit threshold is reached."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 76"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a hybrid IT setup that includes services that run in an on-premises data center and in the AWS Cloud. The company is using AWS Direct Connect to connect its data center to AWS. The company is using one AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection as backup and requires a backup connectivity option to always be present. The company is transitioning to IPv6 by implementing dual-stack architectures.\n\nWhich combination of steps will transition the data center's connectivity to AWS in the LEAST amount of time? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new Site-to-Site VPN tunnel for the IPv6 traffic.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new dual-stack Site-to-Site VPN connection between the data center and AWS. Provision routing. Delete the original Site-to-Site VPN connection.",
        "Associate a new dual-stack public VIF with the Direct Connect connection. Migrate the Direct Connect traffic to the new VIF.",
        "Send IPv6 traffic between the data center and AWS in a tunnel inside the existing IPv4 tunnels."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Add a new IPv6 peer in the existing VIF. Use the IPv6 address provided by Amazon on the peer router.",
        "code": "Question 77"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is developing a new application that is deployed in multiple VPCs across multiple AWS Regions. The VPCs are connected through AWS Transit Gateway. The VPCs contain private subnets and public subnets.\n\nAll outbound internet traffic in the private subnets must be audited and logged. The company's network engineer plans to use AWS Network Firewall and must ensure that all traffic through Network Firewall is completely logged for auditing and alerting.\n\nHow should the network engineer configure Network Firewall logging to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure Network Firewall logging in Network Firewall to capture all alerts and flow logs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure Network Firewall logging in Amazon CloudWatch to capture all alerts. Send the logs to a log group in Amazon CloudWatch Logs.",
        "Configure Network Firewall logging by configuring VPC Flow Logs for the firewall endpoint. Send the logs to a log group in Amazon CloudWatch Logs.",
        "Configure Network Firewall logging by configuring AWS CloudTrail to capture data events."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 78"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An international company provides early warning about tsunamis. The company plans to use IoT devices to monitor sea waves around the world. The data that is collected by the IoT devices must reach the company’s infrastructure on AWS as quickly as possible. The company is using three operation centers around the world. Each operation center is connected to AWS through Its own AWS Direct Connect connection. Each operation center is connected to the internet through at least two upstream internet service providers.\n\nThe company has its own provider-independent (PI) address space. The IoT devices use TCP protocols for reliable transmission of the data they collect. The IoT devices have both landline and mobile internet connectivity. The infrastructure and the solution will be deployed in multiple AWS Regions. The company will use Amazon Route 53 for DNS services.\n\nA network engineer needs to design connectivity between the IoT devices and the services that run in the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the HIGHEST availability?",
      "correct_answer": "Set up an accelerator in AWS Global Accelerator. Configure Regional endpoint groups and health checks.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set up an Amazon CloudFront distribution with origin failover. Create an origin group for each Region where the solution is deployed.",
        "Set up Route 53 latency-based routing. Add latency alias records. For the latency alias records, set the value of Evaluate Target Health to Yes.",
        "Set up Bring Your Own IP (BYOIP) addresses. Use the same PI addresses for each Region where the solution is deployed."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 79"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has set up a NAT gateway in a single Availability Zone (AZ1) in a VPC (VPC1) to access the internet from Amazon EC2 workloads in the VPC. The EC2 workloads are running in private subnets in three Availability Zones (AZ1, AZ2, AZ3). The route table for each subnet is configured to use the NAT gateway to access the internet.\n\nRecently during an outage, internet access stopped working for the EC2 workloads because of the NAT gateway's unavailability. A network engineer must implement a solution to remove the single point of failure from the architecture and provide built-in redundancy.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Set up two NAT gateways. Place each NAT gateway in a different public subnet in separate Availability Zones (AZ2 and AZ3). Configure a route table to point the AZ2 private subnets to the NAT gateway in AZ2. Configure a second route table to point the AZ3 private subnets to the NAT gateway in AZ3.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set up two NAT gateways. Place each NAT gateway in a different public subnet in separate Availability Zones (AZ2 and AZ3). Configure a route table for private subnets to route traffic to the virtual IP addresses of the two NAT gateways.",
        "Set up two NAT gateways. Place each NAT gateway in a different public subnet in separate Availability Zones (AZ2 and AZ3). Configure a route table to point the AZ2 private subnets to the NAT gateway in AZ2. Configure the same route table to point the AZ3 private subnets to the NAT gateway in AZ3.",
        "Create a second VPC (VPC2). Set up two NAT gateways. Place each NAT gateway in a different VPC (VPC1 and VPC2) and in the same Availability Zone (AZ2). Configure a route table in VPC1 to point the AZ2 private subnets to one NAT gateway. Configure a route table in VPC2 to point the AZ2 private subnets to the second NAT gateway."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 80"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a total of 30 VPCs. Three AWS Regions each contain 10 VPCs. The company has attached the VPCs in each Region to a transit gateway in that Region. The company also has set up inter-Region peering connections between the transit gateways.\n\nThe company wants to use AWS Direct Connect to provide access from its on-premises location for only four VPCs across the three Regions. The company has provisioned four Direct Connect connections at two Direct Connect locations.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create four virtual private gateways. Attach the virtual private gateways to the four VPCs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create four transit VIFs on each Direct Connect connection. Associate the transit VIFs with the Direct Connect gateway.",
        "Create four transit VIFs on each Direct Connect connection. Associate the transit VIFs with the four virtual private gateways.",
        "Create an association between the Direct Connect gateway and the transit gateways."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create a Direct Connect gateway. Associate the four virtual private gateways with the Direct Connect gateway.||Create four private VIFs on each Direct Connect connection to the Direct Connect gateway.",
        "code": "Question 81"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to manage Amazon EC2 instances through command line interfaces for Linux hosts and Windows hosts. The EC2 instances are deployed in an environment in which there is no route to the internet. The company must implement role-based access control for management of the instances. The company has a standalone on-premises environment.\n\nWhich approach will meet these requirements with the LEAST maintenance overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy and configure AWS Systems Manager Agent (SSM Agent) on each instance. Deploy VPC endpoints for Systems Manager Session Manager. Connect to the instances by using Session Manager.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set up an AWS Direct Connect connection between the on-premises environment and the VPC where the instances are deployed. Configure routing, security groups, and ACLs. Connect to the instances by using the Direct Connect connection.",
        "Establish an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection between the on-premises environment and the VPC where the instances are deployed. Configure routing, security groups, and ACLs. Connect to the instances by using the Site-to-Site VPN connection.",
        "Deploy an appliance to the VPC where the instances are deployed. Assign a public IP address to the appliance. Configure security groups and ACLs. Connect to the instances by using the appliance as an intermediary."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 82"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer needs to improve the network security of an existing AWS environment by adding an AWS Network Firewall firewall to control internet-bound traffic. The AWS environment consists of five VPCs. Each VPC has an internet gateway, NAT gateways, public Application Load Balancers (ALBs), and Amazon EC2 instances. The EC2 instances are deployed in private subnets. The architecture is deployed across two Availability Zones.\n\nThe network engineer must be able to configure rules for the public IP addresses in the environment, regardless of the direction of traffic. The network engineer must add the firewall by implementing a solution that minimizes changes to the existing production environment. The solution also must ensure high availability.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network engineer take to meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Configure new subnets in two Availability Zones in each VPC. Deploy Network Firewall in each VPC with an endpoint in each Availability Zone.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a centralized inspection VPC with subnets in two Availability Zones. Deploy Network Firewall in this inspection VPC with an endpoint in each Availability Zone.",
        "Deploy Network Firewall in each VPUse existing subnets in each of the two Availability Zones to deploy Network Firewall endpoints.",
        "Update the route tables that are associated with the private subnets that host the EC2 instances. Add routes to the Network Firewall endpoints."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Update the route tables that are associated with the public subnets that host the NAT gateways and the ALBs. Add routes to the Network Firewall endpoints.",
        "code": "Question 83"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to migrate an internal application to the AWS Cloud. The application will run on Amazon EC2 instances in one VPC. Users will access the application from the company's on-premises data center through AWS VPN or AWS Direct Connect. Users will use private domain names for the application endpoint from a domain name that is reserved explicitly for use in the AWS Cloud.\n\nEach EC2 instance must have automatic failover to another EC2 instance in the same AWS account and the same VPC. A network engineer must design a DNS solution that will not expose the application to the internet.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Place the EC2 instances in private subnets. Create an Amazon Route 53 private hosted zone for the AWS reserved domain name. Associate the private hosted zone with the VPCreate a Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint. Configure conditional forwarding in the on-premises DNS resolvers to forward all DNS queries for the AWS domain to the inbound endpoint IP address for Route 53 Resolver. In the private hosted zone, configure primary and failover records that point to the IP addresses of the EC2 instances. Create an Amazon CloudWatch metric and alarm to monitor the application's health. Set up a health check on the alarm for the primary application endpoint.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Assign public IP addresses to the EC2 instances. Create an Amazon Route 53 private hosted zone for the AWS reserved domain name. Associate the private hosted zone with the VPC. Create a Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoint. Configure conditional forwarding in the on-premises DNS resolvers to forward all DNS queries for the AWS domain to the outbound endpoint IP address for Route 53 Resolver. In the private hosted zone, configure primary and failover records that point to the public IP addresses of the EC2 instances. Create an Amazon CloudWatch metric and alarm to monitor the application's health. Set up a health check on the alarm for the primary application endpoint.",
        "Place the EC2 instances in private subnets. Create an Amazon Route 53 public hosted zone for the AWS reserved domain name. Associate the public hosted zone with the VPC. Create a Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint. Configure conditional forwarding in the on-premises DNS resolvers to forward all DNS queries for the AWS domain to the inbound endpoint IP address for Route 53 Resolver. In the public hosted zone, configure primary and failover records that point to the IP addresses of the EC2 instances. Create an Amazon CloudWatch metric and alarm to monitor the application's health. Set up a health check on the alarm for the primary application endpoint.",
        "Place the EC2 instances in private subnets. Create an Amazon Route 53 private hosted zone for the AWS reserved domain name. Associate the private hosted zone with the VPC. Create a Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint. Configure conditional forwarding in the on-premises DNS resolvers to forward all DNS queries for the AWS domain to the inbound endpoint IP address for Route 53 Resolver. In the private hosted zone, configure primary and failover records that point to the IP addresses of the EC2 instances. Set up Route 53 health checks on the private IP addresses of the EC2 instances."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 84"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses Amazon Route 53 for its DNS needs. The company's security team wants to update the DNS infrastructure to provide the most recent security posture.\n\nThe security team has configured DNS Security Extensions (DNSSEC) for the domain. The security team wants a network engineer to explain who is responsible for the rotation of DNSSEC keys.\n\nWhich explanation should the network administrator provide to the security team?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS rotates the zone-signing key (ZSK). The company rotates the key-signing key (KSK).",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The company rotates the zone-signing key (ZSK) and the key-signing key (KSK).",
        "AWS rotates the AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) key and the key-signing key (KSK).",
        "The company rotates the AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) key. AWS rotates the key-signing key (KSK)."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 85"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has agreed to collaborate with a partner for a research project. The company has multiple VPCs in the us-east-1 Region that use CIDR blocks within 10.10.0.0/16. The VPCs are connected by a transit gateway that is named TGW-C in us-east-1. TGW-C has an Autonomous System Number (ASN) configuration value of 64520.\n\nThe partner has multiple VPCs in us-east-1 that use CIDR blocks within 172.16.0.0/16. The VPCs are connected by a transit gateway that is named TGW-P in us-east-1. TGW-P has an ASN configuration value of 64530.\n\nA network engineer needs to establish network connectivity between the company's VPCs and the partner's VPCs in us-east-1.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with MINIMUM changes to both networks?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure a cross-account transit gateway peering attachment between TGW-C and TGW-P. Configure the routing between the transit gateways to use the peering attachment.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new VPC in a new account. Deploy a router from AWS Marketplace. Share TGW-C and TGW-P with the new account by using AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM). Associate TGW-C and TGW-P with the new VPC. Configure the router in the new VPC to route between TGW-C and TGW-P.",
        "Create an IPsec VPN connection between TGW-C and TGW-P. Configure the routing between the transit gateways to use the IPsec VPN connection.",
        "Share TGW-C with the partner account by using AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM). Associate the partner VPCs with TGW-C. Configure routing in the partner VPCs and TGW-C."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 86"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a public application. The application uses an Application Load Balancer (ALB) that has a target group of Amazon EC2 instances.\n\nThe company wants to protect the application from security issues in web requests. The traffic to the application must have end-to-end encryption.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure a third-party certificate on the EC2 instances for the communication between the ALB and the EC2 instances. Import the third-party certificate into AWS Certificate Manager (ACM). Associate the imported certificate with the ALB. Configure TLS connections to terminate at the ALB. Configure an AWS WAF web ACL. Associate the web ACL with the ALB.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure a Network Load Balancer (NLB) that has a target group of the existing EC2 instances. Configure TLS connections to terminate on the EC2 instances that use a public certificate. Configure an AWS WAF web ACL. Associate the web ACL with the NLB.",
        "Configure TLS connections to terminate at the ALB that uses a public certificate. Configure AWS Certificate Manager (ACM) certificates for the communication between the ALB and the EC2 instances. Configure an AWS WAF web ACL. Associate the web ACL with the ALB.",
        "Configure a Network Load Balancer (NLB) that has a target group of the existing EC2 instances. Configure TLS connections to terminate at the EC2 instances by creating a TLS listener. Configure self-signed certificates on the EC2 instances for the communication between the NLB and the EC2 instances. Configure an AWS WAF web ACL. Associate the web ACL with the NLB."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 87"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an application that hosts personally identifiable information (PII) of users. All connections to the application must be secured by HTTPS with TLS certificates that implement Elliptic Curve Cryptography (ECC).\n\nThe application uses stateful connections between the web tier and the end users. Multiple instances host the application. A network engineer must implement a solution that offloads TLS connections to a load balancer.\n\nWhich load-balancing solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Provision an Application Load Balancer. Configure an HTTPS listener by specifying the use of an ECC SSL certificate that is uploaded to AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM). Configure a default action to redirect to the URL for the application. Turn on application-based session affinity (sticky sessions).",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Provision a Network Load Balancer. Configure a TLS listener by specifying the use of an ECC SSL certificate that is uploaded to AWS identity and Access Management (IAM). Turn on health checks to monitor the web hosts that connect to the end users.",
        "Provision an Application Load Balancer. Configure an HTTPS listener by specifying the use of an ECC SSL certificate that is uploaded to AWS Certificate Manager (ACM). Configure a default action to redirect to the URL for the application. Turn on health checks to monitor the web hosts that connect to the end users.",
        "Provision a Network Load Balancer. Configure a TLS listener by specifying the use of an ECC SSL certificate that is uploaded to AWS Certificate Manager (ACM). Turn on application-based session affinity (sticky sessions). Turn on health checks to monitor the web hosts that connect to the end users."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 88"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company hosts infrastructure services in multiple VPCs across multiple accounts in the us-west-2 Region. The VPC CIDR blocks do not overlap. The company wants to connect the VPCs to its data centers by using AWS Site-to-Site VPN tunnels.\n\nThe connections must be encrypted in transit. Additionally, the connection from each data center must route to the closest AWS edge location. The connections must be highly available and must accommodate automatic failover.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy a transit gateway. Share the transit gateway with each of the other accounts by using AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM). Create VPC attachments to the transit gateway from each service account. Add routes to the on-premises subnet in each of the service VPC route tables by using the attachment as the gateway. Create Site-to-Site VPN tunnel attachments with dynamic routing to the transit gateway. Enable the acceleration feature for the Site-to-Site VPN connection. Configure the VPN tunnels on the on-premises equipment. Configure BGP peering.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy VPN gateways to each account. Enable the acceleration feature for VPN gateways on each account. Add routes to the on-premises subnet in each of the service VPC route tables. Use the VPNs as the gateway. Configure the VPN tunnels on the on-premises equipment. Configure BGP peering.",
        "Deploy a transit gateway. Share the transit gateway with each of the other accounts by using AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM). Create VPC attachments to the transit gateway from each service account. Add routes to the on-premises subnet in each of the service VPC route tables by using the attachment as the gateway. Create Site-to-Site VPN tunnel attachments with dynamic routing to the transit gateway. Enable the acceleration feature for the Site-to-Site VPN connection. Configure the VPN tunnels on the on-premises equipment. Configure static routing.",
        "Deploy VPN gateways to each account. Enable the acceleration feature for VPN gateways on each account. Add routes to the on-premises subnet in each of the service VPC route tables. Use the VPNs as the gateway. Configure the VPN tunnels on the on-premises equipment. Configure static routing."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 89"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning a migration of its critical workloads from an on-premises data center to Amazon EC2 instances. The plan includes a new 10 Gbps AWS Direct Connect dedicated connection from the on-premises data center to a VPC that is attached to a transit gateway. The migration must occur over encrypted paths between the on-premises data center and the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements while providing the HIGHEST throughput?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure MACsec for the Direct Connect connection. Configure a transit VIF to a Direct Connect gateway that is associated with the transit gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure a public VIF on the Direct Connect connection. Configure an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection to the transit gateway as a VPN attachment.",
        "Configure a transit VIF on the Direct Connect connection. Configure an IPsec VPN connection to an EC2 instance that is running third-party VPN software.",
        "Configure a public VIF on the Direct Connect connection. Configure two AWS Site-to-Site VPN connections to the transit gateway. Enable equal-cost multi-path (ECMP) routing."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 90"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a transit gateway in AWS Account A. The company uses AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM) to share the transit gateway so that users in other accounts can connect to multiple VPCs in the same AWS Region. AWS Account B contains a VPC (10.0.0.0/16) with subnet 10.0.0.0/24 in the us-west-2a Availability Zone and subnet 10.0.1.0/24 in the us-west-2b Availability Zone. Resources in these subnets can communicate with other VPCs.\n\nA network engineer creates two new subnets: 10.0.2.0/24 in the us-west-2b Availability Zone and 10.0.3.0/24 in the us-west-2c Availability Zone. All the subnets share one route table. The default route 0.0.0.0/0 is pointing to the transit gateway. Resources in subnet 10.0.2.0/24 can communicate with other VPCs, but resources in subnet 10.0.3.0/24 cannot communicate with other VPCs.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do so that resources in subnet 10.0.3.0/24 can communicate with other VPCs?",
      "correct_answer": "In Account B, update the transit gateway attachment. Attach the new subnet ID that is associated with us-west-2c to Account B's VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "In Account B, add 10.0.2.0/24 and 10.0.3.0/24 as the destinations to the route table. Use the transit gateway as the target.",
        "In Account A, create a static route for 10.0.3.0/24 in the transit gateway route tables.",
        "In Account A, recreate propagation for 10.0.0.0/16 in the transit gateway route tables."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 91"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has started using AWS Cloud WAN with one edge location in the us-east-1 Region. The company has a production segment and a security segment in AWS Cloud WAN. The company also has a default core network policy.\n\nThe company has created a production VPC for the production workload. The company has created an outbound inspection VPC to inspect internet-bound traffic from the production VPC. The company has attached the production VPC to the production segment and has attached the outbound inspection VPC to the security segment. The company has also created an AWS Network Firewall firewall in the outbound inspection VPC to inspect internet-based traffic.\n\nThe company has updated a route table for the production VPC to send all internet-bound traffic to the AWS Cloud WAN core network. The company has updated a route table for the outbound inspection VPC to ensure that Network Firewall inspects any outgoing traffic and incoming traffic.\n\nDuring testing, an Amazon EC2 instance in the production VPC cannot reach the internet. The company checks the Network Firewall rules and confirms that the rules are not blocking the traffic.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Update the core network policy to configure segment sharing. Share the production segment with the security segment.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Update the core network policy to create a static route for the security segment. Specify 0.0.0.0/0 as the destination CIDR block. Specify the outbound inspection VPC as an attachment.",
        "Update the core network policy to create a static route for the production segment. Specify 10.2.0.0/16 as the destination CIDR block. Specify the outbound inspection VPC as an attachment.",
        "Create an attachment to attach the outbound inspection VPC to the production segment. Update the core network policy to turn on isolated attachment for the production segment."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Update the core network policy to create a static route for the production segment. Specify 0.0.0.0/0 as the destination CIDR block. Specify the outbound inspection VPC as an attachment.",
        "code": "Question 92"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has two business units (BUs). The company operates in the us-east-1 Region and the us-west-1 Region. The company plans to extend to more Regions in the future. Each BU has a VPC in each Region. Each Region has a transit gateway with the BU VPCs attached. The transit gateways in both Regions are peered.\n\nThe company will create several more BUs in the future and will need to isolate some of the BUs from the other BUs. The company wants to migrate to an architecture to incorporate more Regions and BUs.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the MOST operational efficiency?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an AWS Cloud WAN core network with an edge location in both Regions. Configure a segment for each BU with VPC attachments to the new BU VPCs. Use segment actions to control traffic between segments.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new transit gateway for each new BU in each Region. Peer the new transit gateways with the existing transit gateways. Update the route tables to control traffic between BUs.",
        "Create an AWS Cloud WAN core network with an edge location in both Regions. Configure a segment for each BU with VPC attachments to the new BU VPCs. Configure the segments to isolate attachments to control traffic between segments.",
        "Attach new VPCs to the existing transit gateways. Update route tables to control traffic between BUs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 93"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection between AWS and its branch office. A network engineer is troubleshooting connectivity issues that the connection is experiencing. The VPN connection terminates at a transit gateway and is statically routed. In the transit gateway route table, there are several static route entries that target specific subnets at the branch office.\n\nThe network engineer determines that the root cause of the issues was the expansion of underlying subnet ranges in the branch office during routine maintenance.\n\nWhich solution will solve this problem with the LEAST administrative overhead for future expansion efforts?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a dynamically routed VPN connection on the transit gateway. Connect the dynamically routed VPN connection to the branch office. Create a propagation for the VPN attachment to the transit gateway route table. Remove the existing static VPN connection.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Determine a supernet for the branch office. In the transit gateway route table, add an aggregate route that targets the VPN attachment. Replace the specific subnet routes in the transit gateway route table with the new supernet route.",
        "Create an AWS Direct Connect gateway and a transit VIF. Associate the Direct Connect gateway with the transit gateway. Create a propagation for the Direct Connect attachment to the transit gateway route table.",
        "Create a prefix list that contains the new subnets and the old subnets for the branch office. Remove the specific subnet routes in the transit gateway route table. Create a prefix list reference in the transit gateway route table."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 94"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An education agency is preparing for its annual competition between schools. In the competition, students at schools from around the country solve math problems, complete puzzles, and write essays.\n\nThe IP addressing plan of all the schools is well-known and is administered centrally. The competition is hosted in the AWS Cloud and is not publicly available. All competition traffic must be encrypted in transit. Only authorized endpoints can access the competition. All the schools have firewall policies that block ICMP traffic.\n\nA network engineer builds a solution in which all the schools access the competition through AWS Site-to-Site VPN connections. The network engineer uses BGP as the routing protocol. The network engineer must implement a solution that notifies schools when they lose connectivity and need to take action on their premises to address the issue.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Monitor the state of the VPN tunnels by using Amazon CloudWatch. Create a CloudWatch alarm that uses Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) to notify people at the affected school if the tunnels are down.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a scheduled AWS Lambda function that pings each school's on-premises customer gateway device. Configure the Lambda function to send an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) notification to people at the affected school if the ping fails.",
        "Create a scheduled AWS Lambda function that uses the VPC Reachability Analyzer API to verify the connectivity. Configure the Lambda function to send an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) notification to people at the affected school if failure occurs.",
        "Create an Amazon CloudWatch dashboard for each school to show all CloudWatch metrics for each school's Site-to-Site VPN connection. Share each dashboard with the appropriate school."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create a scheduled AWS Lambda function to monitor the existence of each school's routes in the VPC route table where VPN routes are propagated. Configure the Lambda function to send an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) notification to people at the affected school if failure occurs.",
        "code": "Question 95"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company securely connects resources that are in its VPC to a software as a service (SaaS) solution from a SaaS provider. The SaaS solution is hosted in the AWS Cloud and is powered by AWS PrivateLink. The company uses a PrivateLink endpoint to access the SaaS solution behind the SaaS provider's Network Load Balancer (NLB).\n\nThe company recently added a new Availability Zone and new subnets to its VPC. A network engineer is unable to deploy a new interface VPC endpoint for the SaaS solution in the new Availability Zone.\n\nWhat is the cause of this problem?",
      "correct_answer": "The SaaS provider does not offer the solution in the new Availability Zone and has not configured cross-zone load balancing for the NLB.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The CIDR block of the new subnets conflicts with the SaaS provider's CIDR block.",
        "The enableDnsHostnames attribute and enableDnsSupport attribute were not configured on the new subnets in the new Availability Zone.",
        "The new subnets are missing a route to the VPC internet gateway."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 96"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use an AWS Network Firewall firewall to secure its workloads in the cloud through network traffic inspection. The company must record complete metadata information, such as source/destination IP addresses and protocol type. The company must also record all network traffic flows and any DROP or ALERT actions that the firewall takes for traffic that the firewall processes. The Network Firewall endpoints are placed in the correct subnets, and the VPC route tables direct traffic to the Network Firewall endpoints on the path to and from the internet.\n\nHow should a network engineer configure the firewall to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a firewall policy to ensure that a stateful engine processes all the traffic. Configure Network Firewall logging for alert logs and flow logs. Select a destination for alert logs and flow logs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a firewall policy to ensure that traffic is processed by stateless or stateful rules according to needs. Select Amazon CloudWatch Logs as the destination for the flow logs.",
        "Create a firewall policy to ensure that traffic is processed by stateless or stateful rules according to needs. Configure Network Firewall logging for alert logs and flow logs. Select a destination for logs separately for stateful and stateless engines.",
        "Create a firewall policy to ensure that a stateful engine processes all the traffic. Configure VPC flow logs for the subnets that the firewall protects. Select a destination for the flow logs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 97"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building a new workload on AWS that uses an Application Load Balancer (ALB). The company has configured a new ALB target group that uses slow start mode. A team begins registering Amazon EC2 instances as targets in the new target group. During testing, the team observes that the targets did not enter slow start mode.\n\nWhat caused the targets to not enter slow start mode?",
      "correct_answer": "The target group did not contain at least one healthy target configured in slow start mode.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The ALB configuration uses the round robin routing algorithm for traffic.",
        "The target group must contain EC2 instances that are all the same instance type.",
        "The ALB configuration uses the 5-tuple criteria for traffic."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 98"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer is using AWS Direct Connect connections and MACsec to encrypt data from a corporate data center to the Direct Connect location. The network engineer learns that the MACsec secret key might have been compromised. The network engineer needs to update the connection with an uncompromised secure key.\n\nWhich solution will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new MACsec secret key that uses an AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) customer managed key. Associate the new pre-shared key, Connection Key Name (CKN), and Connectivity Association Key (CAK) with the connection.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new MACsec secret key that uses an AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) AWS managed key. Associate the new pre-shared key, Connection Key Name (CKN), and Connectivity Association Key (CAK) with the connection.",
        "Modify the existing MACsec secret key. Re-associate the existing pre-shared key, Connection Key Name (CKN), and Connectivity Association Key (CAK) with the connection.",
        "Modify the existing MACsec secret key. Associate the new pre-shared key, Connection Key Name (CKN), and Connectivity Association Key (CAK) with the connection."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 99"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer configures a second AWS Direct Connect connection to an existing network. The network engineer runs a test in the AWS Direct Connect Resiliency Toolkit on the connections. The test produces a failure. During the failover event, the network engineer observes a 90-second interruption before traffic shifts to the failover connection.\n\nWhich solution will reduce the time for failover?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure Bidirectional Forwarding Detection (BFD) on the on-premises router.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Decrease the BGP hello timer to 5 seconds.",
        "Add a VPN connection to the connectivity solution. Implement fast failover.",
        "Decrease the BGP hold-down timer to 5 seconds."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 100"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer must develop an AWS CloudFormation template that can create a virtual private gateway, a customer gateway, a VPN connection, and static routes in a route table. During testing of the template, the network engineer notes that the CloudFormation template has encountered an error and is rolling back.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to resolve the error?",
      "correct_answer": "Add the DependsOn attribute to the resource declaration for the route table entry. Specify the virtual private gateway resource.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Change the order of resource creation in the CloudFormation template.",
        "Add the DependsOn attribute to the resource declaration for the virtual private gateway. Specify the route table entry resource.",
        "Add a wait condition in the template to wait for the creation of the virtual private gateway."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 101"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building an API-based application on AWS and is using a microservices architecture for the design. The company is using a multi-account AWS environment that includes a separate AWS account for each microservice development team. Each team hosts its microservice in its own VPC that contains Amazon EC2 instances behind a Network Load Balancer (NLB).\n\nA network engineer needs to use Amazon API Gateway in a shared services account to create an HTTP API to expose these microservices to external applications. The network engineer must ensure that access to the microservices can occur only over a private network. Additionally, the company must be able to control which entities from its internal network can connect to the microservices. In the future, the company will create more microservices that the company must be able to integrate with the application.\n\nWhat is the MOST secure solution that meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an Application Load Balancer (ALB) in a VPC in the shared services account. Configure the integration to the API Gateway API by using a VPC link. Associate the VPC link with the ALB. Create a VPC endpoint service in each microservice account. Create an AWS PrivateLink endpoint for those services in the shared services account. Add the elastic network interface IP addresses of the VPC endpoint as targets for the target group of the ALB.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an Application Load Balancer (ALB) in a VPC in the shared services account. Configure the integration to the API Gateway API by using a VPC link. Associate the VPC link with the ALConnect all the VPCs to each other by using a central transit gateway. Add the IP addresses of the NLB as IP-based targets in the ALB target group.",
        "Configure the integration to the API Gateway API by using HTTP-based integration. Connect all the VPCs to each other by using a central transit gateway. Create a separate HTTP integration to each NLB for each microservice. Add the HTTP endpoint of the NLB as the endpoint URL in the HTTP integration.",
        "Configure the integration to the API Gateway API by using VPC link integration. Connect all the VPCs to each other by using a central transit gateway. Create a separate VPC link to each NLB for each microservice. Add the HTTP endpoint of the NLB as the endpoint URL in the VPC link integration."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 102"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company's VPC has Amazon EC2 instances that are communicating with AWS services over the public internet. The company needs to change the connectivity so that the communication does not occur over the public internet.\n\nThe company deploys AWS PrivateLink endpoints in the VPC. After the deployment of the PrivateLink endpoints, the EC2 instances can no longer communicate at all with the required AWS services.\n\nWhich combination of steps should a network engineer take to restore communication with the AWS services? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Ensure that the enableDnsSupport attribute is set to True for the VPC. Ensure that each VPC endpoint has DNS support enabled.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "In the VPC route table, add a route that has the PrivateLink endpoints as the destination.",
        "Create an Amazon Route 53 public hosted zone for all services.",
        "Create an Amazon Route 53 private hosted zone that includes a custom name for each service."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Ensure that the VPC endpoint policy allows communication.",
        "code": "Question 103"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An international company wants to implement a multi-site hybrid infrastructure. The company wants to deploy its cloud computing resources on AWS in the us-east-1 Region and in the eu-west-2 Region, and in on-premises data centers in the United States (US) and in the United Kingdom (UK). The data centers are connected to each other by a private WAN connection. IP routing information is exchanged dynamically through BGP. The company wants to have two AWS Direct Connect connections, one each in the US and the UK.\n\nThe company expects to have 15 VPCs in each Region with CIDR blocks that do not overlap with each other or with CIDR blocks of the on-premises environment. The VPC CIDR blocks are planned so that the prefix aggregation can be performed both on a Regional level and across the entire AWS environment. The company will deploy a transit gateway in each Region to connect the VPCs. A network engineer plans to use a Direct Connect gateway in each Region. A transit VIF will attach the Direct Connect gateway in each Region to the transit gateway in that Region. The transit gateways will be peered with each other.\n\nThe network engineer wants to ensure that traffic follows the shortest geographical path from source to destination. Traffic between the on-premises data centers and AWS must travel across a local Direct Connect connection. Traffic between the US data center and eu-west-2 and traffic between the UK data center and us-east-1 must use the private WAN connection to reach the Direct Connect connection to the appropriate Region when the Direct Connect connection is available. The network must be resilient to failures in either the private WAN connection or with the Direct Connect connections. The network also must reroute traffic automatically in the event of any failure.\n\nHow should the network engineer configure the transit VIF associations on the Direct Connect gateways to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Advertise VPC-specific CIDR prefixes from only the local Region. Additionally, advertise the aggregate route for the company’s entire AWS environment.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Advertise only the aggregate route for the company's entire AWS environment.",
        "Advertise all the specific VPC CIDR blocks from both Regions.",
        "Advertise both Regional aggregate prefixes. Configure custom BGP communities on the routes advertised toward the data center."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 104"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company's AWS infrastructure is spread across more than 50 accounts and across five AWS Regions. The company needs to manage its security posture with simplified administration and maintenance for all the AWS accounts. The company wants to use AWS Firewall Manager to manage the firewall rules and requirements.\n\nThe company creates an organization with all features enabled in AWS Organizations.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the company take next to meet the requirements? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Configure all the accounts to join the organization.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure only the Firewall Manager administrator account to join the organization.",
        "Set an account as the Firewall Manager child account.",
        "Set up AWS Config for only the organization's management account."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Set an account as the Firewall Manager administrator account.||Set up AWS Config for all the accounts and all the Regions where the company has resources.",
        "code": "Question 105"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using an Amazon CloudFront distribution that is configured with an Application Load Balancer (ALB) as an origin. A network engineer needs to implement a solution that requires all inbound traffic to the ALB to come from CloudFront. The network engineer must implement the solution at the network layer rather than in the application.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements in the MOST operationally efficient way?",
      "correct_answer": "Add an inbound rule to the ALB's security group to allow the AWS managed prefix list for CloudFront.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Add an inbound rule to the network ACLs that are associated with the ALB's subnets. Use the AWS managed prefix list for CloudFront as the source in the rule.",
        "Configure CloudFront to add a custom HTTP header to the requests that CloudFront sends to the ALB.",
        "Associate an AWS WAF web ACL with the ALB. Configure the AWS WAF rules to allow traffic from the CloudFront IP set. Automatically update the CloudFront IP set by using an AWS Lambda function."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 106"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has AWS accounts in an organization in AWS Organizations. The company has implemented Amazon VPC IP Address Manager (IPAM) in its networking AWS account. The company is using AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM) to share IPAM pools with other AWS accounts. The company has created a top-level pool with a CIDR block of 10.0.0.0/8. For each AWS account, the company has created an IPAM pool within the top-level pool.\n\nA network engineer needs to implement a solution to ensure that users in each AWS account cannot create new VPCs. The solution also must prevent users from associating a CIDR block with existing VPCs unless the CIDR block is from the IPAM pool for that account.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new SCP in Organizations. Add a condition that denies the CreateVpc and AssociateVpcCidrBlock Amazon EC2 actions if the Ipv4IpamPoolId context key value is not the ID of an IPAM pool.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new AWS Config rule to find all VPCs that are not configured to allocate their CIDR block from an IPAM pool. Invoke an AWS Lambda function to delete these VPCs.",
        "Create an AWS Lambda function to check for and delete all VPCs that are not configured to allocate their CIDR block from an IPAM pool. Invoke the Lambda function at regular intervals.",
        "Create an Amazon EventBridge rule to check for AWS CloudTrail events for the CreateVpc and AssociateVpcCidrBlock Amazon EC2 actions. Use the rule to invoke an AWS Lambda function to delete all VPCs that are not configured to allocate their CIDR block from an IPAM pool."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 107"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an application that runs on premises. The application needs to communicate with an application that runs in a VPC on AWS. The communication between the applications must be encrypted and must use private IP addresses. The communication cannot travel across the public internet.\n\nThe company has established a 1 Gbps AWS Direct Connect connection between the on-premises location and AWS.\n\nWhich solution will meet the connectivity requirements with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a transit gateway. Configure a transit VIF on the Direct Connect connection. Associate the transit VIF with a Direct Connect gateway. Associate the Direct Connect gateway with a new transit gateway. Set up an AWS Site-to-Site VPN private IP VPN connection to the transit gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure a private VIF on the Direct Connect connection. Associate the private VIF with the VPC's virtual private gateway. Set up an AWS Site-to-Site VPN private IP VPN connection to the virtual private gateway.",
        "Configure a public VIF on the Direct Connect connection. Associate the public VIF with a Direct Connect gateway. Associate the Direct Connect gateway with a new transit gateway. Set up an AWS Site-to-Site VPN private IP VPN connection to the transit gateway.",
        "Create a transit gateway. Configure a transit VIF on the Direct Connect connection. Associate the transit VIF with a Direct Connect gateway. Associate the Direct Connect gateway with a new transit gateway. Set up a third-party firewall in a new VPC that is attached to the transit gateway. Set up a VPN connection to the third-party firewall."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 108"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has established connectivity between its on-premises data center in Paris. France, and the AWS Cloud by using an AWS Direct Connect connection. The company uses a transit VIF that connects the Direct Connect connection with a transit gateway that is hosted in the Europe (Paris) Region. The company hosts workloads in private subnets in several VPCs that are attached to the transit gateway.\n\nThe company recently acquired another corporation that hosts workloads on premises in an office building in Tokyo, Japan. The company needs to migrate the workloads from the Tokyo office to AWS. These workloads must have access to the company's existing workloads in Paris. The company also must establish connectivity between the Tokyo office building and the Paris data center.\n\nIn the Asia Pacific (Tokyo) Region, the company creates a new VPC with private subnets for migration of the workloads. The workload migration must be completed in 5 days. The workloads cannot be directly accessible from the internet.\n\nWhich set of steps should a network engineer take to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "1. Configure a transit gateway in the Asia Pacific (Tokyo) Region. Associate this transit gateway with the Tokyo VPC. 2. Create peering connections between the Tokyo transit gateway and the Paris transit gateway. 3. Configure an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection from the Tokyo office. Set the Tokyo transit gateway as the target. 4. Configure routing on both transit gateways to allow data to flow between sites and the VPCs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1. Create public subnets in the Tokyo VPC to migrate the workloads into. 2. Configure an internet gateway for the Tokyo office to reach the Tokyo VPC. 3. Configure security groups on the Tokyo workloads to only allow traffic from the Tokyo office and the Paris workloads. 4. Create peering connections between the Tokyo VPC and the Paris VPCs. 5. Configure a VPN connection between the Paris data center and the Tokyo office by using existing routers.",
        "1. Configure a transit gateway in the Asia Pacific (Tokyo) Region. Associate this transit gateway with the Tokyo VPC. 2. Create peering connections between the Tokyo transit gateway and the Paris transit gateway. 3. Set up a new Direct Connect connection from the Tokyo office to the Tokyo transit gateway. 4. Configure routing on both transit gateways to allow data to flow between sites and the VPCs.",
        "1. Configure an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection from the Tokyo office to the Paris transit gateway. 2. Create an association between the Paris transit gateway and the Tokyo VPC. 3. Configure routing on the Paris transit gateway to allow data to flow between sites and the VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 109"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Company A recently acquired Company B. Company A has a hybrid AWS and on-premises environment that uses a hosted AWS Direct Connect connection, a Direct Connect gateway, and a transit gateway. Company A has a transit VIF to access the resources in its production environment in the us-east-1 Region.\n\nCompany B has applications that run across multiple VPCs in the us-west-2 Region in a single AWS account. A transit gateway connects all Company B's application VPCs. The CIDR blocks for both companies do not overlap.\n\nCompany A needs to use the existing Direct Connect connection to access Company B’s applications from the on-premises environment.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an association proposal from the Company B account to associate the Company B transit gateway with the Company A Direct Connect gateway. Accept the transit gateway association proposal by logging into the Company A account.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new Direct Connect gateway in the Company B account. Associate the Company B transit gateway with the new Direct Connect gateway. Create a transit VIF on the existing hosted connection for Company B.",
        "Create multiple virtual private gateways. Attach the virtual private gateways to each of Company B's application VPCs. Create a hosted private VIF for each virtual private gateway.",
        "Create a new Direct Connect gateway in the Company B account. Associate the Company B transit gateway with the new Direct Connect gateway. Create a hosted private VIF for Company B."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 110"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has developed a web service for language translation. The web service's application runs on a fleet of Amazon EC2 instances that are in an Auto Scaling group. The instances run behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB) and are deployed in a private subnet. The web service can process requests that contain hundreds of megabytes of data.\n\nThe company needs to give some customers the ability to access the web service. Each customer has its own AWS account. The company must make the web service accessible to approved customers without making the web service accessible to all customers.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet these requirements with the LEAST operational overhead? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create an AWS PrivateLink endpoint service. Configure the endpoint service to require acceptance that will be granted to approved customers only.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create VPC peering connections with the approved customers only.",
        "Configure an authentication action for the endpoint service's load balancer to allow customers to log in by using their AWS credentials. Provide only approved customers with the URL.",
        "Associate the ALB with the endpoint service."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Configure a Network Load Balancer (NLB) and a listener with the ALB as a target. Associate the NLB with the endpoint service.",
        "code": "Question 111"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is deploying a new application in the AWS Cloud. The company wants a highly available web server that will sit behind an Elastic Load Balancer. The load balancer will route requests to multiple target groups based on the URL in the request. All traffic must use HTTPS. TLS processing must be offloaded to the load balancer. The web server must know the user’s IP address so that the company can keep accurate logs for security purposes.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy an Application Load Balancer with an HTTPS listener. Use path-based routing rules to forward the traffic to the correct target group. Include the X-Forwarded-For request header with traffic to the targets.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy an Application Load Balancer with an HTTPS listener for each domain. Use host-based routing rules to forward the traffic to the correct target group for each domain. Include the X-Forwarded-For request header with traffic to the targets.",
        "Deploy a Network Load Balancer with a TLS listener. Use path-based routing rules to forward the traffic to the correct target group. Configure client IP address preservation for traffic to the targets.",
        "Deploy a Network Load Balancer with a TLS listener for each domain. Use host-based routing rules to forward the traffic to the correct target group for each domain. Configure client IP address preservation for traffic to the targets."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 112"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company operates its IT services through a multi-site hybrid infrastructure. The company deploys resources on AWS in the us-east-1 Region and in the eu-west-2 Region. The company also deploys resources in its own data centers that are located in the United States (US) and in the United Kingdom (UK). In both AWS Regions, the company uses a transit gateway to connect 15 VPCs to each other. The company has created a transit gateway peering connection between the two transit gateways. The VPC CIDR blocks do not overlap with each other or with IP addresses used within the data centers. The VPC CIDR prefixes can also be aggregated either on a Regional level or for the company's entire AWS environment.\n\nThe data centers are connected to each other by a private WAN connection. IP routing information is exchanged dynamically through Interior BGP (iBGP) sessions. The data centers maintain connectivity to AWS through one AWS Direct Connect connection in the US and one Direct Connect connection in the UK. Each Direct Connect connection is terminated on a Direct Connect gateway and is associated with a local transit gateway through a transit VIF.\n\nTraffic follows the shortest geographical path from source to destination. For example, packets from the UK data center that are targeted to resources in eu-west-2 travel across the local Direct Connect connection. In cases of cross-Region data transfers, such as from the UK data center to VPCs in us-east-1, the private WAN connection must be used to minimize costs on AWS. A network engineer has configured each transit gateway association on the Direct Connect gateway to advertise VPC-specific CIDR IP prefixes only from the local Region. The routes toward the other Region must be learned through BGP from the routers in the other data center in the original, non-aggregated form.\n\nThe company recently experienced a problem with cross-Region data transfers because of issues with its private WAN connection. The network engineer needs to modify the routing setup to prevent similar interruptions in the future. The solution cannot modify the original traffic routing goal when the network is operating normally.\n\nWhich modifications will meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Add the aggregate IP prefix for the other Region and the local VPC CIDR blocks to the list of subnets advertised through the local Direct Connect connection.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Remove all the VPC CIDR prefixes from the list of subnets advertised through the local Direct Connect connection. Add the company's entire AWS environment aggregate route to the list of subnets advertised through the local Direct Connect connection.",
        "Add the CIDR prefixes from the other Region VPCs and the local VPC CIDR blocks to the list of subnets advertised through the local Direct Connect connection. Configure data center routers to make routing decisions based on the BGP communities received.",
        "Add the aggregate IP prefix for the company's entire AWS environment and the local VPC CIDR blocks to the list of subnets advertised through the local Direct Connect connection."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Remove all the VPC CIDR prefixes from the list of subnets advertised through the local Direct Connect connection. Add both Regional aggregate IP prefixes to the list of subnets advertised through the Direct Connect connection on both sides of the network. Configure data center routers to make routing decisions based on the BGP communities received.",
        "code": "Question 113"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is migrating an application to the AWS Cloud. The company has successfully provisioned and tested connectivity between AWS Direct Connect and the company's on-premises data center. The application runs on Amazon EC2 instances across multiple Availability Zones. The instances are in an Auto Scaling group.\n\nThe application communicates through HTTPS to a third-party vendor's data service that is hosted at the company’s data center. The data service implements a static ACL through explicit allow listing of client IP addresses.\n\nA network engineer must design a network solution so that the migrated application can continue to access the vendor’s data service as the application scales.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST amount of ongoing change to the vendor's allow list?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure a private NAT gateway in the subnets for each Availability Zone that the application runs in. Configure the application to target the NAT gateways instead of the data service directly. Update the data service's allow list to include the IP addresses of the NAT gateways.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure an elastic network interface in the subnets for each Availability Zone that the application runs in. Associate the elastic network interfaces with the Auto Scaling group for the application. Update the data service's allow list to include the IP addresses of the elastic network interfaces.",
        "Configure an elastic network interface in the subnets for each Availability Zone that the application runs in. Launch an EC2 instance into each subnet. Attach the respective elastic network interfaces to the new EC2 instances. In the application subnet route tables, configure the new EC2 instances as the next destination for the data service. Update the data service’s allow list to include the IP addresses of the elastic network interfaces.",
        "Configure an Application Load Balancer (ALB) in the subnets for each Availability Zone that the application runs in. Configure an ALB-associated target group that contains a target that uses the IP address for the data service. Configure the application to target the ALB instead of the data service directly. Update the data service's allow list to include the IP addresses of the ALBs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 114"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a highly available application that is hosted in multiple VPCs and in two on-premises data centers. All the VPCs reside in the same AWS Region. All the VPCs require access to each other and to the on-premises data centers for the transfer of files that are multiple gigabytes in size.\n\nA network engineer is designing an AWS Direct Connect solution to connect the on-premises data centers to each VPC.\n\nWhich architecture will meet the company's requirements with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure a transit gateway in the same Region of each VPC. Attach each VPC to the transit gateway. Configure a Direct Connect gateway. Associate the Direct Connect gateway with the transit gateway. Associate a new transit VIF with each Direct Connect connection. Configure the new transit VIF to exchange BGP routes and to have an MTU of 8500. Configure route propagation between each VPC and the transit gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure a virtual private gateway and a private VIF in each VPC in the Region. Configure a Direct Connect gateway. Associate the VIF of every VPC with the Direct Connect gateway. Create a new private VIF that connects the Direct Connect gateway to each on-premises data center. Configure the new private VIF to exchange BGP routes with the on-premises data centers and to have an MTU of 9001. Use VPC peering between each VPC. Configure static routing in each VPC to provide inter-VPC routing.",
        "Configure a virtual private gateway and a private VIF in each VPC in the Region. Configure a Direct Connect gateway. Associate the VIF of every VPC with the Direct Connect gateway. Create a new private VIF that connects the Direct Connect gateway to each on-premises data center. Configure the new private VIF to exchange BGP routes with the on-premises data centers and to have an MTU of 8500. Use VPC peering between each VPC. Configure static routing in each VPC to provide inter-VPC routing.",
        "Configure a transit gateway in the same Region of each VPAttach each VPC to the transit gateway. Configure a Direct Connect gateway. Associate the Direct Connect gateway with the transit gateway. Associate a new transit VIF with each Direct Connect connection. Configure the new transit VIF to exchange BGP routes and to have an MTU of 9001. Configure route propagation between each VPC and the transit gateway."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 115"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a data center in the us-west-1 Region with a 10 Gbps AWS Direct Connect dedicated connection to a Direct Connect gateway. There are two private VIFs from the same data center location in us-west-1 that are attached to the same Direct Connect gateway.\n\nVIF 1 advertises 172.16.0.0/16 with an AS_PATH attribute value of 65000. VIF 2 advertises 172.16.1.0/24 with an AS PATH attribute value of 65000 65000 65000.\n\nHow will AWS route traffic to the data center for traffic that has a destination address within the 172.16.1.0/24 network range?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS will route all traffic by using VIF 2.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS will route all traffic by using VIF 1.",
        "AWS will use both VIFs for routing by using a round-robin policy.",
        "AWS will use flow control to balance the traffic between the two VIFs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 116"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to host external websites on AWS. The websites will include multiple tiers such as web servers, application logic services, and databases. The company wants to use AWS Network Firewall, AWS WAF, and VPC security groups for network security.\n\nThe company must ensure that the Network Firewall firewalls are deployed appropriately within relevant VPCs. The company needs the ability to centrally manage policies that are deployed to Network Firewall and AWS WAF rules. The company also needs to allow application teams to manage their own security groups while ensuring that the security groups do not allow overly permissive access.\n\nWhat is the MOST operationally efficient solution that meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Define Network Firewall firewalls, AWS WAFv2 web ACLS, Network Firewall policies, and VPC security groups in code. Use AWS CloudFarmation to deploy the objects and initial policies and rule groups. Use AWS Firewall Manager to manage the AWS WAFV2 web ACLS, Network Firewall policies, and VPC security groups. Use Amazon GuardDuty to monitor for overly permissive rules.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Define Network Firewall firewalls, AWS WAFV2 web ACLs. Network Firewall policies, and VPC security groups in code. Use AWS CloudFormation to deploy the objects and initial policies and rule groups. Use CloudFormation to update the AWS WAFv2 web ACLs. Network Firewall policies, and VPC security groups. Use Amazon GuardDuty to monitor for overly permissive rules.",
        "Define Network Firewall firewalls. AWS WAFV2 web ACLs, Network Firewall policies, and VPC security groups in code. Use the AWS Management Console or the AWS CLI to manage the AWS WAFv2 web ACLs. Network Firewall policies, and VPC security groups. Use Amazon GuardDuly to invoke an AWS Lambda function to evaluate the configured rules and remove any overly permissive rules.",
        "Deploy AWS WAFv2 IP sets and AWS WAFv2 web ACLs with AWS CloudFormation. Use AWS Firewall Manager to deploy Network Firewall firewalls and VPC security groups where required and to manage the AWS WAFv2 web ACLs, Network Firewall policies, and VPC security groups."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 117"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has deployed an application in which the front end of the application communicates with the backend instances through a Network Load Balancer (NLB) in the same VPC. The application is highly available across two Availability Zones. The company wants to limit the amount of traffic that travels across the Availability Zones. Traffic from the front end of the application must stay in the same Availability Zone unless there is no healthy target in that Availability Zone behind the NLB. If there is no healthy target in the same Availability Zone, traffic must be sent to the other Availability Zone.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Turn off cross-zone load balancing on the NLConfigure the front end of the application to perform DNS lookups on the local Availability Zone NLB DNS record.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a private hosted zone with weighted routing for each Availability Zone. Point the primary record to the local Availability Zone NLB DNS record. Point the secondary record to the Regional NLB DNS record. Configure the front end of the application to perform DNS lookups on the local private hosted zone records.",
        "Create a private hosted zone. Create a failover record for each Availability Zone. For each failover record, point the primary record to the local Availability Zone NLB DNS record and point the secondary record to the Regional NLB DNS record. Configure the front end of the application to perform DNS lookups on the local private hosted zone records.",
        "Enable sticky sessions (session affinity) so that the NLB can bind a user’s session to targets in the same Availability Zone."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 118"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to protect against potential botnet command and control traffic from any Amazon EC2 instances that is in in the company’s AWS Environment.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use Amazon Route 53 Resolver DNS Firewall. Add a rule to a rule group to use the AWSManagedDomainsBotnetCommandandControl managed domain list with an action to block botnet traffic.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use AWS Shield Advanced. Activate Shield Advanced protections on the EC2 instances to filter and block botnet traffic.",
        "Use AWS WAF Bot Control. Configure a managed rule group that uses an AWS managed rule set to block botnet traffic.",
        "Use AWS Systems Manager. Run a Systems Manager Automation runbook on the EC2 instances to configure the instances to block botnet traffic."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 119"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has two on-premises data centers. The first data center is in the us-east-1 Region. The Second data canter is in the us-east-2 Region. Each data center connects to the closest AWS Direct Connect facility. The company uses Direct Connect connections, transit VIFs, and a single Direct Connect gateway to establish connectivity to VPCs in us-east-1 and us-east-2 from the company’s data centers. The company also has private connectivity from a telecommunications provider that connects the first data center to the second data center.\n\nRecently, there have been multiple connection disruptions to the private connectivity between the data centers. The company needs a solution to improve the reliability of the connection between the two data centers.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Enable the Direct Connect SiteLink feature on the existing transit VIFS that are attached to the existing Direct Connect gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new Direct Connect gateway. Enable the Direct Connect SiteLink feature on the transit VIF. Share the CIDR blocks from the first data center and the second data center with each other.",
        "Create a new public VIF to both Regions. Enable the Direct Connect SiteLink feature on the new public VIF.",
        "Enable the Direct Connect SiteLink feature on the existing Direct Connect connections."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 120"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer is working on a large migration effort from an on-premises data center to an AWS Control Tower based multi-account environment. The environment has a transit gateway that is deployed to a central network services account. The central network services account has been shared with an organization in AWS Organizations through AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM).\n\nA shared services account also exists in the environment. The shared services account hosts workloads that need to be shared with the entire organization.\n\nThe network engineer needs to create a solution to automate the deployment of common network components across the environment. The solution must provision a VPC for application workloads to each new and existing member account. The VPCs must be connected to the transit gateway in the central network services account.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet these requirements with the LEAST operational overhead? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy an AWS Lambda function to the shared services account. Program the Lambda function to assume a role in the new and existing member accounts to provision the necessary network infrastructure.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Update the existing accounts with an Account Factory Customization (AFC). Select the same AFC when provisioning new accounts.",
        "Create an AWSControlTowerBiueprintAccess role in the shared services account. F Create an AWSControlTowerBiueprintAccess role in each member account."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create an AWS CloudFormation template that describes the infrastructure that needs to be created in each account. Upload the template as an AWS Service Catalog product to the shared services account.||Deploy an Amazon EventBridge rule on a default event bus in the shared services account. Configure the EventBridge rule to react to AWS Control Tower CreateManagedAccount lifecycle events and to invoke the AWS Lambda function.",
        "code": "Question 121"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An online retail company is running a web application in the us-wast-2 Region and serves consumers in the United States. The company plans to expand across several countries in Europe and wants to provide low latency for all its users.\n\nThe application needs to identify the users’ IP addresses and provide localized content based on the users’ geographic location. The application uses HTTP GET and POST methods for its functionality. The company also needs to develop a failover mechanism that works for GET and POST methods and is based on health checks. The failover must occur in less than 1 minute for all clients.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure an Application Load Balancer (ALB) for the application in each environment in the new AWS Regions. Create an AWS Global Accelerator accelerator that has endpoint groups that point to the ALBs in each Region.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure a Network Load Balancer (NLB) for the application in each environment in the new AWS Regions. Create an AWS Global Accelerator accelerator that has endpoint groups that point to the NLBs in each Region.",
        "Configure an Application Load Balancer (ALB) for the application in each environment in the new AWS Regions. Create Amazon Route 53 public hosted zones that have failover routing policies.",
        "Configure a Network Load Balancer (NLB) for the application in each environment in the new AWS Regions. Create an Amazon CloudFront distribution. Configure an origin group with origin failover options."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 122"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has VPCs across 50 AWS accounts and is using AWS Organizations. The company wants to implement web filtering. The requirements for how the traffic must be filtered are the same for all the VPCs. A network engineer plans to use AWS Network Firewall. The network engineer needs to implement a solution that minimizes the number of firewall policies and rule groups that are necessary for this web filtering.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet these requirements? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create a firewall policy or rule group in the management account",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a firewall policy or rule group in each account.",
        "Use SCPs to share the firewall policy or rule group.",
        "Create OUs to share the firewall policy or rule group."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Use AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM) to share the firewall policy or rule group.||Enable sharing within Organizations.",
        "code": "Question 123"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company’s network engineer needs to design a new solution to help troubleshoot and detect network anomalies. The network engineer has configured Traffic Mirroring. However, the mirrored traffic is overwhelming the Amazon EC2 instance that is the traffic mirror target. The EC2 instance hosts tools that the company’s security team uses to analyze the traffic. The network engineer needs to design a highly available solution that can scale to meet the demand of the mirrored traffic.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy a Network Load Balancer (NLB) as the traffic mirror target. Behind the NLB. deploy a fleet of EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group. Use Traffic Mirroring as necessary.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy an Application Load Balancer (ALB) as the traffic mirror target. Behind the ALB, deploy a fleet of EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group. Use Traffic Mirroring only during non-business hours.",
        "Deploy a Gateway Load Balancer (GLB) as the traffic mirror target. Behind the GLB. deploy a fleet of EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group. Use Traffic Mirroring as necessary.",
        "Deploy an Application Load Balancer (ALB) with an HTTPS listener as the traffic mirror target. Behind the ALB. deploy a fleet of EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group. Use Traffic Mirroring only during active events or business hours."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 124"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an internal web-based application that employees use. The company hosts the application over a VPN in the company’s on-premises network. The application runs on a fleet of Amazon EC2 instances in a private subnet behind a Network Load Balancer (NLB) in the same subnet. The instances are in an Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling group.\n\nDuring a recent security incident, SQL injection occurred on the application. A network engineer must implement a solution to prevent SQL injection attacks in the future.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet these requirements? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create an AWS WAF web ACL that includes rules to block SQL injection attacks.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an Amazon CloudFront distribution. Specify the EC2 instances as the origin.",
        "Associate the AWS WAF web ACL with the NLB.",
        "Associate the AWS WAF web ACL with the Amazon CloudFront distribution."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Replace the NLB with an Application Load Balancer.||Associate the AWS WAF web ACL with the Application Load Balancer.",
        "code": "Question 125"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is running business applications on AWS. The company uses 50 AWS accounts, thousands of VPCs, and 3 AWS Regions across the United States and Europe.\n\nA network engineer needs to establish network connectivity between an on-premises data center and the Regions. The network engineer also must establish connectivity between the VPCs. On-premises: users and applications must be able to connect to applications that run in the VPCs.\n\nThe company has an existing AWS Direct Connect connection that the network engineer can use. The network engineer creates a transit gateway in each Region and configures the transit gateways as inter-Region peers.\n\nWhich solution will provide network connectivity from the on-premises data center to the Regions and will provide inter-VPC communications across the different Regions?",
      "correct_answer": "Create transit VIF with a gateway association to a new Direct Connect gateway. Associate each transit gateway with the new Direct Connect gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a private VIF with a gateway type of virtual private gateway. Configure the private VIF to use a virtual private gateway that is associated with one of the VPCs.",
        "Create a private VIF to a new Direct Connect gateway. Associate the new Direct Connect gateway with a virtual private gateway in each VPC.",
        "Create an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection that uses a public VIF for the Direct Connect connection. Attach the Site-to-Site VPN connection to the transit gateways."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 126"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has two data centers that are interconnected with multiple redundant links from different suppliers. The company Uses IP addresses that are within the 172.16,0.0/16 CIDR block. The company is running iBGP between the two data centers by using a private Autonomous System Number (ASN) and IGP.\n\nThe company is moving toward a hybrid setup in which the company will initially use one VPC in the AWS Cloud. An AWS Direct Connect connection runs from the first data center to a Direct Connect gateway by using a private VIF. On the connection, the company advertises a summarized route for the 172.16.0.0/16 network. The company is planning to set up a second summarized route from the second data center to a different Direct Connect location.\n\nThe company needs to implement a solution to route traffic to and from AWS through the first Direct Connect connection. The solution must use the second Direct Connect connection for failover purposes only.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Tag the BGP announcements with the local preference BGP community tags. Set the tag to high preference for the first data center. Set the tag to low preference for the second data center. Configure the second data center’s router to have a lower local preference for the direct AWS BGP advertisements than for the advertisement from the fist data center.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Prepend the private ASN on the BGP announcements to AWS from the second data center. Add a second VIF in the first Direct Connect connection. Advertise the same network without any prepends from the first data center. Implement the same setup for the BGP announcement from AWS to the two data centers.",
        "Configure the Direct Connect gateway to prefer routing through the Direct Connect connection with the first data center. Configure the second data center’s router to have a lower local preference for the direct AWS BGP advertisements than for the advertisement from the first data center.",
        "Configure the focal AWS Region BGP community tag on the BGP route that is advertised from the fist data center. Configure AS_PATH prepends on the BGP announcements from the second data center."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 127"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is replatforming a legacy data processing solution to AWS. The company deploys the solution on Amazon EC2 Instances in private subnets that are in one VPC.\n\nThe solution uses Amazon S3 for abject storage. Both the data that the solution processes and the data the solution produces are stored in Amazon S3. The solution uses Amazon DynamoDB to save its own state. The company collects flow logs for the VPC. The solution uses one NAT gateway to register its license through the internet. A software vendor provides a specific hostname so the solution can register its license.\n\nThe company notices that the AWS bill exceeds the projected budget for the solution. A network engineer uses AWS Cost Explorer to investigate the bill. The network engineer notices that the USE2-NatGateway-Bytes($) usage type is the root cause of the higher than expected bill.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to resolve the issue? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Examine the VPC flow logs to identity the traffic that traverses the NAT gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set up Amazon VPC Traffic Mirroring. Analyze the traffic to identify the traffic that the NAT gateway processes.",
        "Set up an AWS Cost and Usage Report in the AWS Billing and Cost Management console. Examine the report to find more details about the NAT gateway charges.",
        "Verify that the security groups attached to the EC2 instances allow outgoing traffic only to the IP addresses that the hostname resolves to, the VPC CIDR block, and the AWS IP address ranges for Amazon S3 and DynamoDB."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Verify that the gateway VPC endpoints for Amazon S3 and DynamoDB are both set up and associated with the route tables of the private subnets.",
        "code": "Question 128"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company ran out of IP address space in one of the Availability Zones in an AWS Region that the company uses. The Availability Zone that is out of space is assigned the 10.10.1.0/24 CIDR block. The company manages its networking configurations in an AWS CloudFormation stack. The company’ VPC is assigned the 10 10.0.0/16 CIDR block and has available capacity in the 10.10.1.0/22 CIDR block.\n\nHow should a network specialist add more IP address space in the existing VPC with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new AWS::EC2::Subnet resource for the Availability Zone in the CloudFormation stack. Set the CidrBlock property to 10.10.2.0/24.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Update the AWS::EC2::Subnet resource for the Availability Zone in the CloudFormation stack. Change the CidrBlock property to 10.10.1.0/22.",
        "Update the AWS::EC2::VPC resource in the CloudFormation stack. Change the CidrBlock property to 10.10.1.0/22.",
        "Copy the CloudFormation stack. Set the AWS::EC2::VPC resource CidrBlock property to 10.10.0.0/16. Set the AWS::EC2::Subnet resource CidrBlock property to 10.10.1.0/22 for the Availability Zone."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 129"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company’s network engineer must implement a cloud-based networking environment for a network operations team to centrally manage. Other Teams will use the environment. Each team must be able to deploy infrastructure to the environment and must be able to manage its own resources. The environment must feature IPv4 and IPv6 support and must provide internet connectivity in a dual-stack configuration.\n\nThe company has an organization in AWS Organizations that contains a workload account for the teams. The network engineer creates a new networking account in the organization.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network engineer take next to meet the requirements? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new VPC. Associate an IPv4 CIDR block of 10.0.0.0/16 and use an Amazon-provided IPV6 CIDR block. Provision subnets by assigning /24 IPv4 CIDR blocks and /64 IPV6 CIDR blocks.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new VPC. Associate an IPv4 CIDR block of 10.0.0.0/16 and specify an IPv6 block of 2001:db8:c5a:6000::/56. Provision subnets by assigning /24 IPv4 CIDR blocks and /64 IPv6 CIDR blocks.",
        "Enable sharing of resources within the organization by using AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM). Create a resource share in the networking account, select the new VPC, and share the new VPC with the target workload account. Use the workload account to accept the resource share through AWS RAM.",
        "Create an internet gateway. Deploy NAT instances to public subnets. Update the route tables. Associate the route tables with the relevant subnets."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Enable sharing of resources within the organization by using AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM). Create a resource share in the networking account, select the provisioned subnets, and share the provisioned subnets with the target workload account. Use the workload account to accept the resource share through AWS RAM.||Create an internet gateway and an egress-only internal gateway. Deploy NAT gateways to the public subnets. Associate the internet gateway with the new VPC. Update the route tables. Associate the route tables with the relevant subnets.",
        "code": "Question 130"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using third-party firewall appliances to monitor and inspect traffic on premises. The company wants to use the same model on AWS. The Company has a single VPC with an internet gateway. The VPC has a fleet of web servers that run on Amazon EC2 instances that are managed by an Auto Scaling group.\n\nThe company’s network team needs to work with the security team to establish inline inspection of all packets that are sent to and from the web servers. The solution must scale as the fleet of virtual firewall appliances scales\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network team take to implement this solution? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new VPC, and deploy a fleet of firewall appliances. Create a Gateway Load Balancer. Add the firewall appliances as targets.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a security group for use with the firewall appliances, and allow port 443. Allow a port for the Galeway Load Balancer to perform health checks.",
        "Deploy a fleet of firewall appliances to the existing VPC. Create a Gateway Load Balancer. Add the firewall appliances as targets.",
        "Create a new route table inside the web server VPC. Create a new edge association with the internet gateway. Update the internet gateway route table and the web server route table to send traffic to and from the internet to the VPC endpoint ID of the Gateway Load Balancer. Update the subnet route table that is associated with the Gateway Load Balancer endpoint to direct internet traffic to the internet gateway."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create a security group for use with the firewall appliances, and allow port 6081. Allow a port for the Gateway Load Balancer to perform health checks.||Update the internet gateway route table and the web server route table to send traffic to and from the internet to the VPC endpoint ID of the Gateway Load Balancer. Update the subnet route table that is associated with the Gateway Load Balancer endpoint to direct internet traffic to the internet gateway.",
        "code": "Question 131"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A financial company offers investment forecasts and recommendations to authorized users through the internet. All the services are hosted in the AWS Cloud. A new compliance requirement states that all the internet service traffic from any host must be logged and retained for 2 years. In its development AWS accounts, the company has designed, tested, and verified a solution that uses Amazon VPC Traffic Mirroring with a Network Load Balancer (NLB) as the traffic mirror target. While the solution runs in one AWS account, the solution mirrors the traffic to another AWS account.\n\nA network engineer notices that not all traffic is mirrored when the solution is deployed into the production environment. The network engineer also notices that this behavior is random.\n\nWhich statements are possible explanations for why not all the traffic is mirrored? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "The Amazon EC2 instance that is being monitored cannot handle the extra traffic that Traffic Mirroring has introduced.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The security groups are misconfigured on the production AWS account that hosts the company’s services.",
        "The IAM policy that allows the creation of traffic mirror sessions is misconfigured",
        "The NLB is experiencing warm-up delay because of sudden and significant increases in traffic."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "The mirrored traffic has a lower priority than the production traffic and is being dropped when network congestion occurs.",
        "code": "Question 132"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a VPC in the AWS Cloud. The company recently acquired a competitor that also has a VPC the AWS Cloud. A network engineer discovers an IP address overlap between the two VPCs. Both VPCs require access to an AWS Marketplace partner service.\n\nWhich solution will ensure interoperability among the VPC hosted services and the AWS Markelplace partner service?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure AWS PrivateLink to facilitate connectivity between the VPCs and the partner service. Use the DNS name that is created with the associated interface endpoints to route traffic between the VPCs and the partner service.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure VPC peering with static routing between the VPCs. Configure an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection with static routing to the partner service.",
        "Configure a NAT gateway in the VPCs. Configure default routes in each VPC to point to the local NAT gateway. Attach each NAT gateway to a transit gateway. Configure an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection with static routing to the partner service.",
        "Configure a NAT instance in the VPCs. Configure default routes in each VPC to point to the local NAT instance. Configure an interface endpoint in each VPC to connect to the partner service. Use the DNS name that is created with the associated interface endpoints to route traffic between the VPCs and the partner service."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 133"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses the us-east-1 Region and the ap-south-1 Region for its business units (BUs). The BUS are named BU-1 and BU-Z. For each BU, there are two VPCs in us-east-1 and one VPC in ap-south-1.\n\nBecause of workload isolation requirements, resources can communicate within the same BU but cannot communicate with resources in the other BU. The company plans to add more BUs and plans to expand into more Regions\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the MOST operational efficiency?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure an AWS Cloud WAN network that operates in the required Regions. Create AWS Cloud WAN segments for each BU Configure VPC attachments for each BU’s VPCs to the corresponding BU segment.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure an AWS Cloud WAN network that operates in the required Regions. Attach all BU VPCs to the AWS Cloud WAN core network. Update the AWS Cloud WAN segment actions to configure new routes to deny traffic between the different BU segments.",
        "Configure a transit gateway in each Region. Configure peering between the transit gateways. Attach the BU VPCs to the transit gateway in the corresponding Region. Configure the transit gateway and VPC route tables to isolate traffic between BU VPCs.",
        "Configure an AWS Cloud WAN network that operates in the required Regions. Attach all BU VPCs to the AWS Cloud WAN core network. Update the core network policy by setting the isolate-attachments parameter for each segment."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 134"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses a hybrid architecture and has an AWS Direct Connect connection between its on-premises data center and AWS. The company has production applications that run in the on-premises data center. The company also has production applications that run in a VPC. The applications that run in the on-premises data center need to communicate with the applications that run in the VPC. The company is using corp.example.com as the domain name for the on-premises resources and is using an Amazon Route 53 private hosted zone for aws.example.com to host the VPC resources.\n\nThe company is using an open-source recursive DNS resolver in a VPC subnet and is using a DNS resolver in the on-premises data center. The company's on-premises DNS resolver has a forwarder that directs requests for the aws.example.com domain name to the DNS resolver in the VPC. The DNS resolver in the VPC has a forwarder that directs requests for the corp.example.com domain name to the DNS resolver in the on-premises data center. The company has deckled to replace the open-source recursive DNS resolver with Amazon Route 53 Resolver endpoints.\n\nWhich combination of steps should a network engineer take to make this replacement? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Configure the on-premises DNS resolver to forward aws.example.com domain queries to the IP addresses of the inbound endpoint.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a Route 53 Resolver rule to forward aws.example.com domain queries to the IP addresses of the outbound endpoint.",
        "Create a Route 53 Resolver rule to forward aws.example.com domain queries to the IP addresses of the inbound endpoint.",
        "Configure the on-premises DNS resolver to forward aws.example.com queries to the IP addresses of the outbound endpoint."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create a Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint and a Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoint.||Create a Route 53 Resolver rule to forward corp.example.com domain queries to the IP address of the on-premises DNS resolver.",
        "code": "Question 135"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has many application VPCs that use AWS Site-to-Site VPN connections for connectivity to an on-premises location. The company’s network team wants to gradually migrate to AWS Transit Gateway to provide VPC-to-VPC connectivity.\n\nThe network team sets up a transit gateway that uses equal-cost multi-path (ECMP) routing. The network team attaches two temporary VPCs to the transit gateway for testing. The test VPCs contain Amazon EC2 instances to confirm connectivity over the transit gateway between the on-premises location and the VPCs. The network team creates two new Site-to-Site VPN connections to the transit gateway.\n\nDuring testing, the network team cannot reach the required bandwidth of 2.5 Gbps over the pair of new Site-o-Site VPN connections.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network team take to improve bandwidth performance and minimize network congestion? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create new accelerated Site-to-Site VPN connections to the transit gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Enable acceleration for the existing Site-to-Site VPN connections to the transit gateway.",
        "Advertise the on-premises prefix to AWS with a different BGP AS_PATH attribute across all the Site-to-Site VPN connections.",
        "Verify that the transit gateway attachments are present in the Availability Zones of the test VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Advertise the on-premises prefix to AWS with the same BGP AS_PATH attribute across all the Site-to-Site VPN connections.||Verify that the on-premises location is sending traffic by using multiple lows.",
        "code": "Question 136"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is migrating its on-premises network from its data center in Virginia to its data center in New York. The AWS Direct Connect connections for the Virginia and New York data center locations are both associated to the us-east-1 Region. The company needs to migrate a private VIF on an existing Direct Connect hosted connection from Virginia to New York. The company's on-premises network uses the connection to access VPCs through a Direct Connect gateway in us-east-1.\n\nThe company has already requested a new Direct Connect hosted connection from the new data center to the New York Direct Connect location.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST downtime?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new private VIF on the new Direct Connect hosted connection. Attach the new private VIF to the existing Direct Connect gateway. Configure BGP routing on the new private VIF as a backup route. Perform the switchover during a maintenance window by shutting down BGP on the existing private VIF. Decommission the existing Direct Connect connection.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new private VIF on the new Direct Connect hosted connection. Create a new Direct Connect gateway and attach the gateway to the new private VIF. Configure BGP routing on the new private VIF as a backup route. Perform the switchover during a maintenance window by shutting down BGP on the existing private VIF. Decommission the existing Direct Connect connection.",
        "During a maintenance window, migrate the existing private VIF to the new Direct Connect hosted connection. Attach the existing private VIF to the existing Direct Connect gateway. Decommission the existing Direct Connect connection.",
        "During a maintenance window, delete the existing private VIF and create a new private VIF to the new Direct Connect hosted connection. Attach the new private VIF to the existing Direct Connect gateway. Decommission the existing Direct Connect hosted connection."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 137"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A retail company is migrating its on-premises application to the AWS Cloud. Currently, the company has two on-premises data center locations. One data center is on the east coast of the United States, and one data center is on the west coast.\n\nEach data center hosts four database systems. The largest database system stores 500 GB of data. The data centers are interconnected by two 10 GbE circuits for data synchronization. Each data center has two separate 1 GbE upstream internet connections. The company plans to have eight total VPCs to service its multiple business units. Four VPCs will be in the us-east-1 Region, and four will be in the us-west-2 Region.\n\nA network engineer needs to design a connectivity solution that allows VPC-to-VPC connectivity. The solution must also allow secure connections between the on-premises data centers and AWS during the migration process. The company expects spikes in traffic among the VPCs during database synchronization. The company wants to run the migration plan during one weekend and as soon as technically possible. The company also wants to minimize long-term operational and human resources costs.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Provision two AWS Direct Connect connections from two Direct Connect locations that serve us-east-1 and us-west-2 to provide connectivity between the data centers and AWS.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy one transit gateway and attach all VPCs to it. Update the transit gateway and VPC route tables to allow any VPC to connect to any other VPC.",
        "Configure VPC peering between all the VPCs. Update the VPC route tables to allow connectivity.",
        "Provision one AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection for each data center and for each VPC to build connectivity between the on-premises data centers and AWS VPCs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Provision one transit gateway VPN attachment for each data center to build connectivity between the on-premises data centers and AWS VPCs.",
        "code": "Question 138"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is developing an API-based application on AWS for its process workflow requirements. The API will be invoked by clients in the company’s on-premises data centers. The company has set up an AWS Direct Connect connection between on premises and AWS. A network engineer decides to implement the API as a private REST API in Amazon API Gateway. The network engineer wants to ensure that clients can reach the API endpoint through private communication.\n\nWhich solution can the network engineer use to invoke the API without any additional infrastructure setup?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an interface VPC endpoint for API Gateway with private DNS names enabled. Access the API by using the public DNS name of the endpoint.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an interface VPC endpoint for API Gateway with private DNS names enabled. Access the API by using the private DNS name of the endpoint.",
        "Create an interface VPC endpoint for API Gateway with private DNS names enabled. Access the API by using an Amazon Route 53 alias of the endpoint.",
        "Create an interface VPC endpoint for API Gateway. Associate the endpoint with the private REST API, Access the API by using an Amazon Route 53 alias of the endpoint."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 139"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A banking company has an application that must connect to specific public IP addresses from a VPC. A network engineer has configured routes in the route table that is associated with the application’s subnet to the required public IP addresses through an internet gateway.\n\nThe network engineer needs to set up email notifications that will alert the network engineer when a user adds a default route to the application subnet's route table with the internet gateway as a target.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST implementation effort?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an AWS Config rule for the route table by using the no-unrestricted-route-to-igw managed rule. Create an Amazon EventBridge rule to match the AWS Config rule and to route to an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topic to send an email notification.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an AWS Lambda function that reads the routes in the route table and sends an email notification. Configure the Lambda function to send an email notification if any route is configured with 0.0.0.0/0 or ::/0 CIDRs to the internet gateway. Configure the Lambda function to run every minute.",
        "Create an AWS Lambda function that will be invoked by an Amazon EC2 CreateRoute API call. Configure the Lambda function to send an email notification. Configure the Lambda function to send an email notification if any route is configured with 0.0.0.0/0 or ::/0 CIDRs to the internet gateway.",
        "Create AWS Config rules for the route table by using the internet-gateway-authorized-vpc-only managed rule. Create an Amazon EventBridge rule to match the AWS Config rule and to route to an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topic to send an email notification."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 140"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building an internet-facing application that is hosted on an Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) cluster. The company is using the Amazon VPC Container Network Interface (CNI) plugin for Kubernetes for pod networking connectivity. The company needs to expose its application to the internet by using a Network Load Balancer (NLB).\n\nThe pods that host the application must have visibility of the source IP address that is contained in the original packet that the NLB receives.\n\nHow should the network engineer configure the NLB and Amazon EKS settings to achieve these goals?",
      "correct_answer": "Specify the ip target type for the NLB. Set the externalTrafficPolicy attribute to Local in the Kubernetes service specification.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Specify the instance target type for the NLSet the externalTrafficPolicy attribute to Cluster in the Kubernetes service specification.",
        "Specify the instance target type for the NLB. Set the externalTrafficPolicy attribute to Local in the Kubernetes service specification.",
        "Specify the ip target type for the NLB. Set the externalTrafficPolicy attribute to Cluster in the Kubernetes service specification."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 141"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is running its application servers on Amazon EC2 instances. The EC2 instances run in separate VPCs that are connected by a transit gateway. The EC2 instances launch in a private subnet with a route to the transit gateway for internal and external connectivity. The external connectivity is provided by a VPC with firewall devices that perform an inspection for packets that ingress and egress through an internet gateway.\n\nA network engineer needs to help the company’s application team increase the payload size per packet delivery between the EC2 instances. All network connectivity must be through the transit gateway\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Instruct the application team to set the maximum transmission unit (MTU) of the system’s network interfaces to 8500 bytes.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Enable jumbo frames on the transit gateway. Instruct the application team to set the maximum transmission unit (MTU) of the system’s network interfaces to 9001 bytes.",
        "Instruct the application team to set the maximum transmission unit (MTU) of the VPC to 8500 bytes.",
        "Instruct the application team to set up enhanced networking on the system by using the enhanced networking adapter. Set the maximum transmission unit (MTU) to 9001 bytes."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 142"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer needs to monitor internet metrics for an application that is in a VPC. The metrics include user experiences such as health events, latency, and traffic insights.\n\nThe network engineer sets up Amazon CloudWatch Internet Monitor for the application. The engineer wants to push the internet health events to a third-party target.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST implementation effort?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a third-party API endpoint in Amazon EventBridge. Create a rule in EventBridge that uses Internet Monitor as the source and the third-party API endpoint in EventBridge as the destination.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a third-party API endpoint in Amazon EventBridge. Configure internet Monitor to send the events to the third-party API endpoint in EventBridge.",
        "Create a third-party API endpoint in internet Monitor. Configure Internet Monitor to send the events to an Amazon S3 bucket. Configure an AWS Lambda function to send the events to the third-party API endpoint in Internet Monitor.",
        "Create a third-party API endpoint in Internet Monitor. Configure Internet Monitor to send the events to the third-party API endpoint in Internet Monitor."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 143"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a web application that runs in eight AWS Regions. In each Region, the application is hosted on multiple compute resources behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB).\n\nThe different Regions are using different domains. Each ALB is configured to accept only HTTPS traffic. Each ALB uses a certificate from AWS Certificate Manager (ACM).\n\nThe company wants to simplify the application’s appearance on the web by using a new single domain for all Regions. A network engineer needs to implement this change by designing a solution that also will minimize latency for the application's end users.\n\nWhich combination of actions will meet these requirements? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create an alias record for the accelerator in Amazon Route 53 for the new domain.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use ACM to create an SSL/TLS certificate in the us-east-1 Region for the new domain.",
        "Set up latency-based routing in Amazon Route 53 for the new domain. Add the ALBs from all the Regions as targets.",
        "Create a custom routing accelerator in AWS Global Accelerator. Configure a listener for HTTPS traffic. Add all the ALBs as targets for the listener. Configure the accelerator to terminate TLS by using the SSLITLS certificate from ACM."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create a standard accelerator in AWS Global Accelerator. Configure a listener for TCP traffic. Add all the ALBs as targets for the listener.||Use ACM to create an SSLITLS certificate for each Region. Configure all the ALBs to use the certificate in their respective Regions.",
        "code": "Question 144"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a VPC that includes application workloads that run on Amazon EC2 instances in a single AWS Region. The company wants to use AWS Local Zones to deploy an extension of the application workloads that run in the Region. The extended workloads in the Local Zone need to communicate bidirectionally with the workloads in the VPC in the Region.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new subnet in the Local Zone. Configure the new subnet to use a CIDR block that is within the VPC’s CIDR block. Deploy instances in the new subnet in the Local Zone.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new VPC in the Local Zone. Attach all the VPCs to a transit gateway. Configure routing for the transit gateway and the VPCs. Deploy instances in the new VPC.",
        "Deploy a third-party appliance in a new VPC in the Region. Create a new VPC in the Local Zone. Create VPN connections to the appliance for the VPCs. Deploy instances in the new VPC in the Local Zone.",
        "Create a new subnet in the Local Zone. Deploy a third-party appliance in the VPC with interfaces in each subnet. Configure the new subnet to route the Local Zone through the appliance. Deploy instances in the new subnet."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 145"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A government contractor is designing a multi-account environment with multiple VPCs for a customer. A network security policy requires all traffic between any two VPCs to be transparently inspected by a third-party appliance.\n\nThe customer wants a solution that features AWS Transit Gateway. The setup must be highly available across multiple Availability Zones, and the solution needs to support automated failover. Furthermore, asymmetric routing is not supported by the inspection appliances.\n\nWhich combination of steps is part of a solution that meets these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy two clusters that consist of multiple appliances across multiple Availability Zones in a designated inspection VPC. Connect the inspection VPC to the transit gateway by using a VPC attachment. Create a target group, and register the appliances with the target group. Create a Gateway Load Balancer, and set it up to forward to the newly created target group. Configure a default route in the inspection VPC’s transit gateway subnet toward the Gateway Load Balancer endpoint.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy two clusters that consist of multiple appliances across multiple Availability Zones in a designated inspection VPC. Connect the inspection VPC to the transit gateway by using a VPC attachment. Create a target group, and register the appliances with the target group. Create a Network Load Balancer (NLB), and set it up to forward to the newly created target group. Configure a default route in the inspection VPCs transit gateway subnet toward the NLB.",
        "Configure two route tables on the transit gateway. Associate one route table with all the attachments of the application VPCs. Associate the other route table with the inspection VPCs attachment. Propagate all VPC attachments into the application route table. Define a static default route in the inspection route table. Enable appliance mode on the attachment that connects the inspection VPC.",
        "Configure one route table on the transit gateway. Associate the route table with all the VPCs. Propagate all VPC attachments into the route table. Define a static default route in the route table."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Configure two route tables on the transit gateway. Associate one route table with all the attachments of the application VPCs. Associate the other route table with the inspection VPC’s attachment. Propagate all VPC attachments into the inspection route table. Define a static default route in the application route table. Enable appliance mode on the attachment that connects the inspection VPC.",
        "code": "Question 146"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using AWS Cloud WAN with one edge location in the us-east-1 Region and one edge location in the us-west-1 Region. A shared services segment exists at both edge locations. Each shared services segment has a VPC attachment to each inspection VPC in each Region. The inspection VPCs inspect traffic from a WAN by using AWS Network Firewall.\n\nThe company creates a new segment for a new business unit (BU) in the us-east-1 edge location. The new BU has three VPCs that are attached to the new BU segment. To comply with regulations, the BU VPCs must not communicate with each other. All internet-bound traffic must be inspected in the inspection VPC.\n\nThe company updates VPC route tables so any traffic that is bound for internet goes to the AWS Cloud WAN core network.\n\nThe company plans to add more VPCs for the new BU in the future. All future VPCs must comply with regulations.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements in the MOST operationally efficient way? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create a network policy to share the inspection service segment with the BU segment.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Update the network policy to share the shared services segment with the BU segment.",
        "Set the isolate-attachments field to False for the BU segment.",
        "Update the network policy to add static routes for the BU segment. Configure the shared services segment to route traffic related to VPC CIDR blocks to each respective VPC attachment."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Set the isolate-attachments field to True for the BU segment.",
        "code": "Question 147"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company hosts a highly available, scalable, and resilient application on Amazon EC2 instances that are part of an Auto Scaling group. A network engineer is planning to integrate IPv6 support with the application deployment in phases. The first phase is to enable IPv6 service consumption on the public Network Load Balancers (NLBs) that are deployed across the infrastructure. The target groups for the NLBS are configured as the Auto Scaling groups of the EC2 instances that host the application. The NLBs are configured for dual-stack operation.\n\nDuring the testing of the first phase, the IPv6 application queries are not reaching the backend servers.\n\nWhat is the cause of this issue?",
      "correct_answer": "The subnets where the EC2 instances are deployed do not have IPv6 addresses configured.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The route tables for the NLB subnets do not have IPV6 routing configured.",
        "The route tables for the EC2 subnets do not have IPV6 routing configured.",
        "The security groups that are associated with the NLBs do not allow IPv6 traffic."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 148"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to implement a distributed architecture on AWS that uses a Gateway Load Balancer (GWLB) and GWLB endpoints.\n\nThe company has chosen a hub-and-spoke model. The model includes a GWLB and virtual appliances that are deployed into a centralized appliance VPC and GWLB endpoints. The model also includes internet gateways that are configured in spoke VPCs.\n\nWhich sequence of traffic flow to the internet from the spoke VPC is correct?",
      "correct_answer": "1. An application in a spoke VPC sends traffic to the GWLB endpoint based on the VPC route table configuration. 2. Traffic is delivered securely and privately to the GWLB. 3. The GWLB sends the traffic to a virtual appliance for inspection. 4. Return traffic flows back to the GWLB endpoint and out to the internet through the internet gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1. An application in a spoke VPC sends traffic to the GWLB endpoint based on the VPC route table configuration. 2. Traffic is delivered securely and privately to the GWLB endpoint. 3. The GWLB sets the X-Forwarded-For request header and sends the traffic to a virtual appliance for inspection. 4. Return traffic flows back to the GWLB and out to the internet through an internet gateway.",
        "1. An application in a spoke VPC sends traffic to the GWLB endpoint. 2. Traffic is delivered securely and privately to the GWLB. 3. The GWLB sets the X-Forwarded-For request header and sends the traffic to a virtual appliance for inspection. 4. Return traffic flows back to the GWLB endpoint and out to the internet through the internet gateway.",
        "1. An application in a spoke VPC sends traffic to the GWLB. 2. Traffic is delivered securely and privately to the GWLB endpoint. 3. The GWLB sends the traffic to a virtual appliance for inspection. 4. Return traffic flows back to the GWLB and out to the internet through an internet gateway."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 149"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer needs to provide a list of IP addresses that are sending traffic to an Amazon EC2 instance. VPC flow logs are enabled. The EC2 instance has a single network interface and two assigned IP addresses. However, the flow logs are logging traffic only for the primary IP address. The network engineer needs to determine whether any traffic is being sent to the second IP address of the EC2 instance.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to locate the traffic flow for the second IP address?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new flow log that includes the pkt-dstaddr field to capture the original destination IP address of the traffic.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new flow log that includes the dstaddr field to capture the original destination IP address of the traffic.",
        "Create a new flow log that includes the pkt-srcaddr field to capture the original destination IP address of the traffic.",
        "Create a new flow log that includes the srcaddr field to capture the original destination IP address of the traffic."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 150"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has configured an AWS Cloud WAN core network with edge locations in the us-east-1 Region and the us-west-1 Region. Each edge location has two segments: development and staging. The segments use the default core network policy.\n\nThe company has attached VPCs to the core network. A development VPC is attached to the development segment in us-east-1 and is configured to use the 10.0.0.0/16 CIDR block. A staging VPC is attached to the staging segment in us-west-1 and is configured to use the 10.5.0.0/16 CIDR block. The company has updated the route tables for both VPCs with a route that directs any traffic for 0.0.0.0/0 to the core network.\n\nThe company’s network team needs to establish communication between the two VPCs by using the AWS Cloud WAN core network. The network team is not receiving a response during tests of communication between the VPCs. The network team has verified that security groups and network ACLs are not blocking the traffic.\n\nWhat should the network team do to establish this communication?",
      "correct_answer": "Update the core network policy to add a static route for each segment. Configure a route to direct the traffic for 10.0.0.0/16 to the development VPC attachment. Configure a route to direct the traffic for 10.5.0.0/16 to the staging VPC attachment.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Update both VPC route tables to have a new static route. Configure a route on the development VPC to direct the traffic for 10.0.0.0/16 to the development VPC attachment. Configure a route on the staging VPC to direct the traffic for 10.5.0.0/16 to the staging VPC attachment.",
        "Update the segment filter to allow traffic on the development and staging segments.",
        "Set the isolate-attachments parameter to False for the development and staging segments."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 151"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has VPCs in the us-east-1 Region that are connected to each other through a transit gateway. A network engineer needs to establish an AWS Direct Connect connection between the company's on-premises data center and the transit gateway for the migration of a workload.\n\nThe Direct Connect connection is UP according to the ConnectionState metric in Amazon CloudWatch. However, the VIF is DOWN. The network engineer has verified the transit VIF and BGP configurations on the on-premises router and has found no issues. However, the network engineer is unable to ping the Amazon peer IP address.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network engineer take to troubleshoot this issue? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Verify that the correct IP address and subnet mask are in use for the subinterface on the router.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ensure that VLAN trunking is disabled on the router.",
        "Verify that the optical signal that is received over the cross connect is optimal.",
        "Ensure that TCP port 179 is not being blocked at the on-premises router."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Verify that the router has a MAC address entry from the AWS endpoint in the Address Resolution Protocol (ARP) table.||Ensure that the correct VLAN tag is applied on the subinterface configuration on the router.",
        "code": "Question 152"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A logistics company has multiple VPCs in an AWS Region. The company uses a transit gateway to connect the VPCs. The company has several on-premises offices that connect to the transit gateway by using AWS Site-to-Site VPN connections over the internet. The company has configured one transit gateway VPN attachment for each office.\n\nRoute propagation is enabled on all route tables. Each Site-to-Site VPN connection uses two tunnels in an active-passive configuration. The company configured each office with appropriate static routes on both the Site-to-Site VPN connection and the office’s customer gateway.\n\nThe company wants to use both IPsec tunnels of every office to maximize the overall VPN connection bandwidth.\n\nWhich design changes are necessary to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Enable equal-cost multi-path (ECMP) routing on the transit gateway. (Ensure ECMP is supported by and enabled on the customer gateways. Change the routing configuration between the transit gateway and the customer gateways from static routing to BGP. Remove related static routes from the customer gateways.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an AWS Transit Gateway Connect attachment for each office Use the existing VPN attachments as the transport for the new Connect attachments. Set up a Generic Routing Encapsulation (GRE) tunnel on each customer gateway that terminates on the Connect attachment for each office. Move the static routes from the transit gateway VPN attachment to the customer gateway for the transit gateway Connect attachment.",
        "Enable equal-cost multi-path (ECMP) routing on the transit gateway. Ensure ECMP is supported by and enabled on the customer gateways. Enable ECMP on the Site-to-Site VPN connection. Ensure static routes on the customer gateways have equal metrics and administrative distance.",
        "Enable equal-cost multi-path (ECMP) routing on the transit gateway. Ensure ECMP is supported by and enabled on the customer gateways. Change the routing configuration between the transit gateway and the customer gateways from static routing to BGP. Ensure the customer gateway applies the correct community strings to give the transit gateway the ability to perform ECMP forwarding."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 153"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A finance company runs multiple applications on Amazon EC2 instances in two VPCs that are within a single AWS Region. The company uses one VPC for stock trading applications. The company uses the second VPC for financial applications. Both VPCs are connected to a transit gateway that is configured as a multicast router.\n\nIn the stock trading VPC, an EC2 instance that has an IP address of 10.128.10.2 sends trading data over a multicast network to the 239.10.10.10 IP address on UDP Port 5102. The company recently launched two new EC2 instances in the financial application VPC. The new EC2 instances need to receive the multicast stock trading data from the EC2 instance that is in the stock trading VPC.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the company take to meet this requirement? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Add the elastic network interfaces of the two new EC2 instances as members of the multicast group by using the group IP address of 239.10.10.10.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Add an inbound rule to the security groups that are attached to the multicast receiver instances. Configure the rule as follows: Protocol: IGMP Version 2. Port: 5102, and Source: 239 10.10.10/32",
        "Create associations to two EC2 instance IDs on the financial application VPC transit gateway attachment under the transit gateway multicast domain.",
        "Add an inbound rule to the security groups that are attached to the multicast receiver instances. Configure the rule as follows. Protocol: UDP, Port: 5102, and Source: 10.128.10.2/32"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create an association to EC2 instance subnets on the financial application VPC transit gateway attachment under the transit gateway multicast domain. D. Add an inbound rule to the security groups that are attached to the multicast receiver instances. Configure the rule as follows: Protocol: IGMP Version 2. Port: All, and Source: 0 0.0.0/32",
        "code": "Question 154"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company runs workloads in multiple VPCs in the us-east-1 Region. The VPCs are connected to a transit gateway. An AWS Direct Connect connection provides private connectivity between a data center that is in the US and the transit gateway. A Direct Connect gateway is associated with the transit gateway.\n\nThe company has recently opened a new office location in London. The company plans to launch cloud services in multiple VPCs in the eu-west-2 Region. Users in the new London office must have private access to the workloads that run in us-east-1. Users in the US data center must have access to any workloads that are created in eu-west-2. A network engineer must implement a flexible solution that provides users the required access. The solution must be able to accommodate future growth.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST operational effort?",
      "correct_answer": "Establish a new Direct Connect connection for the London office. Attach the new Direct Connect connection to the existing Direct Connect gateway. Create a transit gateway in eu-west-2. Associate the new transit gateway with the existing Direct Connect gateway. Create a peering connection between the transit gateways in us-east-1 and eu-west-2.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection from the London office to the Direct Connect gateway in us-east-1.",
        "Create an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection from the London office to each of the VPCs that are in us-east-1.",
        "Establish a new AWS Direct Connect connection for the London office Create a new Direct Connect gateway and a transit gateway in eu-west-2. Attach the new Direct Connect connection to the new Direct Connect gateway. Create a peering connection between the transit gateways in us-east-1 and eu-west-2."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 155"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has 10 Amazon EC2 instances that run web server software in a production VPC. The company also has 10 web servers that run in an on-premises data center. The company has a 10 Gbps AWS Direct Connect connection between the on-premises data center and the production VPC. The data center uses the 10.100.0.0/20 CIDR block.\n\nThe company needs to implement a load balancing solution that receives HTTPS traffic from thousands of external users. The solution must distribute the traffic across the web servers on AWS and the web servers in the data center. Regardless of the location of the web servers, HTTPS requests must go to the same web server for the duration of the session.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy an Application Load Balancer (ALB) in the production VPC. Create one target group for the EC2 Instances and a second target group for the on-premises servers. Specify IP as the target type. Register the EC2 instances and the on-premises servers with the target groups. Enable application-based sticky sessions on the ALB.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy a Network Load Balancer (NLB) in the production VPC. Create one target group for the EC2 Instances and a second target group for the on-premises servers. Specify IP as the target type. Register the EC2 instances and the on-premises servers with the target groups. Enable connection draining on the NLB.",
        "Deploy a Network Load Balancer (NLB) in the production VPCreate one target group for the EC2 Instances and a second target group for the on-premises servers. Specify instance as the target type. Register the EC2 instances and the on-premises servers with the target groups. Enable sticky sessions on the NLB.",
        "Deploy an Application Load Balancer (ALB) in the production VPC. Create one target group for the EC2 Instances and a second target group for the on-premises servers. Specify instance as the target type. Register the EC2 instances and the on-premises servers with the target groups. Enable application-based sticky sessions on the ALB."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 156"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has deployed Amazon EC2 instances in private subnets in a VPC. The EC2 instances must initiate any requests that leave the VPC, including requests to the company's on-premises data center over an AWS Direct Connect connection. No resources outside the VPC can be allowed to open communications directly to the EC2 instances.\n\nThe on-premises data center's customer gateway is configured with a stateful firewall device that filters for incoming and outgoing requests to and from multiple VPCs. In addition, the company wants to use a single IP match rule to allow all the communications from the EC2 instances to its data center from a single IP address.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST amount of operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy a NAT gateway into a private subnet in the VPC where the EC2 instances are deployed. Specify the NAT gateway type as private. Configure the on-premises firewall to allow connections from the IP address that is assigned to the NAT gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a VPN connection over the Direct Connect connection by using the on-premises firewall. Use the firewall to block all traffic from on premises to AWS. Allow a stateful connection from the EC2 instances to initiate the requests.",
        "Configure the on-premises firewall to filter all requests from the on-premises network to the EC2 instances. Allow a stateful connection if the EC2 instances in the VPC initiate the traffic.",
        "Deploy a NAT instance into a private subnet in the VPC where the EC2 instances are deployed. Configure the on-premises firewall to allow connections from the IP address that is assigned to the NAT instance."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 157"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A global company is establishing network connections between the company's primary and secondary data centers and a VPC. A network engineer needs to maximize resiliency and fault tolerance for the connections. The network bandwidth must be greater than 10 Gbps.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Set up two 10 Gbps connections at the primary data center that terminate at one AWS Direct Connect location. Ensure the connections are managed by separate providers. Set up two 10 Gbps connections at the secondary data center that terminate at a second Direct Connect location. Ensure the connections are managed by separate providers.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set up a 100 Gbps connection at the primary data center that terminates at an AWS Direct Connect location. Set up a second 100 Gbps connection at the secondary data center that terminates at a second Direct Connect location. Ensure the connections are managed by separate providers.",
        "Set up a 10 Gbps connection at the primary data center that terminates at an AWS Direct Connect location. Set up a second 10 Gbps connection at the secondary data center that terminates at a second Direct Connect location. Ensure the connections are managed by separate providers.",
        "Set up a 10 Gbps connection at the primary data center that terminates at an AWS Direct Connect location. Set up an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection at the secondary data center that terminates at a virtual private gateway in the same Region as the company’s VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 158"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company’s data center is connected to a single AWS Region by an AWS Direct Connect dedicated connection. The company has a single VPC in the Region. The company stores logs for all its applications locally in the data center.\n\nThe company must keep all application logs for 7 years. The company decides to copy all application logs to an Amazon S3 bucket.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a private VIF on the Direct Connect connection. Create an Amazon S3 interface endpoint in the VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a public VIF on the Direct Connect connection. Create an Amazon S3 gateway endpoint in the VPC.",
        "Create a private VIF on the Direct Connect connection. Create an Amazon S3 gateway endpoint in the VPC.",
        "Create a public VIF on the Direct Connect connection. Create an Amazon S3 interface endpoint in the VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 159"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to host a secure web application across multiple Amazon EC2 instances. The application will have an associated DNS domain in an Amazon Route 53 hosted zone.\n\nThe company wants to protect the domain from DNS poisoning attacks. The company also wants to allow web browsers to authenticate into the application by using a trusted third party.\n\nWhich combination of actions will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure the Route 53 hosted zone to use DNS Security Extensions (DNSSEC). Install X.509 certificates that are signed by a public certificate authority on the EC2 instances.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure the Route 53 hosted zone to use DNS Security Extensions (DNSSEC). Install self-signed X.509 certificates on the EC2 instances.",
        "Configure a Name Authority Pointer (NAPTR) record in the Route 53 hosted zone. Install X 509 certificates that are signed by a public certificate authority on the EC2 instances.",
        "Configure a Name Authority Pointer (NAPTR) record in the Route 53 hosted zone. Install self-signed X.509 certificates on the EC2 instances."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 160"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to use an AWS Transit Gateway hub and spoke architecture to migrate to AWS. The current on-premises multi-protocol label switching (MPLS) network has strict controls that enforce network segmentation by using MPLS VPNs. The company has provisioned two 10 Gbps AWS Direct Connect connections to provide resilient, high-speed, low-latency connectivity to AWS.\n\nA security engineer needs to apply the concept of network segmentation to the AWS environment to ensure that virtual routing and forwarding (VRF) is logically separated for each of the company's software development environments. The number of MPLS VPNs will increase in the future. On-premises MPLS VPNs will have overlapping address space. The company's AWS network design must support overlapping address space for the VPNs.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure a Transit Gateway Connect attachment for each MPLS VPN between the company's edge routers and Transit Gateway. Configure a transit gateway route table that matches the MPLS VPN for each of the company's development environments.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy a software-defined WAN (SD-WAN) head-end virtual appliance and an SD-WAN controller into a Transit Gateway Connect VPC. Configure the company's edge routers to be managed by the new SD-WAN controller and to use SD-WAN to segment the traffic into the defined segments for each of the company's development environments.",
        "Configure IPsec VPNs on the company edge routers for each MPLS VPN for each of the company's development environments. Attach each IPsec VPN tunnel to a discrete MPLS VPN. Configure AWS Site-to-Site VPN connections that terminate at a transit gateway for each MPLS VPN. Configure a transit gateway route table that matches the MPLS VPN for each Transit Gateway VPN attachment.",
        "Create a transit VPC that terminates at the AWS Site-to-Site VRF-aware IPsec VPN. Configure IPsec VPN connections to each VPC for each of the company's development environment VRFs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 161"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to migrate to AWS and use multiple VPCs in multiple AWS Regions. A network engineer must connect the eu-west-1 and eu-central-1 Regions to the company headquarters and branch office, respectively.\n\nThe network engineer created a production VPC, named Prod A, with a CIDR block of 10.0.0.0/16. Prod A runs in an account in eu-west-1. The network engineer then created another production VPC, named Prod B, with a CIDR block of 10.1.0.0/16. Prod В runs in a different account in eu-central-1.\n\nThe network engineer performed the following steps to try to achieve the required connectivity:\n\n1. Created one transit gateway in each Region\n\n2. Shared and accepted the transit gateways with the production accounts in both Regions\n\n3. Configured the peering attachment between both transit gateways\n\n4. Attached both VPCs to the respective Region transit gateway\n\n5. Created both transit gateway route tables and associated the attachments with the route tables\n\n6. Configured a static route in both transit gateway route tables to send traffic to the remote VPC in the other Region\n\n7. Activated route propagation on the VPC route tables in each Region\n\nAfter the configuration, the network engineer tried to connect from Prod A to Prod B. However, the connection was unsuccessful.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to achieve the required connectivity?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new route destined to 10.0.0.0/8 in both production VPC route tables with the Region transit gateway as the target.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Modify the IP address of the peering attachment to a wider range.",
        "Delete the static routes that were in the transit gateway route table to send traffic to the remote VPC and enable route propagation instead.",
        "Modify the transit gateway route tables from the production accounts to propagate routes dynamically between the production VPCs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 162"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company hosts an application on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). The instances are part of an Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling group.\n\nTo comply with new security standards, the company must capture all application access data, including server response codes, request paths, latency, and client IP addresses. The company also needs to query the captured data for performance analysis.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Enable access logs on the ALB. Store the logs in an Amazon S3 bucket. Query the logs in the S3 bucket by using Amazon Athena.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Enable VPC flow logs on the ALB subnets. Store the logs to an Amazon S3 bucket. Query the logs in the S3 bucket by using Amazon Athena.",
        "Configure Amazon VPC Traffic Mirroring on all EC2 elastic network interfaces. Deploy a third-party monitoring appliance from AWS Marketplace in a private subnet. Use Amazon Data Firehose to send all mirrored traffic to the monitoring appliance. Query the logs directly from the monitoring appliance.",
        "Configure Amazon CloudWatch detailed monitoring on the EC2 instances Include all available logs. Use Amazon Data Firehose to send all the collected logs to an Amazon S3 bucket. Query the data directly from the S3 bucket."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 163"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has five VPCs in the us-east-1 Region. The company hosts an internal web application in us-east-1. One of the company's VPCs. named VPC-A, needs to connect to an external partner's AWS environment. The partner’s environment is in the same AWS Region where the partner hosts a new version of the company's web application. The partner hosts its version of the application in a VPC named VPC-B.\n\nThe company has Amazon EC2 instances in VPC-A that need to connect to the web application in VPC-B A network engineer notices that the partner's VPC-B and the company's VPC-A use the same IP space. The network engineer needs a solution to allow the EC2 instances to connect to the web application. The solution must not negatively affect the exiting environment of the company or the partner.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network engineer take meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Ensure the partner creates a VPC endpoint service that uses a Network Load Balancer in VPC-B.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Establish a VPC peering connection between VPC-A to VPC-B.",
        "Deploy a new routable VPC CIDR block as a secondary CIDR block to both VPC-A and VPC-B. Deploy a public NAT gateway in VPC-A.",
        "Establish an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection between VPC-A and VPC-B."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Deploy a VPC endpoint in VPC-A that uses a VPC endpoint service that is shared by the partner.",
        "code": "Question 164"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a hybrid environment that connects an on-premises data center to the AWS Cloud. The hybrid environment uses a 10 Gbps AWS Direct Connect dedicated connection. The Direct Connect connection has multiple private VIFs that terminate in multiple VPCs.\n\nTo comply with regulations, the company must encrypt all WAN traffic, regardless of the underlying transport. The company needs to implement an encryption solution that will not affect the company's bandwidth capacity.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure a new Direct Connect connection that supports MAC security (MACSec) Associate the existing VIFs to the new Direct Connect connection.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a public VIF. Configure a new AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection to use the new public VIF.",
        "Configure MAC security (MACsec) support on the port of the existing Direct Connect connection. Change the encryption mode to must_encrypt.",
        "Create a public VIF. Configure a new private IP VPN that uses the Direct Connect connection."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 165"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to capture and log traffic for Nitro-based Amazon EC2 instances to comply with regulations. The company's network team has prepared a solution that enables VPC traffic mirroring and sends traffic to a second set of EC2 instances in an Auto Scaling group.\n\nThe network team has added a Network Load Balancer (NLB) in front of the EC2 instances the traffic will be sent to. However, the solution does not send any mirrored traffic to the EC2 instances that are behind the NLB.\n\nHow should the network team configure traffic mirroring to use the NLB endpoint?",
      "correct_answer": "Select the NLB as a target for traffic mirroring. Use a UDP listener.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Select the NLB as a source for traffic mirroring. Use a UDP listener.",
        "Select the NLB as a target for traffic mirroring. Use a TCP listener and a UDP listener.",
        "Select the NLB as a target for traffic mirroring. Use a TCP listener."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 166"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A US-based company is expanding its business to Europe. A network engineer needs to extend the company's network infrastructure by setting up a new hub and spoke architecture in the eu-west-1 Region. The network engineer uses a transit gateway peering connection to connect the new resources in eu-west-1 to an existing environment in the us-east-1 Region.\n\nThe hub and spoke architecture in each AWS Region includes an inspection VPC that uses AWS Network Firewall to centralize traffic inspection for each Region. To reduce costs, the network engineer decides to inspect inter-Region traffic by using the inspection VPC in the Region that originates the traffic. The network engineer configures the transit gateway route tables accordingly for each Region.\n\nWhen the network engineer tests the new architecture, communication within each Region works as expected. However, the network engineer finds that inter-Region communication is not working. The network engineer must resolve the inter-Region communication issue.\n\nWhich solution will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Enable Appliance mode on both the transit gateway attachments for the inspection VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure Open Shortest Path First (OSPF) routing on the transit gateway peering connection to propagate the VPC CIDR blocks from each Region to the remote peer.",
        "Use AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM) to share access between the transit gateways. Enable the Allow sharing with anyone setting.",
        "Prevent asymmetric routing in the inspection VPCs by ensuring that both requests and responses are inspected by the same inspection VPC"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 167"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A global company operates all its non-production environments out of three AWS Regions: eu-west-1, us-east-1, and us-west-1. The company hosts all its production workloads in two on-premises data centers. The company has 60 AWS accounts and each account has two VPCs in each Region. Each VPC has a virtual private gateway where two VPN connections terminate for resilient connectivity to the data centers. The company has 360 VPN tunnels to each data center, resulting in high management overhead. The total VPN throughput for each Region is 500 Mbps.\n\nThe company wants to migrate the production environments to AWS. The company needs a solution that will simplify the network architecture and allow for future growth. The production environments will generate an additional 2 Gbps of traffic per Region back to the data centers. This traffic will increase over time.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a transit gateway in each Region with multiple newly commissioned VPN connections from each data center. Share the transit gateways with each account by using AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM). In each Region, attach the transit gateway to each VPRemove the existing VPN connections that are attached directly to the virtual private gateways.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set up an AWS Direct Connect connection from each data center to AWS in each Region. Create and attach private VIFs to a single Direct Connect gateway. Attach the Direct Connect gateway to all the VPCs. Remove the existing VPN connections that are attached directly to the virtual private gateways.",
        "Create a single transit gateway with VPN connections from each data center. Share the transit gateway with each account by using AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM). Attach the transit gateway to each VPC. Remove the existing VPN connections that are attached directly to the virtual private gateways.",
        "Peer all the VPCs in each Region to a new VPC in each Region that will function as a centralized transit VPC. Create new VPN connections from each data center to the transit VPCs. Terminate the original VPN connections that are attached to all the original VPCs. Retain the new VPN connection to the new transit VPC in each Region."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 168"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company runs applications in two VPCs that are in separate AWS Regions. One VPC is in the us-east-1 Region. The second VPC is in the us-west-1 Region. The company needs to establish connectivity between the two VPCs. The company also needs to connect the VPCs to applications that run in an on-premises data center.\n\nThe current traffic requirement between the VPCs is 50 ТВ per month. The company expects traffic volume between the VPCs to increase. The traffic requirement from the VPCs to the on-premises data center is 10 ТВ per month. The company expects the traffic between the VPCs and the data center to remain constant.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a virtual private gateway in each Region. Create VPN connections from the on-premises firewall to the virtual private gateways. Create a VPC peering connection between the two VPCs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a transit gateway in each Region. Create VPN connections from the transit gateways to the on-premises firewall. Create a peering connection between the transit gateways.",
        "Create a virtual private gateway in each Region. Create VPN connections from the on-premises firewall to the virtual private gateways. Configure the on-premises firewall to route the traffic between the two VPCs.",
        "Create a virtual private gateway in each Region. Create VPN connections from the on-premises firewall to the virtual private gateways. Create a VPN connection between the virtual private gateways."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 169"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company runs workloads in multiple VPCs. The company needs to securely access a workload in one of the VPCs, named VPC-A, from an on-premises data center. A network engineer sets up an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection to a transit gateway. The network engineer configures dynamic routing for the connection, and communication works properly.\n\nRecently, the owner of VPC-A added another CIDR range to the VPC. The VPC-A owner created workloads that use the additional CIDR range.\n\nThe company's on-premises network is unable to reach the new workloads. The network engineer needs to resolve the network connectivity issue and ensure that connectivity will not be affected if additional VPC CIDR ranges are added to the VPC in the future.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the MOST operational efficiency?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure route propagation for VPC-A to the VPN attachment route table.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Manually update the VPN attachment route table to include the new CIDR range.",
        "Configure an Amazon EventBridge rule to invoke an AWS Lambda function when the rule to matches an update to the VPC-A CIDR range. Configure the Lambda function to update the VPN attachment route table.",
        "Configure an Amazon CloudWatch alarm to invoke an AWS Lambda function when there is an update to the VPC-A CIDR range. Configure the Lambda function to update the VPN attachment route table. Restart the VPN tunnels."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 170"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is migrating its internet VPN connections to dedicated AWS Direct Connect connections. The company needs to set up the Direct Connect connections so that all network communications are encrypted in transit.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet this requirement? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create new Direct Connect connections while requesting MACsec ports.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a shared key for an IPsec connection.",
        "Configure a new Direct Connect gateway. Associate the shared key with the new Direct Connect gateway.",
        "Set up IPsec on the on-premises router. Associate the shared key with the IPsec configuration."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create a MACsec Connectivity Association Key Name (CKN) and Connectivity Association Key (CAK) pair. Associate the pair with each new connection.||Update the on-premises routers to use MACsec and the shared Connectivity Association Key Name (CKN) and Connectivity Association Key (CAK) pair.",
        "code": "Question 171"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an application VPC and a networking VPC that are connected through VPC peering. The networking VPC contains a Network Load Balancer (NLB). The application VPC contains Amazon EC2 instances that run an application. The EC2 instances are part of a target group that is associated with the NLB in the networking VPC.\n\nThe company configures a third VPC and peers it to the networking VPC. The new VPC contains a new version of the existing application. The new version of the application runs on new EC2 instances in an application subnet. The new version of the application runs in a different Availability Zone than that original version of the application.\n\nThe company needs to establish connectivity between the NLB and the new version of the application.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet this requirement? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Register the new application EC2 instances with the NLB by using instance IP addresses.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Register the new application EC2 instances with the NLB by using the instance IDs.",
        "Configure the NLB to use zonal shift.",
        "Configure the network ACL for the application subnet in the new VPC to allow outbound connections."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Configure the NLB in the Availability Zone where the new application EC2 instances run.||Configure the network ACL for the application subnet in the new VPC to allow inbound connections and outbound connections.",
        "code": "Question 172"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses AWS Site-to-Site VPN connections to encrypt traffic between the company's on-premises location and a single VPC. The Site-to-Site VPN connections use two 1 Gbps AWS Direct Connect connections with public VIFs. The company plans to add 15 additional VPCs in the same AWS Region.\n\nThe company must maintain the same level of encryption that the Site-to-Site VPN connections currently provide for each connection between the on-premises location and the new VPCs. The new connections must not use public IP addresses. The bandwidth of the Site-to-Site VPN connections will remain less than the current provisioned speed.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet these requirements with LEAST operational overhead? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create a transit gateway and a Direct Connect gateway. Associate the transit gateway with the Direct Connect gateway. Attach all the new VPCs to the transit gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "For each new VPC, create a new Direct Connect private VIF to a Direct Connect gateway. Associate all VPCs with the Direct Connect gateway.",
        "Assign a public IP CIDR block to the transit gateway.",
        "Create a public VICreate a Site-to-Site VPN public IP VPN connection."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Assign a private IP CIDR block to the transit gateway.||Create a transit VIF to the Direct Connect gateway. Create a Site-to-Site VPN private IP VPN connection.",
        "code": "Question 173"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company hosts application servers on premises and on Amazon EC2 instances in a VPC. The application servers access data that is hosted in an Amazon S3 bucket through the public internet. The EC2 instances in the VPC use an AWS Site-to-Site VPN for connectivity with the on-premises application servers.\n\nNew company regulations state that all traffic between the application servers and the S3 bucket must remain private and must not use public IP addresses.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure an S3 interface endpoint. Update the on-premises servers to use the interface endpoint DNS name to access the S3 bucket. Configure an S3 gateway endpoint. Modify the route table so that the EC2 instances use the gateway endpoint.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure an S3 gateway endpoint Modify the route table with the appropriate route for the endpoint. Access the S3 bucket through the gateway endpoint from the EC2 instances.",
        "Configure an S3 interface endpoint. Update the on-premises servers and EC2 instances to use the interface endpoint DNS name to access the S3 bucket.",
        "Configure an S3 gateway endpoint. Modify the route table with the appropriate route for the endpoint. Use an S3 bucket policy to restrict access to the gateway endpoint. Configure a proxy server fleet behind a Network Load Balancer in the VPC so that the on-premises servers can access the S3 bucket."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 174"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses AWS Network Firewall to protect outgoing traffic for multiple VPCs that are in the same AWS account. Each VPC contains Amazon EC2 instances that host the company's applications. Each EC2 instance is tagged with the name of the application it hosts. The EC2 instances are in Auto Scaling groups.\n\nA Network Firewall stateful rule group must remain up-to-date, even when an Auto Scaling group launches and terminates EC2 instances.\n\nWhich solution will meet this requirement with the LEAST implementation and administrative effort?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a resource group for each application name. Reference the Amazon Resource Name (ARN) for the resource groups in the stateful rule group.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a network ACL for each application. Reference the network ACL in the stateful rule group.",
        "Create a prefix list for each application. Reference the prefix list in the stateful rule group.",
        "Create an AWS Lambda function that queries the EC2 instance tags for each application name and then updates the stateful rule group with the IP address of each instance."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 175"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has multiple AWS Site-to-Site VPN connections between an on-premises environment and multiple VPCs. The Site-to-Site VPN connections use virtual private gateways and are configured with IPv4 addresses. The company hosts several internal applications in the VPCs.\n\nApplication users have reported that the applications are performing slowly. A network engineer notices excessive latency in the network path that the VPN connections use. The network engineer needs to resolve the excessive latency.\n\nWhich solution will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy a transit gateway and a new accelerated Site-to-Site VPN connection.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use AWS Global Accelerator to deploy an accelerator on the existing Site-to-Site VPN connections.",
        "Replace the existing Site-to-Site VPN connections with new Site-to-Site VPN connections that use IPv6.",
        "Replace the existing Site-to-Site VPN connections with AWS PrivateLink connections."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 176"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a transit gateway in a single AWS account. The company sends flow logs for the transit gateway to an Amazon CloudWatch Logs log group.\n\nThe company created an AWS Lambda function to analyze the logs. The Lambda function sends a notification to an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topic when a VPC generates traffic that is dropped by the transit gateway. Each notification contains the account ID. VPC ID, and total amount of dropped packets.\n\nThe company wants to subscribe a new Lambda function to the SNS topic. The new Lambda function must automatically prevent the traffic that is identified in each notification from leaving a VPC by applying a network ACL to the transit gateway attachment subnets in the VPC that generates the traffic.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure the existing Lambda function to add the source IP addresses of the dropped traffic to each SNS notification. Configure the new Lambda function to create an outbound rule by using the source IP addresses in the network ACL.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure the existing Lambda function to add the destination IP addresses of the dropped traffic to each SNS notification. Configure the new Lambda function to create an outbound rule by using the destination IP addresses in the network ACL.",
        "Configure the existing Lambda function to add the source IP addresses of the dropped traffic to each SNS notification. Configure the new Lambda function to create an inbound rule by using the source IP addresses in the network ACL.",
        "Configure the existing Lambda function to add the destination IP addresses of the dropped traffic to each SNS notification. Configure the new Lambda function to create an inbound rule by using the destination IP addresses in the network ACL."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 177"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has multiple VPCs with subnets that use IPv4. Traffic from the VPCs to the internet uses a NAT gateway. The company wants to transition to IPv6.\n\nA network engineer creates multiple IPv6-only subnets in an existing testing VPC. The network engineer deploys a new Amazon EC2 instance that has an IPv6 address into one of the subnets. During testing, the network engineer discovers that the new EC2 instance is not able to communicate with an IPv4-only service through the internet. The network engineer needs to enable the IPv6 EC2 instance to communicate with the IPv4-only service.\n\nWhich solution will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Enable DNS64 for the IPv6-only subnets. Update the route tables for the IPv6-only subnets to send traffic through the NAT gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Enable NAT64 for the testing VPC. Reconfigure the existing NAT gateway to support IPv6.",
        "Enable DNS64 for the new EC2 instance. Create a new egress-only internet gateway that supports IPv6.",
        "Enable NAT64 for each route table. Create a new NAT gateway that supports both IPv4 and IPv6."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 178"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building its website on AWS in a single VPC. The VPC has public subnets and private subnets in two Availability Zones. The website has static content such as images. The company is using Amazon S3 to store the content.\n\nThe company has deployed a fleet of Amazon EC2 instances as web servers in a private subnet. The EC2 instances are in an Auto Scaling group behind an Application Load Balancer. The EC2 instances will serve traffic, and they must pull content from an S3 bucket to render the webpages. The company is using AWS Direct Connect with a public VIF for on-premises connectivity to the S3 bucket.\n\nA network engineer notices that traffic between the EC2 instances and Amazon S3 is routing through a NAT gateway. As traffic increases, the company's costs are increasing. The network engineer needs to change the connectivity to reduce the NAT gateway costs that result from the traffic between the EC2 instances and Amazon S3.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Implement gateway VPC endpoints for Amazon S3. Update the VPC route table.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a Direct Connect private VIF. Migrate the traffic from the public VIF to the private VIF.",
        "Create an AWS Site-to-Site VPN tunnel over the existing public VIF.",
        "Implement interface VPC endpoints for Amazon S3. Update the VPC route table."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 179"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company deployed an application in two AWS Regions in one AWS account. The company has one VPC in each Region. The VPCs use non-overlapping private CIDR ranges.\n\nThe company needs to connect both VPCs to a single on-premises data center to test the application. The application requires up to 800 Mbps of throughput. A network engineer needs to establish connectivity between the VPCs and the on-premises data center.\n\nWhich solution will meet this requirement with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure a customer gateway and a virtual private gateway in each VPC. Configure an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection between the data center and each VPC. Configure BGP routing between the VPCs and the data center.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Order a 2 Gbps Direct Connect connection for the data center. Configure a virtual private gateway in each VPC. Create a private VIF for each virtual private gateway, and associate the virtual private gateways with the Direct Connect connection. Configure static routes in the VPC route tables and in the data center router.",
        "Order a 2 Gbps Direct Connect connection for the data center. Configure a virtual private gateway in each VPC. Create a private VIF for each virtual private gateway, and associate the virtual private gateways with the Direct Connect connection. Configure Open Shortest Path First (OSPF) routing between the private VIF and the data center.",
        "Configure a customer gateway and a virtual private gateway in each VPConfigure an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection between the data center and each VPConfigure static routes in each VPC route table to point to the subnets in the data center."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 180"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company runs a workload in a single VPC on AWS. The company’s architecture contains several interface VPC endpoints for AWS services, including Amazon CloudWatch Logs and AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS). The endpoints are configured to use a shared security group. The security group is not used for any other workloads or resources.\n\nAfter a security review of the environment, the company determined that the shared security group is more permissive than necessary. The company wants to make the rules associated with the security group more restrictive. The changes to the security group rules must not prevent the resources in the VPC from using AWS services through interface VPC endpoints. The changes must prevent unnecessary access.\n\nThe security group currently uses the following rules:\n\n• Inbound - Rule 1\n\nProtocol: TCP -\n\nPort: 443 -\n\nSource: 0.0.0.0/0 -\n\n• Inbound - Rule 2\n\nProtocol: TCP -\n\nPort: 443 -\n\nSource: VPC CIDR -\n\n• Outbound - Rule 1\n\nProtocol: All -\n\nPort: All -\n\nDestination: 0.0.0.0/0 -\n\nWhich rule or rules should the company remove to meet with these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Inbound - Rule 1 and Outbound - Rule 1",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Outbound - Rule 2",
        "Inbound - Rule 2 and Outbound - Rule 1",
        "Outbound - Rule 1"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 181"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses transit gateways to route traffic between the company's VPCs. Each transit gateway has a single route table. Each route table contains attachments and routes for the VPCs that are in the same AWS Region as the transit gateway. The route tables in each VPC also contain routes to all the other VPC CIDR ranges that are available through the transit gateways. Some VPCs route to local NAT gateways.\n\nThe company plans to add many new VPCs soon. A network engineer needs a solution to add new VPC CIDR ranges to the route tables in each VPC.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements in the MOST operationally efficient way?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new customer-managed prefix list. Add all VPC CIDR ranges to the new prefix list. Update the route tables in each VPC to use the new prefix list ID as the destination and the appropriate transit gateway ID as the target.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Turn on default route table propagation for the transit gateway route tables. Turn on route propagation for each route table in each VPC.",
        "Update the route tables in each VPC to use 0.0.0.010 as the destination and the appropriate transit gateway ID as the target.",
        "Turn on default route table association for the transit gateway route tables. Turn on route propagation for each route table in each VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 182"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has several AWS Site-to-Site VPN connections between an on-premises customer gateway and a transit gateway. The company's application uses IPv4 to communicate through the VPN connections.\n\nThe company has updated the VPC to be dual stack and wants to transition to using IPv6-only for new workloads. When the company tries to communicate through the existing VPN connections, IPv6 traffic fails.\n\nWhich solution will provide IPv6 support with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new Site-to-Site VPN connection that supports IPv6.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new Site-to-Site VPN connection to a self-managed Amazon EC2 instance that runs open source software.",
        "Update the existing Site-to-Site VPN connections to support IPv6.",
        "Update the on-premises customer gateway's public IP address from IPv4 to IPv6."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 183"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has two teams: Team A and Team B. Team A has VPCs that run in Account A. The team uses a transit gateway (TGW-A) to route traffic between workloads that run in the different VPCs. Similarly, Team В has VPCs that run in Account B. Team В uses a different transit gateway (TGW-B) to route traffic between workloads that run in the different VPCs.\n\nThe company's network team manages the routing for Team A and Team В. The network team wants to retire TGW-B and use a single transit gateway to manage routing for the VPCs of both teams.\n\nWhich solution will meet this requirement with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a resource share for TGW-A Share TGW-A with Account B. Create VPC attachments for the VPCs in Account В. Configure routing for the VPCs in TGW-A route tables. Update the route tables of the VPCs in Account В to forward traffic to TGW-Delete TGW-B attachments and TGW-B.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a resource share for TGW-A. Share TGW-A with Account В. Replicate the TGW-B configuration to TGW-A to automatically start routing changes for the VPCs in Account В. Delete TGW-B when routing changes are complete.",
        "Create a new transit gateway (TGW-C) in Account A. Create a resource share for TGW-Share TGW-C with Account B. Create VPC attachments for the VPCs in Account A and Account В. Configure routing for all the VPCs in TGW-C route tables. Update the route tables for the VPCs in Account A and Account В to forward traffic to TGW-Delete TGW-A attachments and TGW-B attachments. Delete TGW-A and TGW-B.",
        "Create a new transit gateway (TGW-C) in a new account (Account C). Create a resource share for TGW-C. Share TGW-C with Account A and Account B. Create VPC attachments for the VPCs in Account A and Account В. Configure routing for all the VPCs in TGW-C route tables. Update the route tables for the VPCs in Account A and Account В to forward traffic to TGW-C. Delete TGW-A attachments and TGW-B attachments. Delete TGW-A and TGW-B."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 184"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an AWS environment that includes multiple VPCs that are connected by a transit gateway. The company wants to use a certificate-based AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection to establish connectivity between an on-premises environment and the AWS environment. The company does not have a static public IP address for the on-premises environment.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the company take to establish VPN connectivity between the transit gateway and the on-premises environment? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create a private certificate in AWS Certificate Manager (ACM).",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a public certificate in AWS Certificate Manager (ACM).",
        "Configure the Site-to-Site VPN tunnels to use the pre-shared key (PSK).",
        "Create a customer gateway. Specify the current dynamic IP address of the customer gateway device's external interface."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create a customer gateway. Do not specify the IP address of the customer gateway device.",
        "code": "Question 185"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company operates in multiple AWS Regions. The company has deployed transit gateways in each Region. The company uses AWS Organizations to operate multiple AWS accounts in one organization.\n\nThe company needs to capture all VPC flow log data when a new VPC is created. The company needs to send flow logs to a specific Amazon S3 bucket.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST administrative effort?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a custom AWS Config rule with automatic remediation that verifies VPC Flow Logs is enabled and configured correctly. Apply the AWS Config rule to the organization.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Update IAM permissions for each user to include a condition that ensures users can create VPCs only when VPC Flow Logs is enabled and configured correctly.",
        "Enable VPC Flow Logs on each transit gateway. Configure VPC Flow Logs to send flow logs to the specified S3 bucket.",
        "Deploy a serverless application that uses AWS CloudTrail to monitor for VPC creation events in each account. Configure the application to apply the correct VPC Flow Logs configuration."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 186"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to analyze TCP internet traffic. The traffic originates from Amazon EC2 instances in the company’s VPC. The EC2 instances initiate connections through a NAT gateway.\n\nThe company wants to capture data about the traffic including source and destination IP addresses ports, and the first 8 bytes of the TCP segments of the traffic. The company needs to collect, store, and analyze all the required data points.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure the NAT gateway to be a VPC traffic mirror source. Deploy software on the traffic mirror target to forward the data to an Amazon S3 bucket. Analyze the data by using Amazon Athena.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure the EC2 instances to be VPC traffic mirror sources. Deploy software on the traffic mirror target to forward the data to Amazon CloudWatch Logs. Analyze the data by using CloudWatch Logs Insights",
        "Turn on VPC Flow Logs for the EC2 instances. Specify the default format and set Amazon CloudWatch Logs as the log destination. Analyze the flow log data by using CloudWatch Logs Insights.",
        "Turn on VPC Flow Logs for the EC2 instances. Specify a custom format and set Amazon S3 as the log destination. Analyze the flow log data by using Amazon Athena."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 187"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A media company is planning to host an event that the company will live stream to users. The company wants to use Amazon CloudFront.\n\nA network engineer creates a primary origin and a secondary origin for CloudFront. The engineer needs to ensure that the primary origin can fail over to the secondary origin within 15 seconds if a disruption occurs.\n\nWhich solution will meet this requirement with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Set the CloudFront origin connection timeout value to 5 seconds Set the origin connection attempts value to 2.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure a Lambda@Edge function to check the health status of both origins every 10 seconds. Reroute incoming requests when the origin health status is unhealthy.",
        "Create a Network Load Balancer (NLB) in front of both origins Configure the NLB as the origin in CloudFront.",
        "Configure a Lambda@Edge function to monitor incoming requests for an origin response. Reroute incoming requests if no response is received from the primary origin within 10 seconds."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 188"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "AnyCompany deploys and manages networking resources in its AWS network account, named Account-A. AnyCompany acquires Example Corp, which has an application that runs behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB) in Example Corp's AWS account, named Account-B.\n\nExample Corp needs to use AWS Global Accelerator to create an accelerator to publish the application to users. AnyCompany's networking team will manage the accelerator.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST management overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a cross-account Global Accelerator attachment in Account-В for the Account-A principal. Create an accelerator in Account-A by using the shared attachment.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an accelerator in Account-В. Use a cross-account role from Account-A to grant the networking team access to manage the accelerator.",
        "Deploy a Network Load Balancer (NLB) in Account-A to route traffic to the ALB in Account-В. Create an accelerator, and set the NLB as the endpoint in Account-A.",
        "Create an accelerator in Account-A. Use AWS Resource Access Management (AWS RAM) to share the accelerator with Account-В. Associate the ALB in Account-В with the accelerator in Account-A."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 189"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to improve visibility into its AWS environment. The AWS environment consists of multiple VPCs that are connected to a transit gateway. The transit gateway connects to an on-premises data center through an AWS Direct Connect gateway and a pair of redundant Direct Connect connections that use transit VIFs. The company must receive notification each time a new route is advertised to AWS from on premises over Direct Connect.\n\nWhat should a network engineer do to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Onboard Transit Gateway Network Manager to Amazon CloudWatch Logs Insights. Use Amazon EventBridge (Amazon CloudWatch Events) to send notifications when routes change.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Enable Amazon CloudWatch metrics on Direct Connect to track the received routes. Configure a CloudWatch alarm to send notifications when routes change.",
        "Configure an AWS Lambda function to periodically check the routes on the Direct Connect gateway and to send notifications when routes change.",
        "Enable Amazon CloudWatch Logs on the transit VIFs to track the received routes. Create a metric filter Set an alarm on the filter to send notifications when routes change."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 190"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has two AWS Direct Connect connections between Direct Connect locations and the company's on-premises environment in the US. The company uses the connections to communicate with AWS workloads that run in the us-east-1 Region. The company has a transit gateway that connects several VPCs. The Direct Connect connections terminate at a Direct Connect gateway and the transit VIFs to the transit gateway.\n\nThe company recently acquired a smaller company that is based in Europe. The newly acquired company has only on-premises workloads. The newly acquired company does not expect to run workloads on AWS for the next 3 years. However, the newly acquired company requires connectivity to the parent company's AWS resources in us-east-1 and to the parent company's on-premises environment in the US. The parent company wants to use two new Direct Connect connections in Europe to provide the required connectivity.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST operational overhead for the newly acquired company?",
      "correct_answer": "Associate new transit VIFs to the existing Direct Connect gateway. Configure the new transit VIFs to use Direct Connect SiteLink.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Associate new transit VIFs to a new Direct Connect gateway and to a new transit gateway in the eu-west-1 Region. Use transit gateway peering to connect the transit gateways.",
        "Associate new private VIFs to the existing Direct Connect gateway. Configure the existing transit VIFs and the new private VIFs to use Direct Connect SiteLink.",
        "Associate new private VIFs to a new Direct Connect gateway and to a new VPC in us-east-1. Configure the existing transit VIFs and the new private VIFs to use Direct Connect SiteLink and AWS PrivateLink endpoints in the new VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 191"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is establishing hybrid cloud connectivity from an on-premises environment to AWS in the us-east-1 Region. The company is using a 10 Gbps AWS Direct Connect dedicated connection. The company has two accounts in AWS. Account A has transit gateways in four AWS Regions. Account В has transit gateways in three Regions. The company does not plan to expand.\n\nTo meet security requirements the company's accounts must have separate cloud infrastructure.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Create one Direct Connect gateway in us-east-1 for Account A. Create a second Direct Connect gateway in us-east-1 for Account Create a transit VIF for Account A. Associate the four transit gateways in Account A to the Direct Connect gateway in Account A. Create a transit VIF for Account Associate the three transit gateways in Account В to the Direct Connect gateway in Account В.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create one Direct Connect gateway in us-east-1. Use AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM) to share the Direct Connect gateway with each account. Create a transit VIF for Account Associate the four transit gateways in Account A to the Direct Connect gateway. Create a transit VIF for Account B. Associate the three transit gateways in Account В to the Direct Connect gateway.",
        "Create one Direct Connect gateway in us-east-1. Use AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM) to share the Direct Connect gateway with each account. Create a transit VIF for Account A. Associate the four transit gateways in Account A to the Direct Connect gateway. Order a new 10 Gbps Direct Connect dedicated connection for Account B. Create a transit VIF on the new Direct Connect connection for Account B. Associate the three transit gateways in Account В to the Direct Connect gateway.",
        "Create one Direct Connect gateway in us-east-1 for Account A. Create a second Direct Connect gateway in us-east-1 for Account B. Create a transit VIF for Account A. Associate the four transit gateways in Account A to the Direct Connect gateway in Account A. Order a new 10 Gbps Direct Connect dedicated connection for Account В. Create a transit VIF on the new Direct Connect connection for Account В. Associate the three transit gateways in Account В to the Direct Connect gateway in Account В."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 192"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company runs an application across multiple AWS Regions and multiple Availability Zones. The company needs to expand to a new AWS Region. Low latency is critical to the functionality of the application.\n\nA network engineer needs to gather metrics for the latency between the existing. Regions and the new Region. The network engineer must gather metrics for at least the previous 30 days.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Set up AWS Network Manager Infrastructure Performance. Publish network performance metrics to Amazon CloudWatch.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure an AWS Network Access Analyzer Network Access Scope, and use the analysis to review the latency.",
        "Use an Amazon VPC Reachability Analyzer path to review the latency.",
        "Set up VPC Flow Logs. Publish log metrics to Amazon CloudWatch."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 193"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A software company offers a software-as-a-service (SaaS) accounting application that is hosted in the AWS Cloud The application requires connectivity to the company's on-premises network. The company has two redundant 10 GB AWS Direct Connect connections between AWS and its on-premises network to accommodate the growing demand for the application.\n\nThe company already has encryption between its on-premises network and the colocation. The company needs to encrypt traffic between AWS and the edge routers in the colocation within the next few months. The company must maintain its current bandwidth.\n\nWhat should a network engineer do to meet these requirements with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy a new pair of 10 GB Direct Connect connections with MACsec. Configure MACsec on the edge routers. Reroute traffic to the new Direct Connect connections. Decommission the original Direct Connect connections",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy a new public VIF with encryption on the existing Direct Connect connections. Reroute traffic through the new public VIF.",
        "Create a virtual private gateway Deploy new AWS Site-to-Site VPN connections from on premises to the virtual private gateway Reroute traffic from the Direct Connect private VIF to the new VPNs.",
        "Deploy a new pair of 10 GB Direct Connect connections with MACsec. Deploy a new public VIF on the new Direct Connect connections. Deploy two AWS Site-to-Site VPN connections on top of the new public VIF. Reroute traffic from the existing private VIF to the new Site-to-Site connections. Decommission the original Direct Connect connections."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 194"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company hosts an application on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). The company recently experienced a network security breach. A network engineer must collect and analyze logs that include the client IP address, target IP address, target port, and user agent of each user that accesses the application.\n\nWhat is the MOST operationally efficient solution that meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure the ALB to store logs in an Amazon S3 bucket. Use Amazon Athena to analyze the logs in Amazon S3.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure the ALB to store logs in an Amazon S3 bucket. Download the files from Amazon S3, and use a spreadsheet application to analyze the logs.",
        "Configure the ALB to push logs to Amazon Kinesis Data Streams. Use Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics to analyze the logs.",
        "Configure Amazon Kinesis Data Streams to stream data from the ALB to Amazon OpenSearch Service (Amazon Elasticsearch Service). Use search operations in Amazon OpenSearch Service (Amazon Elasticsearch Service) to analyze the data."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 195"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has developed an application on AWS that will track inventory levels of vending machines and initiate the restocking process automatically. The company plans to integrate this application with vending machines and deploy the vending machines in several markets around the world. The application resides in a VPC in the us-east-1 Region. The application consists of an Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) cluster behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). The communication from the vending machines to the application happens over HTTPS.\n\nThe company is planning to use an AWS Global Accelerator accelerator and configure static IP addresses of the accelerator in the vending machines for application endpoint access. The application must be accessible only through the accelerator and not through a direct connection over the internet to the ALB endpoint.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure the ALB in a private subnet of the VPC. Attach an internet gateway without adding routes in the subnet route tables to point to the internet gateway. Configure the accelerator with endpoint groups that include the ALB endpoint. Configure the ALB’s security group to only allow inbound traffic from the internet on the ALB listener port.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure the ALB in a private subnet of the VPC. Configure the accelerator with endpoint groups that include the ALB endpoint. Configure the ALB's security group to only allow inbound traffic from the internet on the ALB listener port.",
        "Configure the ALB in a public subnet of the VPAttach an internet gateway. Add routes in the subnet route tables to point to the internet gateway. Configure the accelerator with endpoint groups that include the ALB endpoint. Configure the ALB's security group to only allow inbound traffic from the accelerator's IP addresses on the ALB listener port.",
        "Configure the ALB in a private subnet of the VPC. Attach an internet gateway. Add routes in the subnet route tables to point to the internet gateway. Configure the accelerator with endpoint groups that include the ALB endpoint. Configure the ALB's security group to only allow inbound traffic from the accelerator's IP addresses on the ALB listener port."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 196"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A media company is implementing a news website for a global audience. The website uses Amazon CloudFront as its content delivery network. The backend runs on Amazon EC2 Windows instances behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). The instances are part of an Auto Scaling group. The company's customers access the website by using service example com as the CloudFront custom domain name. The CloudFront origin points to an ALB that uses service-alb.example.com as the domain name.\n\nThe company’s security policy requires the traffic to be encrypted in transit at all times between the users and the backend.\n\nWhich combination of changes must the company make to meet this security requirement? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create a certificate for service.example.com by using AWS Certificate Manager (ACM). Configure CloudFront to use this custom SSL/TLS certificate. Change the default behavior to redirect HTTP to HTTPS.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a self-signed certificate for service.example.com. Import the certificate into AWS Certificate Manager (ACM). Configure CloudFront to use this imported SSL/TLS certificate. Change the default behavior to redirect HTTP to HTTPS.",
        "Create a certificate with any domain name by using AWS Certificate Manager (ACM) for the EC2 instances. Configure the backend to use this certificate for its HTTPS listener. Specify the instance target type during the creation of a new target group that uses the HTTPS protocol for its targets. Attach the existing Auto Scaling group to this new target group.",
        "Create a self-signed certificate for service-alb.example.com. Import the certificate into AWS Certificate Manager (ACM). On the ALB add a new HTTPS listener that uses the new target group and the imported service-alb.example.com ACM certificate. Modify the CloudFront origin to use the HTTPS protocol only. Delete the HTTP listener on the ALB."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create a public certificate from a third-party certificate provider with any domain name for the EC2 instances. Configure the backend to use this certificate for its HTTPS listener. Specify the instance target type during the creation of a new target group that uses the HTTPS protocol for its targets. Attach the existing Auto Scaling group to this new target group.||Create a certificate for service-alb.example.com by using AWS Certificate Manager (ACM). On the ALB add a new HTTPS listener that uses the new target group and the service-alb.example.com ACM certificate. Modify the CloudFront origin to use the HTTPS protocol only. Delete the HTTP listener on the ALB.",
        "code": "Question 197"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is hosting an application on Amazon EC2 instances behind a Network Load Balancer (NLB). A solutions architect added EC2 instances in a second Availability Zone to improve the availability of the application. The solutions architect added the instances to the NLB target group.\n\nThe company's operations team notices that traffic is being routed only to the instances in the first Availability Zone.\n\nWhat is the MOST operationally efficient solution to resolve this issue?",
      "correct_answer": "Enable the new Availability Zone on the NLB",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new NLB for the instances in the second Availability Zone",
        "Enable proxy protocol on the NLB",
        "Create a new target group with the instances in both Availability Zones"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 198"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer needs to set up an Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling group to run a Linux-based network appliance in a highly available architecture. The network engineer is configuring the new launch template for the Auto Scaling group.\n\nIn addition to the primary network interface the network appliance requires a second network interface that will be used exclusively by the application to exchange traffic with hosts over the internet. The company has set up a Bring Your Own IP (BYOIP) pool that includes an Elastic IP address that should be used as the public IP address for the second network interface.\n\nHow can the network engineer implement the required architecture?",
      "correct_answer": "During creation of the Auto Scaling group, select subnets for the primary network interface. Use the user data option to run a cloud-init script to allocate a second network interface and to associate an Elastic IP address from the BYOIP pool.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure the two network interfaces in the launch template. Define the primary network interface to be created in one of the private subnets. For the second network interface, select one of the public subnets. Choose the BYOIP pool ID as the source of public IP addresses.",
        "Configure the primary network interface in a private subnet in the launch template. Use the user data option to run a cloud-init script after boot to attach the second network interface from a subnet with auto-assign public IP addressing enabled.",
        "Create an AWS Lambda function to run as a lifecycle hook of the Auto Scaling group when an instance is launching. In the Lambda function, assign a network interface to an AWS Global Accelerator endpoint."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 199"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company delivers applications over the internet. An Amazon Route 53 public hosted zone is the authoritative DNS service for the company and its internet applications, all of which are offered from the same domain name.\n\nA network engineer is working on a new version of one of the applications. All the application's components are hosted in the AWS Cloud. The application has a three-tier design. The front end is delivered through Amazon EC2 instances that are deployed in public subnets with Elastic IP addresses assigned. The backend components are deployed in private subnets from RFC1918.\n\nComponents of the application need to be able to access other components of the application within the application's VPC by using the same host names as the host names that are used over the public internet. The network engineer also needs to accommodate future DNS changes, such as the introduction of new host names or the retirement of DNS entries.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet these requirements? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create a Route 53 private hosted zone for the same domain name Associate the application’s VPC with the new private hosted zone.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Add a geoproximity routing policy in Route 53.",
        "Create an Amazon EventBridge (Amazon CloudWatch Events) rule that runs when AWS CloudTrail logs a Route 53 API call to the public hosted zone. Create an AWS Lambda function as the target of the rule. Configure the function to use the event information to update the private hosted zone.",
        "Add the private IP addresses in the existing Route 53 public hosted zone."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Enable DNS hostnames for the application's VPC.||Create entries in the private hosted zone for each name in the public hosted zone by using the corresponding private IP addresses.",
        "code": "Question 200"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is deploying an application. The application is implemented in a series of containers in an Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS) cluster. The company will use the Fargate launch type for its tasks. The containers will run workloads that require connectivity initiated over an SSL connection. Traffic must be able to flow to the application from other AWS accounts over private connectivity. The application must scale in a manageable way as more consumers use the application.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Choose a Network Load Balancer (NLB) as the type of load balancer for the ECS service. Specify the NLB in the service definition. Create a VPC endpoint service for the NLB. Share the VPC endpoint service with other AWS accounts.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Choose a Gateway Load Balancer (GLB) as the type of load balancer for the ECS service. Create a lifecycle hook to add new tasks to the target group from Amazon ECS as required to handle scaling. Specify the GLB in the service definition. Create a VPC peer for external AWS accounts. Update the route tables so that the AWS accounts can reach the GLB.",
        "Choose an Application Load Balancer (ALB) as the type of load balancer for the ECS service. Create path-based routing rules to allow the application to target the containers that are registered in the target group. Specify the ALB in the service definition. Create a VPC endpoint service for the ALB Share the VPC endpoint service with other AWS accounts.",
        "Choose an Application Load Balancer (ALB) as the type of load balancer for the ECS service. Create path-based routing rules to allow the application to target the containers that are registered in the target group. Specify the ALB in the service definition. Create a VPC peer for the external AWS accounts. Update the route tables so that the AWS accounts can reach the ALB."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 201"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company's development team has created a new product recommendation web service. The web service is hosted in a VPC with a CIDR block of 192.168.224.0/19. The company has deployed the web service on Amazon EC2 instances and has configured an Auto Scaling group as the target of a Network Load Balancer (NLB).\n\nThe company wants to perform testing to determine whether users who receive product recommendations spend more money than users who do not receive product recommendations. The company has a big sales event in 5 days and needs to integrate its existing production environment with the recommendation engine by then. The existing production environment is hosted in a VPC with a CIDR block of 192.168.128 0/17.\n\nA network engineer must integrate the systems by designing a solution that results in the least possible disruption to the existing environments.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a VPC endpoint service. Associate the VPC endpoint service with the NLB for the web service. Create an interface VPC endpoint for the web service in the existing production VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a VPC peering connection between the web service VPC and the existing production VPC. Add a routing rule to the appropriate route table to allow data to flow to 192.168.224.0/19 from the existing production environment and to flow to 192.168.128.0/17 from the web service environment. Configure the relevant security groups and ACLs to allow the systems to communicate.",
        "Ask the development team of the web service to redeploy the web service into the production VPC and integrate the systems there.",
        "Create a transit gateway in the existing production environment. Create attachments to the production VPC and the web service VPC. Configure appropriate routing rules in the transit gateway and VPC route tables for 192.168.224.0/19 and 192.168.128.0/17. Configure the relevant security groups and ACLs to allow the systems to communicate."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 202"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer needs to update a company's hybrid network to support IPv6 for the upcoming release of a new application. The application is hosted in a VPC in the AWS Cloud. The company's current AWS infrastructure includes VPCs that are connected by a transit gateway. The transit gateway is connected to the on-premises network by AWS Direct Connect and AWS Site-to-Site VPN. The company's on-premises devices have been updated to support the new IPv6 requirements.\n\nThe company has enabled IPv6 for the existing VPC by assigning a new IPv6 CIDR block to the VPC and by assigning IPv6 to the subnets for dual-stack support. The company has launched new Amazon EC2 instances for the new application in the updated subnets.\n\nWhen updating the hybrid network to support IPv6 the network engineer must avoid making any changes to the current infrastructure. The network engineer also must block direct access to the instances' new IPv6 addresses from the internet. However, the network engineer must allow outbound internet access from the instances.\n\nWhat is the MOST operationally efficient solution that meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Update the Direct Connect transit VIF and configure BGP peering with the AWS assigned IPv6 peering address. Create a new VPN connection that supports IPv6 connectivity. Add an egress-only internet gateway. Update any affected VPC security groups and route tables to provide connectivity within the VPC and between the VPC and the on-premises devices",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Update the Direct Connect transit VIF and configure BGP peering with the AWS assigned IPv6 peering address. Update the existing VPN connection to support IPv6 connectivity. Add an egress-only internet gateway. Update any affected VPC security groups and route tables to provide connectivity within the VPC and between the VPC and the on-premises devices.",
        "Create a Direct Connect transit VIF and configure BGP peering with the AWS assigned IPv6 peering address. Create a new VPN connection that supports IPv6 connectivity. Add an egress-only internet gateway. Update any affected VPC security groups and route tables to provide connectivity within the VPC and between the VPC and the on-premises devices.",
        "Create a Direct Connect transit VIF and configure BGP peering with the AWS assigned IPv6 peering address. Create a new VPN connection that supports IPv6 connectivity. Add a NAT gateway. Update any affected VPC security groups and route tables to provide connectivity within the VPC and between the VPC and the on-premises devices."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 203"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer must provide additional safeguards to protect encrypted data at Application Load Balancers (ALBs) through the use of a unique random session key.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Change the ALB security policy to a policy that supports forward secrecy (FS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Change the ALB security policy to a policy that supports TLS 1.2 protocol only",
        "Use AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) to encrypt session keys",
        "Associate an AWS WAF web ACL with the ALBs. and create a security rule to enforce forward secrecy (FS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 204"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has deployed a software-defined WAN (SD-WAN) solution to interconnect all of its offices. The company is migrating workloads to AWS and needs to extend its SD-WAN solution to support connectivity to these workloads.\n\nA network engineer plans to deploy AWS Transit Gateway Connect and two SD-WAN virtual appliances to provide this connectivity. According to company policies, only a single SD-WAN virtual appliance can handle traffic from AWS workloads at a given time.\n\nHow should the network engineer configure routing to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure the AS_PATH prepend attribute on the secondary SD-WAN virtual appliance for BGP routes toward the transit gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Add a static default route in the transit gateway route table to point to the secondary SD-WAN virtual appliance. Add routes that are more specific to point to the primary SD-WAN virtual appliance.",
        "Configure the BGP community tag 7224:7300 on the primary SD-WAN virtual appliance for BGP routes toward the transit gateway.",
        "Disable equal-cost multi-path (ECMP) routing on the transit gateway for Transit Gateway Connect."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 205"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to deploy many software-defined WAN (SD-WAN) sites. The company is using AWS Transit Gateway and has deployed a transit gateway in the required AWS Region. A network engineer needs to deploy the SD-WAN hub virtual appliance into a VPC that is connected to the transit gateway. The solution must support at least 5 Gbps of throughput from the SD-WAN hub virtual appliance to other VPCs that are attached to the transit gateway.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Assign a new CIDR block to the transit gateway. Create a new VPC for the SD-WAN hub virtual appliance. Attach the new VPC to the transit gateway with a VPC attachment. Add a transit gateway Connect attachment. Create a Connect peer and specify the GRE and BGP parameters. Create a route in the appropriate VPC for the SD-WAN hub virtual appliance to route to the transit gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new VPC for the SD-WAN hub virtual appliance. Create two IPsec VPN connections between the SD-WAN hub virtual appliance and the transit gateway. Configure BGP over the IPsec VPN connections",
        "Create a new VPC for the SD-WAN hub virtual appliance. Attach the new VPC to the transit gateway with a VPC attachment. Create two IPsec VPN connections between the SD-WAN hub virtual appliance and the transit gateway. Configure BGP over the IPsec VPN connections.",
        "Assign a new CIDR block to the transit gateway. Create a new VPC for the SD-WAN hub virtual appliance. Attach the new VPC to the transit gateway with a VPC attachment. Add a transit gateway Connect attachment. Create a Connect peer and specify the VXLAN and BGP parameters. Create a route in the appropriate VPC for the SD-WAN hub virtual appliance to route to the transit gateway."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 206"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A global delivery company is modernizing its fleet management system. The company has several business units. Each business unit designs and maintains applications that are hosted in its own AWS account in separate application VPCs in the same AWS Region. Each business unit's applications are designed to get data from a central shared services VPC.\n\nThe company wants the network connectivity architecture to provide granular security controls. The architecture also must be able to scale as more business units consume data from the central shared services VPC in the future.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements in the MOST secure manner?",
      "correct_answer": "Create VPC endpoint services powered by AWS PrivateLink in the central shared services VPCreate VPC endpoints in each application VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a central transit gateway. Create a VPC attachment to each application VPC. Provide full mesh connectivity between all the VPCs by using the transit gateway.",
        "Create VPC peering connections between the central shared services VPC and each application VPC in each business unit's AWS account.",
        "Create a central transit VPC with a VPN appliance from AWS Marketplace. Create a VPN attachment from each VPC to the transit VPC. Provide full mesh connectivity among all the VPCs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 207"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is deploying a new application on AWS. The application uses dynamic multicasting. The company has five VPCs that are all attached to a transit gateway Amazon EC2 instances in each VPC need to be able to register dynamically to receive a multicast transmission.\n\nHow should a network engineer configure the AWS resources to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an Internet Group Management Protocol (IGMP) multicast domain within the transit gateway. Associate the VPCs and applicable subnets with the multicast domain. Register the multicast senders' network interface with the multicast domain. Adjust the network ACLs to allow UDP traffic from the source to all receivers and to allow UDP traffic that is sent to the multicast group address.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a static source multicast domain within the transit gateway. Associate the VPCs and applicable subnets with the multicast domain. Register the multicast senders' network interface with the multicast domain. Adjust the network ACLs to allow UDP traffic from the source to all receivers and to allow UDP traffic that is sent to the multicast group address.",
        "Create a static source multicast domain within the transit gateway. Associate the VPCs and applicable subnets with the multicast domain. Register the multicast senders' network interface with the multicast domain. Adjust the network ACLs to allow TCP traffic from the source to all receivers and to allow TCP traffic that is sent to the multicast group address.",
        "Create an Internet Group Management Protocol (IGMP) multicast domain within the transit gateway. Associate the VPCs and applicable subnets with the multicast domain. Register the multicast senders' network interface with the multicast domain. Adjust the network ACLs to allow TCP traffic from the source to all receivers and to allow TCP traffic that is sent to the multicast group address."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 208"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is creating new features for its ecommerce website. These features will use several microservices that are accessed through different paths. The microservices will run on Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS). The company requires the use of HTTPS for all of its public websites. The application requires the customer’s source IP addresses.\n\nA network engineer must implement a load balancing strategy that meets these requirements.\n\nWhich combination of actions should the network engineer take to accomplish this goal? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Retrieve client IP addresses by using the X-Forwarded-For header",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use a Network Load Balancer",
        "Use AWS App Mesh load balancing",
        "Retrieve client IP addresses by using the X-IP-Source header"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Use an Application Load Balancer.",
        "code": "Question 209"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is migrating its containerized application to AWS. For the architecture the company will have an ingress VPC with a Network Load Balancer (NLB) to distribute the traffic to front-end pods in an Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) cluster. The front end of the application will determine which user is requesting access and will send traffic to 1 of 10 services VPCs. Each services VPC will include an NLB that distributes traffic to the services pods in an EKS cluster.\n\nThe company is concerned about overall cost. User traffic will be responsible for more than 10 TB of data transfer from the ingress VPC to services VPCs every month. A network engineer needs to recommend how to design the communication between the VPCs.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements at the LOWEST cost?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a VPC peering connection between the ingress VPC and each of the 10 services VPCs. Use zonal DNS names for the NLB in the services VPCs to minimize cross-AZ traffic from the ingress VPC to the services VPCs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a transit gateway. Peer each VPC to the transit gateway. Use zonal DNS names for the NLB in the services VPCs to minimize cross-AZ traffic from the ingress VPC to the services VPCs.",
        "Create an AWS PrivateLink endpoint in every Availability Zone in the ingress VPC. Each PrivateLink endpoint will point to the zonal DNS entry of the NLB in the services VPCs.",
        "Create a transit gateway. Peer each VPC to the transit gateway. Turn off cross-AZ load balancing on the transit gateway. Use Regional DNS names for the NLB in the services VPCs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 210"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has stateful security appliances that are deployed to multiple Availability Zones in a centralized shared services VPC. The AWS environment includes a transit gateway that is attached to application VPCs and the shared services VPC. The application VPCs have workloads that are deployed in private subnets across multiple Availability Zones. The stateful appliances in the shared services VPC inspect all east west (VPC-to-VPC) traffic.\n\nUsers report that inter-VPC traffic to different Availability Zones is dropping. A network engineer verified this claim by issuing Internet Control Message Protocol (ICMP) pings between workloads in different Availability Zones across the application VPCs. The network engineer has ruled out security groups, stateful device configurations and network ACLs as the cause of the dropped traffic.\n\nWhat is causing the traffic to drop?",
      "correct_answer": "Appliance mode is not enabled on the transit gateway attachment to the shared services VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The stateful appliances and the transit gateway attachments are deployed in a separate subnet in the shared services VPC.",
        "The stateful appliances and the transit gateway attachments are deployed in the same subnet in the shared services VPC.",
        "Appliance mode is not enabled on the transit gateway attachment to the application VPCs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 211"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has hundreds of Amazon EC2 instances that are running in two production VPCs across all Availability Zones in the us-east-1 Region. The production VPCs are named\n\nVPC A and VPC B.\n\nA new security regulation requires all traffic between production VPCs to be inspected before the traffic is routed to its final destination. The company deploys a new shared VPC that contains a stateful firewall appliance and a transit gateway with a VPC attachment across all VPCs to route traffic between VPC A and VPC B through the firewall appliance for inspection. During testing, the company notices that the transit gateway is dropping the traffic whenever the traffic is between two Availability Zones.\n\nWhat should a network engineer do to fix this issue with the LEAST management overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Enable transit gateway appliance mode on the VPC attachment in the shared VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "In the shared VPC, replace the VPC attachment with a VPN attachment. Create a VPN tunnel between the transit gateway and the firewall appliance. Configure BGP.",
        "Enable transit gateway appliance mode on the VPC attachment in VPC A and VPC B.",
        "In the shared VPC, configure one VPC peering connection to VPC A and another VPC peering connection to VPC B."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 212"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has deployed a critical application on a fleet of Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer. The application must always be reachable on port 443 from the public internet. The application recently had an outage that resulted from an incorrect change to the EC2 security group.\n\nA network engineer needs to automate a way to verify the network connectivity between the public internet and the EC2 instances whenever a change is made to the security group. The solution also must notify the network engineer when the change affects the connection.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a VPC Reachability Analyzer path on port 443. Specify the internet gateway of the VPC as the source. Specify the EC2 instances as the destination. Create an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topic to notify the network engineer when a change to the security group affects the connection. Create an AWS Lambda function to start Reachability Analyzer and to publish a message to the SNS topic in case the analyses fail. Create an Amazon EventBridge (Amazon CloudWatch Events) rule to invoke the Lambda function when a change to the security group occurs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Enable VPC Flow Logs on the elastic network interface of each EC2 instance to capture REJECT traffic on port 443. Publish the flow log records to a log group in Amazon CloudWatch Logs. Create a CloudWatch Logs metric filter for the log group for rejected traffic. Create an alarm to notify the network engineer.",
        "Enable VPC Flow Logs on the elastic network interface of each EC2 instance to capture all traffic on port 443. Publish the flow log records to a log group in Amazon CloudWatch Logs. Create a CloudWatch Logs metric filter for the log group for all traffic. Create an alarm to notify the network engineer",
        "Create a VPC Reachability Analyzer path on port 443. Specify the security group as the source. Specify the EC2 instances as the destination. Create an Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) topic to notify the network engineer when a change to the security group affects the connection. Create an AWS Lambda function to start Reachability Analyzer and to publish a message to the SNS topic in case the analyses fail Create an Amazon EventBridge (Amazon CloudWatch Events) rule to invoke the Lambda function when a change to the security group occurs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 213"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A security team is performing an audit of a company's AWS deployment. The security team is concerned that two applications might be accessing resources that should be blocked by network ACLs and security groups. The applications are deployed across two Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) clusters that use the Amazon VPC Container Network Interface (CNI) plugin for Kubernetes. The clusters are in separate subnets within the same VPC and have a Cluster Autoscaler configured.\n\nThe security team needs to determine which POD IP addresses are communicating with which services throughout the VPC. The security team wants to limit the number of flow logs and wants to examine the traffic from only the two applications.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Create VPC flow logs in a custom format. Set the application subnets as resources. Include the pkt-srcaddr field and the pkt-dstaddr field in the flow logs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create VPC flow logs in the default format. Create a filter to gather flow logs only from the EKS nodes. Include the srcaddr field and the dstaddr field in the flow logs.",
        "Create VPC flow logs in a custom format. Set the EKS nodes as the resource Include the pkt-srcaddr field and the pkt-dstaddr field in the flow logs.",
        "Create VPC flow logs in a custom format. Create a filter to gather flow logs only from the EKS nodes. Include the pkt-srcaddr field and the pkt-dstaddr field in the flow logs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 214"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A data analytics company has a 100-node high performance computing (HPC) cluster. The HPC cluster is for parallel data processing and is hosted in a VPC in the AWS Cloud. As part of the data processing workflow, the HPC cluster needs to perform several DNS queries to resolve and connect to Amazon RDS databases, Amazon S3 buckets, and on-premises data stores that are accessible through AWS Direct Connect. The HPC cluster can increase in size by five to seven times during the company’s peak event at the end of the year.\n\nThe company is using two Amazon EC2 instances as primary DNS servers for the VPC. The EC2 instances are configured to forward queries to the default VPC resolver for Amazon Route 53 hosted domains and to the on-premises DNS servers for other on-premises hosted domain names. The company notices job failures and finds that DNS queries from the HPC cluster nodes failed when the nodes tried to resolve RDS and S3 bucket endpoints.\n\nWhich architectural change should a network engineer implement to provide the DNS service in the MOST scalable way?",
      "correct_answer": "Create Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoints. Create Route 53 Resolver rules to forward queries to on-premises DNS servers for on premises hosted domain names. Reconfigure the HPC cluster nodes to use the default VPC resolver instead of the EC2 instance-based DNS servers. Terminate the EC2 instances.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Scale out the DNS service by adding two additional EC2 instances in the VPC. Reconfigure half of the HPC cluster nodes to use these new DNS servers. Plan to scale out by adding additional EC2 instance-based DNS servers in the future as the HPC cluster size grows.",
        "Scale up the existing EC2 instances that the company is using as DNS servers. Change the instance size to the largest possible instance size to accommodate the current DNS load and the anticipated load in the future.",
        "Create Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoints. Create rules on the on-premises DNS servers to forward queries to the default VPC resolver. Reconfigure the HPC cluster nodes to forward all DNS queries to the on-premises DNS servers. Terminate the EC2 instances."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 215"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company's network engineer is designing an active-passive connection to AWS from two on-premises data centers. The company has set up AWS Direct Connect connections between the on-premises data centers and AWS. From each location, the company is using a transit VIF that connects to a Direct Connect gateway that is associated with a transit gateway.\n\nThe network engineer must ensure that traffic from AWS to the data centers is routed first to the primary data center. The traffic should be routed to the failover data center only in the case of an outage.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Set the BGP community tag for all prefixes from the primary data center to 7224:7300. Set the BGP community tag for all prefixes from the failover data center to 7224:7100",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set the BGP community tag for all prefixes from the primary data center to 7224:7100. Set the BGP community tag for all prefixes from the failover data center to 7224:7300",
        "Set the BGP community tag for all prefixes from the primary data center to 7224:9300. Set the BGP community tag for all prefixes from the failover data center to 7224:9100",
        "Set the BGP community tag for all prefixes from the primary data center to 7224:9100. Set the BGP community tag for all prefixes from the failover data center to 7224:9300"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 216"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A real estate company is building an internal application so that real estate agents can upload photos and videos of various properties. The application will store these photos and videos in an Amazon S3 bucket as objects and will use Amazon DynamoDB to store corresponding metadata. The S3 bucket will be configured to publish all PUT events for new object uploads to an Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) queue.\n\nA compute cluster of Amazon EC2 instances will poll the SQS queue to find out about newly uploaded objects. The cluster will retrieve new objects, perform proprietary image and video recognition and classification update metadata in DynamoDB and replace the objects with new watermarked objects. The company does not want public IP addresses on the EC2 instances.\n\nWhich networking design solution will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively as application usage increases?",
      "correct_answer": "Place the EC2 instances in a private subnet. Create an interface VPC endpoint for Amazon SQS. Create gateway VPC endpoints for Amazon S3 and DynamoDB.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Place the EC2 instances in a public subnet. Disable the Auto-assign Public IP option while launching the EC2 instances. Create an internet gateway. Attach the internet gateway to the VPC. In the public subnet's route table, add a default route that points to the internet gateway.",
        "Place the EC2 instances in a private subnet. Create a NAT gateway in a public subnet in the same Availability Zone. Create an internet gateway. Attach the internet gateway to the VPC. In the public subnet's route table, add a default route that points to the internet gateway",
        "Place the EC2 instances in a private subnet. Create a gateway VPC endpoint for Amazon SQS. Create interface VPC endpoints for Amazon S3 and DynamoDB."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 217"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses a 4 Gbps AWS Direct Connect dedicated connection with a link aggregation group (LAG) bundle to connect to five VPCs that are deployed in the us-east-1 Region. Each VPC serves a different business unit and uses its own private VIF for connectivity to the on-premises environment. Users are reporting slowness when they access resources that are hosted on AWS.\n\nA network engineer finds that there are sudden increases in throughput and that the Direct Connect connection becomes saturated at the same time for about an hour each business day. The company wants to know which business unit is causing the sudden increase in throughput. The network engineer must find out this information and implement a solution to resolve the problem.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Review the Amazon CloudWatch metrics for VirtualInterfaceBpsEgress and VirtualInterfaceBpsIngress to determine which VIF is sending the highest throughput during the period in which slowness is observed. Create a new 10 Gbps dedicated connection. Shift traffic from the existing dedicated connection to the new dedicated connection.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Review the Amazon CloudWatch metrics for VirtualInterfaceBpsEgress and VirtualInterfaceBpsIngress to determine which VIF is sending the highest throughput during the period in which slowness is observed. Upgrade the bandwidth of the existing dedicated connection to 10 Gbps.",
        "Review the Amazon CloudWatch metrics for ConnectionBpsIngress and ConnectionPpsEgress to determine which VIF is sending the highest throughput during the period in which slowness is observed. Upgrade the existing dedicated connection to a 5 Gbps hosted connection.",
        "Review the Amazon CloudWatch metrics for ConnectionBpsIngress and ConnectionPpsEgress to determine which VIF is sending the highest throughput during the period in which slowness is observed. Create a new 10 Gbps dedicated connection. Shift traffic from the existing dedicated connection to the new dedicated connection."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 218"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an AWS Direct Connect connection between its on-premises data center in the United States (US) and workloads in the us-east-1 Region. The connection uses a transit VIF to connect the data center to a transit gateway in us-east-1.\n\nThe company is opening a new office in Europe with a new on-premises data center in England. A Direct Connect connection will connect the new data center with some workloads that are running in a single VPC in the eu-west-2 Region. The company needs to connect the US data center and us-east-1 with the Europe data center and eu-west-2. A network engineer must establish full connectivity between the data centers and Regions with the lowest possible latency.\n\nHow should the network engineer design the network architecture to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Connect the VPC in eu-west-2 to a new transit gateway. Connect the Europe data center to the new transit gateway by using a Direct Connect gateway and a new transit VIF. Associate the transit gateway in us-east-1 with the same Direct Connect gateway. Enable SiteLink for both transit VIFs. Peer the two transit gateways.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Connect the VPC in eu-west-2 with the Europe data center by using a Direct Connect gateway and a private VIF. Associate the transit gateway in us-east-1 with the same Direct Connect gateway. Enable SiteLink for the transit VIF and the private VIF.",
        "Connect the VPC in eu-west-2 to a new transit gateway. Connect the Europe data center to the new transit gateway by using a Direct Connect gateway and a new transit VIF. Create a new Direct Connect gateway. Associate the transit gateway in us-east-1 with the new Direct Connect gateway. Enable SiteLink for both transit VIFs. Peer the two transit gateways.",
        "Connect the VPC in eu-west-2 with the Europe data center by using a Direct Connect gateway and a private VIF. Create a new Direct Connect gateway. Associate the transit gateway in us-east-1 with the new Direct Connect gateway. Enable SiteLink for the transit VIF and the private VIF."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 219"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer has deployed an Amazon EC2 instance in a private subnet in a VPC. The VPC has no public subnet. The EC2 instance hosts application code that sends messages to an Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) queue. The subnet has the default network ACL with no modification applied. The EC2 instance has the default security group with no modification applied.\n\nThe SQS queue is not receiving messages.\n\nWhich of the following are possible causes of this problem? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "The EC2 instance is not attached to an IAM role that allows write operations to Amazon SQS.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The security group is blocking traffic to the IP address range used by Amazon SQS",
        "The network ACL is blocking return traffic from Amazon SQS",
        "There is no route configured in the subnet route table for the IP address range used by Amazon SQS"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "There is no interface VPC endpoint configured for Amazon SQS",
        "code": "Question 220"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer needs to standardize a company's approach to centralizing and managing interface VPC endpoints for private communication with AWS services. The company uses AWS Transit Gateway for inter-VPC connectivity between AWS accounts through a hub-and-spoke model. The company's network services team must manage all Amazon Route 53 zones and interface endpoints within a shared services AWS account. The company wants to use this centralized model to provide AWS resources with access to AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) without sending traffic over the public internet.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "In the shared services account, create an interface endpoint for AWS KMS. Modify the interface endpoint by disabling the private DNS name. Create a private hosted zone in the shared services account with an alias record that points to the interface endpoint. Associate the private hosted zone with the spoke VPCs in each AWS account.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "In the shared services account, create an interface endpoint for AWS KMS. Modify the interface endpoint by disabling the private DNS name. Create a private hosted zone in each spoke AWS account with an alias record that points to the interface endpoint. Associate each private hosted zone with the shared services AWS account.",
        "In each spoke AWS account, create an interface endpoint for AWS KMS. Modify each interface endpoint by disabling the private DNS name. Create a private hosted zone in each spoke AWS account with an alias record that points to each interface endpoint. Associate each private hosted zone with the shared services AWS account.",
        "In each spoke AWS account, create an interface endpoint for AWS KMS. Modify each interface endpoint by disabling the private DNS name. Create a private hosted zone in the shared services account with an alias record that points to each interface endpoint. Associate the private hosted zone with the spoke VPCs in each AWS account."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 221"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A development team is building a new web application in the AWS Cloud. The main company domain, example.com, is currently hosted in an Amazon Route 53 public hosted zone in one of the company's production AWS accounts.\n\nThe developers want to test the web application in the company's staging AWS account by using publicly resolvable subdomains under the example.com domain with the ability to create and delete DNS records as needed. Developers have full access to Route 53 hosted zones within the staging account, but they are prohibited from accessing resources in any of the production AWS accounts.\n\nWhich combination of steps should a network engineer take to allow the developers to create records under the example com domain? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create a staging example.com NS record in the example.com domain. Populate the value with the name servers from the staging.example.com domain. Set the routing policy type to simple routing.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a public hosted zone for example com in the staging account",
        "Create a private hosted zone for staging example com in the staging account.",
        "Create an example com NS record in the staging example.com domain. Populate the value with the name servers from the example.com domain. Set the routing policy type to simple routing."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create a public hosted zone for staging.example.com in the staging account.",
        "code": "Question 222"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company plans to deploy a two-tier web application to a new VPC in a single AWS Region. The company has configured the VPC with an internet gateway and four subnets. Two of the subnets are public and have default routes that point to the internet gateway. Two of the subnets are private and share a route table that does not have a default route.\n\nThe application will run on a set of Amazon EC2 instances that will be deployed behind an external Application Load Balancer. The EC2 instances must not be directly accessible from the internet. The application will use an Amazon S3 bucket in the same Region to store data. The application will invoke S3 GET API operations and S3 PUT API operations from the EC2 instances. A network engineer must design a VPC architecture that minimizes data transfer cost.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy the EC2 instances in the private subnets. Create an S3 gateway endpoint in the VPSpecify die route table of the private subnets during endpoint creation to create routes to Amazon S3.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy the EC2 instances in the public subnets. Create an S3 interface endpoint in the VPC. Modify the application configuration to use the S3 endpoint-specific DNS hostname.",
        "Deploy the EC2 instances in the private subnets. Create a NAT gateway in the VPC. Create default routes in the private subnets to the NAT gateway. Connect to Amazon S3 by using the NAT gateway.",
        "Deploy the EC2 instances in the private subnets. Create an S3 interface endpoint in the VPC. Modify the application configuration to use the S3 endpoint-specific DNS hostname."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 223"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has two AWS accounts one for Production and one for Connectivity. A network engineer needs to connect the Production account VPC to a transit gateway in the Connectivity account. The feature to auto accept shared attachments is not enabled on the transit gateway.\n\nWhich set of steps should the network engineer follow in each AWS account to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "1. In the Connectivity account: Create a resource share in AWS Resource Access Manager for the transit gateway. Provide the Production account ID Enable the feature to allow external accounts. 2. In the Production account: Accept the resource. 3. In the Production account: Create an attachment to the VPC subnets. 4. In the Connectivity account: Accept the attachment. Associate a route table with the attachment.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1. In the Production account: Create a resource share in AWS Resource Access Manager for the transit gateway. Provide the Connectivity account ID. Enable the feature to allow external accounts 2. In the Connectivity account: Accept the resource. 3. In the Connectivity account: Create an attachment to the VPC subnets. 4. In the Production account: Accept the attachment. Associate a route table with the attachment.",
        "1. In the Production account: Create a resource share in AWS Resource Access Manager for the VPC subnets. Provide the Connectivity account ID. Enable the feature to allow external accounts. 2. In the Connectivity account: Accept the resource. 3. In the Production account: Create an attachment on the transit gateway to the VPC subnets. 4. In the Connectivity account: Accept the attachment. Associate a route table with the attachment.",
        "1. In the Connectivity account: Create a resource share in AWS Resource Access Manager for the VPC subnets. Provide the Production account ID. Enable the feature to allow external accounts. 2. In the Production account: Accept the resource. 3. In the Connectivity account: Create an attachment on the transit gateway to the VPC subnets. 4. In the Production account: Accept the attachment. Associate a route table with the attachment."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 224"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is running multiple workloads on Amazon EC2 instances in public subnets. In a recent incident, an attacker exploited an application vulnerability on one of the EC2 instances to gain access to the instance. The company fixed the application and launched a replacement EC2 instance that contains the updated application.\n\nThe attacker used the compromised application to spread malware over the internet. The company became aware of the compromise through a notification from AWS. The company needs the ability to identify when an application that is deployed on an EC2 instance is spreading malware.\n\nWhich solution will meet this requirement with the LEAST operational effort?",
      "correct_answer": "Use Amazon GuardDuty to analyze traffic patterns by inspecting DNS requests and VPC flow logs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use Amazon GuardDuty to deploy AWS managed decoy systems that are equipped with the most recent malware signatures.",
        "Set up a Gateway Load Balancer. Run an intrusion detection system (IDS) appliance from AWS Marketplace on Amazon EC2 for traffic inspection.",
        "Configure Amazon Inspector to perform deep packet inspection of outgoing traffic."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 225"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company deploys a new web application on Amazon EC2 instances. The application runs in private subnets in three Availability Zones behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). Security auditors require encryption of all connections. The company uses Amazon Route 53 for DNS and uses AWS Certificate Manager (ACM) to automate SSL/TLS certificate provisioning. SSL/TLS connections are terminated on the ALB.\n\nThe company tests the application with a single EC2 instance and does not observe any problems. However, after production deployment, users report that they can log in but that they cannot use the application. Every new web request restarts the login process.\n\nWhat should a network engineer do to resolve this issue?",
      "correct_answer": "Modify the ALB target group configuration by enabling the stickiness attribute. Use an application-based cookie. Set the duration to the maximum application session length.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Modify the ALB listener configuration. Edit the rule that forwards traffic to the target group. Change the rule to enable group-level stickiness. Set the duration to the maximum application session length.",
        "Replace the ALB with a Network Load Balancer. Create a TLS listener. Create a new target group with the protocol type set to TLS Register the EC2 instances. Modify the target group configuration by enabling the stickiness attribute.",
        "Remove the ALB. Create an Amazon Route 53 rule with a failover routing policy for the application name. Configure ACM to issue certificates for each EC2 instance."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 226"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company recently migrated its Amazon EC2 instances to VPC private subnets to satisfy a security compliance requirement. The EC2 instances now use a NAT gateway for internet access. After the migration, some long-running database queries from private EC2 instances to a publicly accessible third-party database no longer receive responses. The database query logs reveal that the queries successfully completed after 7 minutes but that the client EC2 instances never received the response.\n\nWhich configuration change should a network engineer implement to resolve this issue?",
      "correct_answer": "Enable TCP keepalive on the client EC2 instances with a value of less than 300 seconds.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure the NAT gateway timeout to allow connections for up to 600 seconds.",
        "Enable enhanced networking on the client EC2 instances.",
        "Close idle TCP connections through the NAT gateway."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 227"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses AWS Direct Connect to connect its corporate network to multiple VPCs in the same AWS account and the same AWS Region. Each VPC uses its own private VIF and its own virtual LAN on the Direct Connect connection. The company has grown and will soon surpass the limit of VPCs and private VIFs for each connection.\n\nWhat is the MOST scalable way to add VPCs with on-premises connectivity?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a transit gateway, and attach the VPCs. Create a Direct Connect gateway, and associate it with the transit gateway. Create a transit VIF to the Direct Connect gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Provision a new Direct Connect connection to handle the additional VPCs. Use the new connection to connect additional VPCs.",
        "Create virtual private gateways for each VPC that is over the service quota. Use AWS Site-to-Site VPN to connect the virtual private gateways to the corporate network.",
        "Create a Direct Connect gateway, and add virtual private gateway associations to the VPCs. Configure a private VIF to connect to the corporate network."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 228"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A software-as-a-service (SaaS) provider hosts its solution on Amazon EC2 instances within a VPC in the AWS Cloud. All of the provider's customers also have their environments in the AWS Cloud.\n\nA recent design meeting revealed that the customers have IP address overlap with the provider's AWS deployment. The customers have stated that they will not share their internal IP addresses and that they do not want to connect to the provider's SaaS service over the internet.\n\nWhich combination of steps is part of a solution that meets these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy the SaaS service endpoint behind a Network Load Balancer.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy the SaaS service endpoint behind an Application Load Balancer.",
        "Configure a VPC peering connection to the customer VPCs. Route traffic through NAT gateways.",
        "Deploy an AWS Transit Gateway, and connect the SaaS VPC to it. Share the transit gateway with the customers. Configure routing on the transit gateway."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Configure an endpoint service, and grant the customers permission to create a connection to the endpoint service.",
        "code": "Question 229"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer is designing a hybrid architecture that uses a 1 Gbps AWS Direct Connect connection between the company's data center and two AWS Regions: us-east-1 and eu-west-1. The VPCs in us-east-1 are connected by a transit gateway and need to access several on-premises databases. According to company policy, only one VPC in eu-west-1 can be connected to one on-premises server. The on-premises network segments the traffic between the databases and the server.\n\nHow should the network engineer set up the Direct Connect connection to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create one dedicated connection. Use a transit VIF to connect to the transit gateway in us-east-1. Use a private VIF to connect to the VPC in eu-west-1. Use two Direct Connect gateways, one for each VIF, to route from the Direct Connect locations to the corresponding AWS Region along the path that has the lowest latency.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create one hosted connection. Use a transit VIF to connect to the transit gateway in us-east-1. Use a private VIF to connect to the VPC in eu-west-1. Use one Direct. Connect gateway for both VIFs to route from the Direct Connect locations to the corresponding AWS Region along the path that has the lowest latency.",
        "Create one hosted connection. Use a transit VIF to connect to the transit gateway in us-east-1. Use a private VIF to connect to the VPC in eu-west-1. Use two Direct Connect gateways, one for each VIF, to route from the Direct Connect locations to the corresponding AWS Region along the path that has the lowest latency.",
        "Create one dedicated connection. Use a transit VIF to connect to the transit gateway in us-east-1. Use a private VIF to connect to the VPC in eu-west-1. Use one Direct Connect gateway for both VIFs to route from the Direct Connect locations to the corresponding AWS Region along the path that has the lowest latency."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 230"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has deployed an application in a VPC that uses a NAT gateway for outbound traffic to the internet. A network engineer notices a large quantity of suspicious network traffic that is traveling from the VPC over the internet to IP addresses that are included on a deny list. The network engineer must implement a solution to determine which AWS resources are generating the suspicious traffic. The solution must minimize cost and administrative overhead.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use VPC flow logs. Publish the flow logs to a log group in Amazon CloudWatch Logs. Use CloudWatch Logs Insights to query the flow logs to identify the AWS resources that are generating the suspicious traffic.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Launch an Amazon EC2 instance in the VPC. Use Traffic Mirroring by specifying the NAT gateway as the source and the EC2 instance as the destination. Analyze the captured traffic by using open-source tools to identify the AWS resources that are generating the suspicious traffic.",
        "Use VPC flow logs. Launch a security information and event management (SIEM) solution in the VPC. Configure the SIEM solution to ingest the VPC flow logs. Run queries on the SIEM solution to identify the AWS resources that are generating the suspicious traffic.",
        "Configure the VPC to stream the network traffic directly to an Amazon Kinesis data stream. Send the data from the Kinesis data stream to an Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose delivery stream to store the data in Amazon S3. Use Amazon Athena to query the data to identify the AWS resources that are generating the suspicious traffic."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 231"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has its production VPC (VPC-A) in the eu-west-1 Region in Account 1. VPC-A is attached to a transit gateway (TGW-A) that is connected to an on-premises data center in Dublin, Ireland, by an AWS Direct Connect transit VIF that is configured for an AWS Direct Connect gateway. The company also has a staging VPC (VPC-B) that is attached to another transit gateway (TGW-B) in the eu-west-2 Region in Account 2.\n\nA network engineer must implement connectivity between VPC-B and the on-premises data center in Dublin.\n\nWhich solutions will meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Associate TGW-B with the Direct Connect gateway. Advertise the VPC-B CIDR block under the allowed prefixes.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure inter-Region VPC peering between VPC-A and VPC-B. Add the required VPC peering routes. Add the VPC-B CIDR block in the allowed prefixes on the Direct Connect gateway association.",
        "Configure another transit VIF on the Direct Connect connection and associate TGW-B. Advertise the VPC-B CIDR block under the allowed prefixes.",
        "Configure an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection over the transit VIF to TGW-B as a VPN attachment."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Configure inter-Region transit gateway peering between TGW-A and TGW-B. Add the peering routes in the transit gateway route tables. Add both the VPC-A and the VPC-B CIDR block under the allowed prefix list in the Direct Connect gateway association.",
        "code": "Question 232"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company’s network engineer is designing a hybrid DNS solution for an AWS Cloud workload. Individual teams want to manage their own DNS hostnames for their applications in their development environment. The solution must integrate the application-specific hostnames with the centrally managed DNS hostnames from the on-premises network and must provide bidirectional name resolution. The solution also must minimize management overhead.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network engineer take to meet these requirements? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Use an Amazon Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Modify the DHCP options set by setting a custom DNS server value.",
        "Create DNS proxy servers.",
        "Set up a zone transfer between Amazon Route 53 and the on-premises DNS."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Use an Amazon Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoint.||Create Amazon Route 53 private hosted zones.",
        "code": "Question 233"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company hosts a web application on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). The ALB is the origin in an Amazon CloudFront distribution. The company wants to implement a custom authentication system that will provide a token for its authenticated customers.\n\nThe web application must ensure that the GET/POST requests come from authenticated customers before it delivers the content. A network engineer must design a solution that gives the web application the ability to identify authorized customers.\n\nWhat is the MOST operationally efficient solution that meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use an AWS Lambda@Edge function to inspect the authorized token inside the GET/POST request payload. Use the Lambda@Edge function also to insert a customized header to inform the web application of an authenticated customer request.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use the ALB to inspect the authorized token inside the GET/POST request payload. Use an AWS Lambda function to insert a customized header to inform the web application of an authenticated customer request.",
        "Integrate AWS WAF with the ALB to inspect the authorized token inside the GET/POST request payload. Configure the ALB listener to insert a customized header to inform the web application of an authenticated customer request.",
        "Set up an EC2 instance that has a third-party packet inspection tool to inspect the authorized token inside the GET/POST request payload. Configure the tool to insert a customized header to inform the web application of an authenticated customer request."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 234"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has created three VPCs: a production VPC, a nonproduction VPC, and a shared services VPC. The production VPC and the nonproduction VPC must each have communication with the shared services VPC. There must be no communication between the production VPC and the nonproduction VPC. A transit gateway is deployed to facilitate communication between VPCs.\n\nWhich route table configurations on the transit gateway will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure a route table with the production and nonproduction VPC attachments associated with propagated routes for only the shared services VPC. Create an additional route table with only the shared services VPC attachment associated with propagated routes from the production and nonproduction VPCs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure a route table with the production and nonproduction VPC attachments associated with propagated routes for each VPC. Create an additional route table with only the shared services VPC attachment associated with propagated routes from each VPC.",
        "Configure a route table with all the VPC attachments associated with propagated routes for only the shared services VPCreate an additional route table with only the shared services VPC attachment associated with propagated routes from the production and nonproduction VPCs.",
        "Configure a route table with the production and nonproduction VPC attachments associated with propagated routes disabled. Create an additional route table with only the shared services VPC attachment associated with propagated routes from the production and nonproduction VPCs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 235"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection from the company's on-premises data center to a virtual private gateway in the AWS Cloud Because of congestion, the company is experiencing availability and performance issues as traffic travels across the internet before the traffic reaches AWS. A network engineer must reduce these issues for the connection as quickly as possible with minimum administration effort.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure a transit gateway in the same AWS Region as the existing virtual private gateway. Create a new accelerated Site-to-Site VPN connection. Connect the new connection to the transit gateway by using a VPN attachment. Update the customer gateway device to use the new Site to Site VPN connection. Delete the existing Site-to-Site VPN connection",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Edit the existing Site-to-Site VPN connection by enabling acceleration. Stop and start the VPN service on the customer gateway for the new setting to take effect.",
        "Create a new accelerated Site-to-Site VPN connection. Connect the new Site-to-Site VPN connection to the existing virtual private gateway. Update the customer gateway device to use the new Site-to-Site VPN connection. Delete the existing Site-to-Site VPN connection.",
        "Create a new AWS Direct Connect connection with a private VIF between the on-premises data center and the AWS Cloud. Update the customer gateway device to use the new Direct Connect connection. Delete the existing Site-to-Site VPN connection."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 236"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An Australian ecommerce company hosts all of its services in the AWS Cloud and wants to expand its customer base to the United States (US). The company is targeting the western US for the expansion.\n\nThe company’s existing AWS architecture consists of four AWS accounts with multiple VPCs deployed in the ap-southeast-2 Region. All VPCs are attached to a transit gateway in ap-southeast-2. There are dedicated VPCs for each application service. The company also has VPCs for centralized security features such as proxies, firewalls, and logging.\n\nThe company plans to duplicate the infrastructure from ap-southeast-2 to the us-west-1 Region. A network engineer must establish connectivity between the various applications in the two Regions. The solution must maximize bandwidth, minimize latency and minimize operational overhead.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Peer the transit gateways in each Region. Configure routing between the two transit gateways for each Region's IP addresses.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create VPN attachments between the two transit gateways. Configure the VPN attachments to use BGP routing between the two transit gateways.",
        "Create a VPN server in a VPC in each Region. Update the routing to point to the VPN servers for the IP addresses in alternate Regions.",
        "Attach the VPCs in us-west-1 to the transit gateway in ap-southeast-2."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 237"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An IoT company sells hardware sensor modules that periodically send out temperature, humidity, pressure, and location data through the MQTT messaging protocol. The hardware sensor modules send this data to the company's on-premises MQTT brokers that run on Linux servers behind a load balancer. The hardware sensor modules have been hardcoded with public IP addresses to reach the brokers.\n\nThe company is growing and is acquiring customers across the world. The existing solution can no longer scale and is introducing additional latency because of the company's global presence. As a result, the company decides to migrate its entire infrastructure from on premises to the AWS Cloud. The company needs to migrate without reconfiguring the hardware sensor modules that are already deployed across the world. The solution also must minimize latency.\n\nThe company migrates the MQTT brokers to run on Amazon EC2 instances.\n\nWhat should the company do next to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Place the EC2 instances behind a Network Load Balancer (NLB). Configure TCP listeners. Create an AWS Global Accelerator accelerator in front of the NLUse Bring Your Own IP (BYOIP) from the on-premises network with Global Accelerator.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Place the EC2 instances behind a Network Load Balancer (NLB). Configure TCP listeners. Use Bring Your Own IP (BYOIP) from the on-premises network with the NLB.",
        "Place the EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). Configure TCP listeners. Create an AWS Global Accelerator accelerator in front of the ALB. Use Bring Your Own IP (BYOIP) from the on-premises network with Global Accelerator",
        "Place the EC2 instances behind an Amazon CloudFront distribution. Use Bring Your Own IP (BYOIP) from the on-premises network with CloudFront."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 238"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has deployed a web application on AWS. The web application uses an Application Load Balancer (ALB) across multiple Availability Zones. The targets of the ALB are AWS Lambda functions. The web application also uses Amazon CloudWatch metrics for monitoring.\n\nUsers report that parts of the web application are not loading properly. A network engineer needs to troubleshoot the problem. The network engineer enables access logging for the ALB.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do next to determine which errors the ALB is receiving?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure the Amazon S3 bucket destination. Use Amazon Athena to determine which error messages the ALB is receiving.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Send the logs to Amazon CloudWatch Logs. Review the ALB logs in CloudWatch Insights to determine which error messages the ALB is receiving.",
        "Configure the Amazon S3 bucket destination. After Amazon CloudWatch Logs pulls the ALB logs from the S3 bucket automatically, review the logs in CloudWatch Logs to determine which error messages the ALB is receiving.",
        "Send the logs to Amazon CloudWatch Logs. Use the Amazon Athena CloudWatch Connector to determine which error messages the ALB is receiving."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 239"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer is designing the architecture for a healthcare company's workload that is moving to the AWS Cloud. All data to and from the on-premises environment must be encrypted in transit. All traffic also must be inspected in the cloud before the traffic is allowed to leave the cloud and travel to the on-premises environment or to the internet.\n\nThe company will expose components of the workload to the internet so that patients can reserve appointments. The architecture must secure these components and protect them against DDoS attacks. The architecture also must provide protection against financial liability for services that scale out during a DDoS event.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network engineer take to meet all these requirements for the workload? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Use AWS Direct Connect with MACsec support for connectivity to the cloud.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use Traffic Mirroring to copy all traffic to a fleet of traffic capture appliances.",
        "Set up AWS WAF on all network components.",
        "Configure an AWS Lambda function to create Deny rules in security groups to block malicious IP addresses."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Use Gateway Load Balancers to insert third-party firewalls for inline traffic inspection.||Configure AWS Shield Advanced and ensure that it is configured on all public assets.",
        "code": "Question 240"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to use Amazon S3 to archive financial data. The data is currently stored in an on-premises data center. The company uses AWS Direct Connect with a Direct Connect gateway and a transit gateway to connect to the on-premises data center. The data cannot be transported over the public internet and must be encrypted in transit.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an IPsec VPN connection over the transit VIF. Create a VPC and attach the VPC to the transit gateway. In the VPC, provision an interface VPC endpoint for Amazon S3. Use HTTPS for communication.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a Direct Connect public VIF. Set up an IPsec VPN connection over the public VIF to access Amazon S3. Use HTTPS for communication.",
        "Create a VPC and attach the VPC to the transit gateway. In the VPC, provision an interface VPC endpoint for Amazon S3. Use HTTPS for communication.",
        "Create a Direct Connect public VIF. Set up an IPsec VPN connection over the public VIF to the transit gateway. Create an attachment for Amazon S3. Use HTTPS for communication."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 241"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using Amazon Route 53 Resolver DNS Firewall in a VPC to block all domains except domains that are on an approved list. The company is concerned that if DNS Firewall is unresponsive, resources in the VPC might be affected if the network cannot resolve any DNS queries. To maintain application service level agreements, the company needs DNS queries to continue to resolve even if Route 53 Resolver does not receive a response from DNS Firewall.\n\nWhich change should a network engineer implement to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Update the DNS Firewall VPC configuration to enable fail open for the VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Update the DNS Firewall VPC configuration to disable fail open for the VPC.",
        "Create a new DHCP options set with parameter dns_firewall_fail_open=false. Associate the new DHCP options set with the VPC.",
        "Create a new DHCP options set with parameter dns_firewall_fail_open=true. Associate the new DHCP options set with the VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 242"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is migrating an existing application to a new AWS account. The company will deploy the application in a single AWS Region by using one VPC and multiple Availability Zones. The application will run on Amazon EC2 instances. Each Availability Zone will have several EC2 instances. The EC2 instances will be deployed in private subnets.\n\nThe company's clients will connect to the application by using a web browser with the HTTPS protocol. Inbound connections must be distributed across the Availability Zones and EC2 instances. All connections from the same client session must be connected to the same EC2 instance. The company must provide end-to-end encryption for all connections between the clients and the application by using the application SSL certificate.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a Network Load Balancer. Create a target group. Set the protocol to TCP and the port to 443 for the target group. Turn on session affinity (sticky sessions). Register the EC2 instances as targets. Create a listener. Set the protocol to TCP and the port to 443 for the listener. Deploy SSL certificates to the EC2 instances.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an Application Load Balancer. Create a target group. Set the protocol to HTTP and the port to 80 for the target group. Turn on session affinity (sticky sessions) with an application-based cookie policy. Register the EC2 instances as targets. Create an HTTPS listener. Set the default action to forward to the target group. Use AWS Certificate Manager (ACM) to create a certificate for the listener.",
        "Create a Network Load Balancer. Create a target group. Set the protocol to TLS and the port to 443 for the target group. Turn on session affinity (sticky sessions). Register the EC2 instances as targets. Create a listener. Set the protocol to TLS and the port to 443 for the listener. Use AWS Certificate Manager (ACM) to create a certificate for the application.",
        "Create an Application Load Balancer. Create a target group. Set the protocol to HTTPS and the port to 443 for the target group. Turn on session affinity (sticky sessions) with an application-based cookie policy. Register the EC2 instances as targets. Create an HTTP listener. Set the port to 443 for the listener. Set the default action to forward to the target group."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 243"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is developing an application in which IoT devices will report measurements to the AWS Cloud. The application will have millions of end users. The company observes that the IoT devices cannot support DNS resolution. The company needs to implement an Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling solution so that the IoT devices can connect to an application endpoint without using DNS.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Use a Network Load Balancer (NLB). Create an EC2 Auto Scaling group. Attach the Auto Scaling group to the NLB. Set up the IoT devices to connect to the IP addresses of the NLB.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use an Application Load Balancer (ALB)-type target group for a Network Load Balancer (NLB). Create an EC2 Auto Scaling group. Attach the Auto Scaling group to the ALB. Set up the IoT devices to connect to the IP addresses of the NLB.",
        "Use an AWS Global Accelerator accelerator with an Application Load Balancer (ALB) endpoint. Create an EC2 Auto Scaling group. Attach the Auto Scaling group to the ALSet up the IoT devices to connect to the IP addresses of the accelerator.",
        "Use an AWS Global Accelerator accelerator with a Network Load Balancer (NLB) endpoint. Create an EC2 Auto Scaling group. Attach the Auto Scaling group to the NLB. Set up the IoT devices to connect to the IP addresses of the accelerator."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 244"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has deployed a new web application on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). The instances are in an Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling group. Enterprise customers from around the world will use the application. Employees of these enterprise customers will connect to the application over HTTPS from office locations.\n\nThe company must configure firewalls to allow outbound traffic to only approved IP addresses. The employees of the enterprise customers must be able to access the application with the least amount of latency.\n\nWhich change should a network engineer make in the infrastructure to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new accelerator in AWS Global Accelerator. Add the ALB as an accelerator endpoint.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new Network Load Balancer (NLB). Add the ALB as a target of the NLB.",
        "Create a new Amazon CloudFront distribution. Set the ALB as the distribution’s origin.",
        "Create a new Amazon Route 53 hosted zone. Create a new record to route traffic to the ALB."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 245"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has hundreds of VPCs on AWS. All the VPCs access the public endpoints of Amazon S3 and AWS Systems Manager through NAT gateways. All the traffic from the VPCs to Amazon S3 and Systems Manager travels through the NAT gateways. The company's network engineer must centralize access to these services and must eliminate the need to use public endpoints.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a central shared services VPIn the central shared services VPC, create interface VPC endpoints for Amazon S3 and Systems Manager to access. Ensure that private DNS is turned off. Connect all the VPCs to the central shared services VPC by using AWS Transit Gateway. Create an Amazon Route 53 private hosted zone with a full service endpoint name for Amazon S3 and Systems Manager. Associate the private hosted zones with all the VPCs. Create an alias record in each private hosted zone with the full AWS service endpoint pointing to the interface VPC endpoint in the shared services VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a central egress VPC that has private NAT gateways. Connect all the VPCs to the central egress VPC by using AWS Transit Gateway. Use the private NAT gateways to connect to Amazon S3 and Systems Manager by using private IP addresses.",
        "Create a central shared services VPC. In the central shared services VPC, create interface VPC endpoints for Amazon S3 and Systems Manager to access. Ensure that private DNS is turned off. Connect all the VPCs to the central shared services VPC by using AWS Transit Gateway. Create an Amazon Route 53 forwarding rule for each interface VPC endpoint. Associate the forwarding rules with all the VPCs. Forward DNS queries to the interface VPC endpoints in the shared services VPC.",
        "Create a central shared services VPC. In the central shared services VPC, create interface VPC endpoints for Amazon S3 and Systems Manager to access. Connect all the VPCs to the central shared services VPC by using AWS Transit Gateway. Ensure that private DNS is turned on for the interface VPC endpoints and that the transit gateway is created with DNS support turned on."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 246"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company manages resources across VPCs in multiple AWS Regions. The company needs to connect to the resources by using its internal domain name. A network engineer needs to apply the aws.example.com DNS suffix to all resources.\n\nWhat must the network engineer do to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Create one Amazon Route 53 private hosted zone for aws.example.com. Associate the private hosted zone with every VPC that has resources. In the private hosted zone, create DNS records for all resources.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an Amazon Route 53 private hosted zone for aws.example.com in each Region that has resources. Associate the private hosted zone with that Region's VPC. In the appropriate private hosted zone, create DNS records for the resources in each Region.",
        "Create one Amazon Route 53 private hosted zone for aws.example.com. Configure the private hosted zone to allow zone transfers with every VPC.",
        "Create one Amazon Route 53 private hosted zone for example.com. Create a single resource record for aws.example.com in the private hosted zone. Apply a multivalue answer routing policy to the record. Add all VPC resources as separate values in the routing policy."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 247"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An insurance company is planning the migration of workloads from its on-premises data center to the AWS Cloud. The company requires end-to-end domain name resolution. Bi-directional DNS resolution between AWS and the existing on-premises environments must be established. The workloads will be migrated into multiple VPCs. The workloads also have dependencies on each other, and not all the workloads will be migrated at the same time.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure a private hosted zone for each application VPC, and create the requisite records. Create a set of Amazon Route 53 Resolver inbound and outbound endpoints in an egress VPC. Define Route 53 Resolver rules to forward requests for the on-premises domains to the on-premises DNS resolver. Associate the application VPC private hosted zones with the egress VPC, and share the Route 53 Resolver rules with the application accounts by using AWS Resource Access Manager. Configure the on-premises DNS servers to forward the cloud domains to the Route 53 inbound endpoints.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure a public hosted zone for each application VPC, and create the requisite records. Create a set of Amazon Route 53 Resolver inbound and outbound endpoints in an egress VPC. Define Route 53 Resolver rules to forward requests for the on-premises domains to the on-premises DNS resolver. Associate the application VPC private hosted zones with the egress VPC. and share the Route 53 Resolver rules with the application accounts by using AWS Resource Access Manager. Configure the on-premises DNS servers to forward the cloud domains to the Route 53 inbound endpoints.",
        "Configure a private hosted zone for each application VPC, and create the requisite records. Create a set of Amazon Route 53 Resolver inbound and outbound endpoints in an egress VPDefine Route 53 Resolver rules to forward requests for the on-premises domains to the on-premises DNS resolver. Associate the application VPC private hosted zones with the egress VPand share the Route 53 Resolver rules with the application accounts by using AWS Resource Access Manager. Configure the on-premises DNS servers to forward the cloud domains to the Route 53 outbound endpoints.",
        "Configure a private hosted zone for each application VPC, and create the requisite records. Create a set of Amazon Route 53 Resolver inbound and outbound endpoints in an egress VPC. Define Route 53 Resolver rules to forward requests for the on-premises domains to the on-premises DNS resolver. Associate the Route 53 outbound rules with the application VPCs, and share the private hosted zones with the application accounts by using AWS Resource Access Manager. Configure the on-premises DNS servers to forward the cloud domains to the Route 53 inbound endpoints."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 248"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A global company runs business applications in the us-east-1 Region inside a VPC. One of the company's regional offices in London uses a virtual private gateway for an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection tom the VPC. The company has configured a transit gateway and has set up peering between the VPC and other VPCs that various departments in the company use.\n\nEmployees at the London office are experiencing latency issues when they connect to the business applications.\n\nWhat should a network engineer do to reduce this latency?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new Site-to-Site VPN connection. Set the transit gateway as the target gateway. Enable acceleration on the new Site-to-Site VPN connection. Update the VPN device in the London office with the new connection details.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Modify the existing Site-to-Site VPN connection by setting the transit gateway as the target gateway. Enable acceleration on the existing Site-to-Site VPN connection.",
        "Create a new transit gateway in the eu-west-2 (London) Region. Peer the new transit gateway with the existing transit gateway. Modify the existing Site-to-Site VPN connection by setting the new transit gateway as the target gateway.",
        "Create a new AWS Global Accelerator standard accelerator that has an endpoint of the Site-to-Site VPN connection. Update the VPN device in the London office with the new connection details."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 249"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a hybrid cloud environment. The company’s data center is connected to the AWS Cloud by an AWS Direct Connect connection. The AWS environment includes VPCs that are connected together in a hub-and-spoke model by a transit gateway. The AWS environment has a transit VIF with a Direct Connect gateway for on-premises connectivity.\n\nThe company has a hybrid DNS model. The company has configured Amazon Route 53 Resolver endpoints in the hub VPC to allow bidirectional DNS traffic flow. The company is running a backend application in one of the VPCs.\n\nThe company uses a message-oriented architecture and employs Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) to receive messages from other applications over a private network. A network engineer wants to use an interface VPC endpoint for Amazon SQS for this architecture. Client services must be able to access the endpoint service from on premises and from multiple VPCs within the company's AWS infrastructure.\n\nWhich combination of steps should the network engineer take to ensure that the client applications can resolve DNS for the interface endpoint? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create the interface endpoint for Amazon SQS with the option for private DNS names turned off.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create the interface endpoint for Amazon SQS with the option for private DNS names turned on.",
        "Use the automatically created private hosted zone for sqs.us-east-1.amazonaws.com with previously created necessary records that point to the interface endpoint. Associate the private hosted zones with other VPCs.",
        "Access the SQS endpoint by using the public DNS name sqs.us-east-1 amazonaws.com in VPCs and on premises."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Manually create a private hosted zone for sqs.us-east-1.amazonaws.com. Add necessary records that point to the interface endpoint. Associate the private hosted zones with other VPCs.||Access the SQS endpoint by using the private DNS name of the interface endpoint .sqs.us-east-1.vpce.amazonaws.com in VPCs and on premises.",
        "code": "Question 250"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A retail company is running its service on AWS. The company’s architecture includes Application Load Balancers (ALBs) in public subnets. The ALB target groups are configured to send traffic to backend Amazon EC2 instances in private subnets. These backend EC2 instances can call externally hosted services over the internet by using a NAT gateway.\n\nThe company has noticed in its billing that NAT gateway usage has increased significantly. A network engineer needs to find out the source of this increased usage.\n\nWhich options can the network engineer use to investigate the traffic through the NAT gateway? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Enable VPC flow logs on the NAT gateway's elastic network interface. Publish the logs to a log group in Amazon CloudWatch Logs. Use CloudWatch Logs Insights to query and analyze the logs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Enable NAT gateway access logs. Publish the logs to a log group in Amazon CloudWatch Logs. Use CloudWatch Logs Insights to query and analyze the logs.",
        "Configure Traffic Mirroring on the NAT gateway's elastic network interface. Send the traffic to an additional EC2 instance. Use tools such as tcpdump and Wireshark to query and analyze the mirrored traffic.",
        "Enable NAT gateway access logs. Publish the logs to an Amazon S3 bucket. Create a custom table for the S3 bucket in Amazon Athena to describe the log structure. Use Athena to query and analyze the logs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Enable VPC flow logs on the NAT gateway's elastic network interface. Publish the logs to an Amazon S3 bucket. Create a custom table for the S3 bucket in Amazon Athena to describe the log structure. Use Athena to query and analyze the logs.",
        "code": "Question 251"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company’s network engineer builds and tests network designs for VPCs in a development account. The company needs to monitor the changes that are made to network resources and must ensure strict compliance with network security policies. The company also needs access to the historical configurations of network resources.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Record the current state of network resources by using AWS Config. Create rules that reflect the desired configuration settings. Set remediation for noncompliant resources.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an Amazon EventBridge (Amazon CloudWatch Events) rule with a custom pattern to monitor the account for changes. Configure the rule to invoke an AWS Lambda function to identify noncompliant resources. Update an Amazon DynamoDB table with the changes that are identified.",
        "Create custom metrics from Amazon CloudWatch logs. Use the metrics to invoke an AWS Lambda function to identify noncompliant resources. Update an Amazon DynamoDB table with the changes that are identified.",
        "Record the current state of network resources by using AWS Systems Manager Inventory. Use Systems Manager State Manager to enforce the desired configuration settings and to carry out remediation for noncompliant resources."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 252"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is migrating an application from on premises to AWS. The company will host the application on Amazon EC2 instances that are deployed in a single VPC. During the migration period, DNS queries from the EC2 instances must be able to resolve names of on-premises servers. The migration is expected to take 3 months After the 3-month migration period, the resolution of on-premises servers will no longer be needed.\n\nWhat should a network engineer do to meet these requirements with the LEAST amount of configuration?",
      "correct_answer": "Set up an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection between on premises and AWS. Deploy an Amazon Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoint in the Region that is hosting the VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set up an AWS Direct Connect connection with a private VIF. Deploy an Amazon Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint and a Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoint in the Region that is hosting the VPC.",
        "Set up an AWS Client VPN connection between on premises and AWS. Deploy an Amazon Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint in the VPC.",
        "Set up an AWS Direct Connect connection with a public VIF. Deploy an Amazon Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint in the Region that is hosting the VPC. Use the IP address that is assigned to the endpoint for connectivity to the on-premises DNS servers."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 253"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is hosting an application on Amazon EC2 instances behind an Application Load Balancer. The instances are in an Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling group. Because of a recent change to a security group, external users cannot access the application.\n\nA network engineer needs to prevent this downtime from happening again. The network engineer must implement a solution that remediates noncompliant changes to security groups.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure an AWS Config rule to detect inconsistencies between the desired security group configuration and the current security group configuration. Create an AWS Systems Manager Automation runbook to remediate noncompliant security groups.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure Amazon GuardDuty to detect inconsistencies between the desired security group configuration and the current security group configuration. Create an AWS Systems Manager Automation runbook to remediate noncompliant security groups.",
        "Configure an AWS Config rule to detect inconsistencies between the desired security group configuration and the current security group configuration. Configure AWS OpsWorks for Chef to remediate noncompliant security groups.",
        "Configure Amazon GuardDuty to detect inconsistencies between the desired security group configuration and the current security group configuration. Configure AWS OpsWorks for Chef to remediate noncompliant security groups."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 254"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is deploying third-party firewall appliances for traffic inspection and NAT capabilities in its VPC. The VPC is configured with private subnets and public subnets. The company needs to deploy the firewall appliances behind a load balancer.\n\nWhich architecture will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy a Gateway Load Balancer with the firewall appliances as targets. Configure the firewall appliances with two network interfaces: one network interface in a private subnet and another network interface in a public subnet. Use the NAT functionality on the firewall appliances to send the traffic to the internet after inspection.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy a Gateway Load Balancer with the firewall appliances as targets. Configure the firewall appliances with a single network interface in a private subnet. Use a NAT gateway to send the traffic to the internet after inspection.",
        "Deploy a Network Load Balancer with the firewall appliances as targets. Configure the firewall appliances with a single network interface in a private subnet. Use a NAT gateway to send the traffic to the internet after inspection.",
        "Deploy a Network Load Balancer with the firewall appliances as targets. Configure the firewall appliances with two network interfaces: one network interface in a private subnet and another network interface in a public subnet. Use the NAT functionality on the firewall appliances to send the traffic to the internet after inspection."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 255"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company's AWS architecture consists of several VPCs. The VPCs include a shared services VPC and several application VPCs. The company has established network connectivity from all VPCs to the on-premises DNS servers.\n\nApplications that are deployed in the application VPCs must be able to resolve DNS for internally hosted domains on premises. The applications also must be able to resolve local VPC domain names and domains that are hosted in Amazon Route 53 private hosted zones.\n\nWhat should a network engineer do to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoint in the shared services VPC. Create forwarding rules for the on-premises hosted domains. Associate the rules with the new Resolver endpoint and each application VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint in the shared services VPC. Create forwarding rules for the on-premises hosted domains. Associate the rules with the new Resolver endpoint and each application VPC. Update each application VPC's DHCP configuration to point DNS resolution to the new Resolver endpoint.",
        "Create a new Route 53 Resolver outbound endpoint in the shared services VPCreate forwarding rules for the on-premises hosted domains. Associate the rules with the new Resolver endpoint and each application VPUpdate each application VPC's DHCP configuration to point DNS resolution to the new Resolver endpoint.",
        "Create a new Route 53 Resolver inbound endpoint in the shared services VPC. Create forwarding rules for the on-premises hosted domains. Associate the rules with the new Resolver endpoint and each application VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 256"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has been using an outdated application layer protocol for communication among applications. The company decides not to use this protocol anymore and must migrate all applications to support a new protocol. The old protocol and the new protocol are TCP-based, but the protocols use different port numbers.\n\nAfter several months of work, the company has migrated dozens of applications that run on Amazon EC2 instances and in containers. The company believes that all the applications have been migrated, but the company wants to verify this belief. A network engineer needs to verify that no application is still using the old protocol.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements without causing any downtime?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure VPC flow logs to be delivered into an Amazon S3 bucket. Use Amazon Athena to query the data and to filter for the port number that is used by the old protocol.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use Amazon Inspector and its Network Reachability rules package. Wait until the analysis has finished running to find out which EC2 instances are still listening to the old port.",
        "Enable Amazon GuardDuty. Use the graphical visualizations to filter for traffic that uses the port of the old protocol. Exclude all internet traffic to filter out occasions when the same port is used as an ephemeral port.",
        "Inspect all security groups that are assigned to the EC2 instances that host the applications. Remove the port of the old protocol if that port is in the list of allowed ports. Verify that the applications are operating properly after the port is removed from the security groups."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 257"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has deployed its AWS environment in a single AWS Region. The environment consists of a few hundred application VPCs, a shared services VPC, and a VPN connection to the company’s on-premises environment. A network engineer needs to implement a transit gateway with the following requirements:\n\n• Application VPCs must be isolated from each other.\n\n• Bidirectional communication must be allowed between the application VPCs and the on-premises network.\n\n• Bidirectional communication must be allowed between the application VPCs and the shared services VPC.\n\nThe network engineer creates the transit gateway with options disabled for default route table association and default route table propagation. The network engineer also creates the VPN attachment for the on-premises network and creates the VPC attachments for the application VPCs and the shared services VPC.\n\nThe network engineer must meet all the requirements for the transit gateway by designing a solution that needs the least number of transit gateway route tables.\n\nWhich combination of actions should the network engineer perform to accomplish this goal? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Configure a separate transit gateway route table for all application VPCs. Associate all application VPCs with this transit gateway route table. Propagate the shared services VPC attachment and the VPN attachment to this transit gateway route table.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure a separate transit gateway route table for on premises. Associate the VPN attachment with this transit gateway route table. Propagate all application VPC attachments to this transit gateway route table.",
        "Configure a separate transit gateway route table for each application VPC. Associate each application VPC attachment with its respective transit gateway route table. Propagate the shared services VPC attachment and the VPN attachment to this transit gateway route table.",
        "Configure a separate transit gateway route table for the shared services VPC. Associate the shared services VPC attachment with this transit gateway route table. Propagate all application VPC attachments to this transit gateway route table."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Configure a separate transit gateway route table for on premises and the shared services VPC. Associate the VPN attachment and the shared services VPC attachment with this transit gateway route table. Propagate all application VPC attachments to this transit gateway route table.",
        "code": "Question 258"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection between its existing VPC and on-premises network. The default DHCP options set is associated with the VPC. The company has an application that is running on an Amazon Linux 2 Amazon EC2 instance in the VPC. The application must retrieve an Amazon RDS database secret that is stored in AWS Secrets Manager through a private VPC endpoint. An on-premises application provides internal RESTful API service that can be reached by URL (https://api.example.internal). Two on-premises Windows DNS servers provide internal DNS resolution.\n\nThe application on the EC2 instance needs to call the internal API service that is deployed in the on-premises environment. When the application on the EC2 instance attempts to call the internal API service by referring to the hostname that is assigned to the service, the call fails. When a network engineer tests the API service call from the same EC2 instance by using the API service's IP address, the call is successful.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to resolve this issue and prevent the same problem from affecting other resources in the VPC?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an Amazon Route 53 Resolver rule. Associate the rule with the VPC. Configure the rule to forward DNS queries to the on-premises Windows DNS servers if the domain name matches example.internal.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a new DHCP options set that specifies the on-premises Windows DNS servers. Associate the new DHCP options set with the existing VPC. Reboot the Amazon Linux 2 EC2 instance.",
        "Modify the local host file in the Amazon Linux 2 EC2 instance in the VPMap the service domain name (api.example.internal) to the IP address of the internal API service.",
        "Modify the local /etc/resolv.conf file in the Amazon Linux 2 EC2 instance in the VPC. Change the IP addresses of the name servers in the file to the IP addresses of the company's on-premises Windows DNS servers."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 259"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has several production applications across different accounts in the AWS Cloud. The company operates from the us-east-1 Region only. Only certain partner companies can access the applications. The applications are running on Amazon EC2 instances that are in an Auto Scaling group behind an Application Load Balancer (ALB). The EC2 instances are in private subnets and allow traffic only from the ALB. The ALB is in a public subnet and allows inbound traffic only from partner network IP address ranges over port 80.\n\nWhen the company adds a new partner, the company must allow the IP address range of the partner network in the security group that is associated with the ALB in each account. A network engineer must implement a solution to centrally manage the partner network IP address ranges.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements in the MOST operationally efficient manner?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a new prefix list. Add all allowed IP address ranges to the prefix list. Share the prefix list across different accounts by using AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM). Update security groups to use the prefix list instead of the partner IP address range. Update the prefix list with the new IP address range when the company adds a new partner.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an Amazon DynamoDB table to maintain all IP address ranges and security groups that need to be updated. Update the DynamoDB table with the new IP address range when the company adds a new partner. Invoke an AWS Lambda function to read new IP address ranges and security groups from the DynamoDB table to update the security groups. Deploy this solution in all accounts.",
        "Create a new prefix list. Add all allowed IP address ranges to the prefix list. Use Amazon EventBridge (Amazon CloudWatch Events) rules to invoke an AWS Lambda function to update security groups whenever a new IP address range is added to the prefix list. Deploy this solution in all accounts.",
        "Create an Amazon S3 bucket to maintain all IP address ranges and security groups that need to be updated. Update the S3 bucket with the new IP address range when the company adds a new partner. Invoke an AWS Lambda function to read new IP address ranges and security groups from the S3 bucket to update the security groups. Deploy this solution in all accounts."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 260"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses a 1 Gbps AWS Direct Connect connection to connect its AWS environment to its on-premises data center. The connection provides employees with access to an application VPC that is hosted on AWS. Many remote employees use a company-provided VPN to connect to the data center. These employees are reporting slowness when they access the application during business hours. On-premises users have started to report similar slowness while they are in the office.\n\nThe company plans to build an additional application on AWS. On-site and remote employees will use the additional application. After the deployment of this additional application, the company will need 20% more bandwidth than the company currently uses. With the increased usage, the company wants to add resiliency to the AWS connectivity. A network engineer must review the current implementation and must make improvements within a limited budget.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection to the application VPC. Configure the on-premises routing for the remote employees to connect to the Site-to-Site VPN connection.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set up a new 1 Gbps Direct Connect dedicated connection to accommodate the additional traffic load from remote employees and the additional application. Create a link aggregation group (LAG).",
        "Deploy Amazon Workspaces into the application VPInstruct the remote employees to connect to Workspaces.",
        "Replace the existing 1 Gbps Direct Connect connection with two new 2 Gbps Direct Connect hosted connections. Create an AWS Client VPN endpoint in the application VPC. Instruct the remote employees to connect to the Client VPN endpoint."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 261"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A banking company is successfully operating its public mobile banking stack on AWS. The mobile banking stack is deployed in a VPC that includes private subnets and public subnets. The company is using IPv4 networking and has not deployed or supported IPv6 in the environment. The company has decided to adopt a third-party service provider's API and must integrate the API with the existing environment. The service provider’s API requires the use of IPv6.\n\nA network engineer must turn on IPv6 connectivity for the existing workload that is deployed in a private subnet. The company does not want to permit IPv6 traffic from the public internet and mandates that the company's servers must initiate all IPv6 connectivity. The network engineer turns on IPv6 in the VPC and in the private subnets.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an egress-only Internet gateway in the VPAdd a route to the existing subnet route tables to point IPv6 traffic to the egress-only internet gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an internet gateway and a NAT gateway in the VPC. Add a route to the existing subnet route tables to point IPv6 traffic to the NAT gateway.",
        "Create an internet gateway and a NAT instance in the VPC. Add a route to the existing subnet route tables to point IPv6 traffic to the NAT instance.",
        "Create an egress-only internet gateway in the VPC. Configure a security group that denies all inbound traffic. Associate the security group with the egress-only internet gateway."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 262"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a global network and is using transit gateways to connect AWS Regions together. The company finds that two Amazon EC2 instances in different Regions are unable to communicate with each other. A network engineer needs to troubleshoot this connectivity issue.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Use AWS Network Manager Route Analyzer to analyze routes in the transit gateway route tables. Verify that the VPC route tables are correct. Use VPC flow logs to analyze the IP traffic that security group rules and network ACL rules accept or reject in the VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use AWS Network Manager Route Analyzer to analyze routes in the transit gateway route tables and in the VPC route tables. Use VPC flow logs to analyze the IP traffic that security group rules and network ACL rules accept or reject in the VPC.",
        "Use AWS Network Manager Route Analyzer to analyze routes in the transit gateway route tables. Verify that the VPC route tables are correct. Use AWS Firewall Manager to analyze the IP traffic that security group rules and network ACL rules accept or reject in the VPC.",
        "Use VPC Reachability Analyzer to analyze routes in the transit gateway route tables. Verify that the VPC route tables are correct. Use VPC flow logs to analyze the IP traffic that security group rules and network ACL rules accept or reject in the VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 263"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to transfer data between its VPC and its on-premises data center. The data must travel through a connection that has dedicated bandwidth. The data also must be encrypted in transit. The company has been working with an AWS Partner Network (APN) Partner to establish the connection.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet these requirements? (Choose three.)",
      "correct_answer": "Request a hosted connection from the APN Partner.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Request a hosted public VIF from the APN Partner.",
        "Create an AWS Client VPN connection.",
        "Create a private VIF."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection.||Create a public VIF.",
        "code": "Question 264"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company's security guidelines state that all outbound traffic from a VPC to the company's on-premises data center must pass through a security appliance. The security appliance runs on an Amazon EC2 instance. A network engineer needs to improve the network performance between the on-premises data center and the security appliance.\n\nWhich actions should the network engineer take to meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Use an EC2 instance that supports enhanced networking.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Send outbound traffic through a transit gateway.",
        "Place the EC2 instance in a placement group within the VPC.",
        "Attach multiple elastic network interfaces to the EC2 instance."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Increase the EC2 instance size.",
        "code": "Question 265"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company's application team is unable to launch new resources into its VPC. A network engineer discovers that the VPC has run out of usable IP addresses. The VPC CIDR block is 172.16.0.0/16.\n\nWhich additional CIDR block can the network engineer attach to the VPC?",
      "correct_answer": "172.17.0.0/16",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "172.17.0.0/29",
        "10.0.0.0/16",
        "192.168.0.0/16"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 266"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A financial trading company is using Amazon EC2 instances to run its trading platform. Part of the company's trading platform includes a third-party pricing service that the EC2 instances communicate with over UDP on port 50000.\n\nRecently, the company has had problems with the pricing service. Some of the responses from the pricing service appear to be incorrectly formatted and are not being processed successfully. The third-party vendor requests access to the data that the pricing service is returning. The third-party vendor wants to capture request and response data for debugging by logging in to an EC2 instance that accesses the pricing service. The company prohibits direct access to production systems and requires all log analysis to be performed in a dedicated monitoring account.\n\nWhich set of steps should a network engineer take to capture the data and meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "1. Configure a traffic mirror filter to capture the UDP data. 2. Configure Traffic Mirroring to capture the traffic for the EC2 instance's elastic network interface. 3. Configure a packet inspection package on a new EC2 instance in the monitoring account. Use the elastic network interface of the new EC2 instance as the target for the traffic mirror. 4. Extract the data by using the packet inspection package. 5. Provide the data to the third-party vendor.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1. Configure VPC flow logs to capture the data that flows in the VPC. 2. Send the data to an Amazon S3 bucket. 3. In the monitoring account, extract the data that flows to the EC2 instance's IP address and filter the traffic for the UDP data. 4. Provide the data to the third-party vendor.",
        "1. Configure a traffic mirror filter to capture the UDP data. 2. Configure Traffic Mirroring to capture the traffic for the EC2 instance's elastic network interface. 3. Configure a packet inspection package on a new EC2 instance in the production environment. Use the elastic network interface of the new EC2 instance as the target for the traffic mirror. 4. Extract the data by using the packet inspection package. 5. Provide the data to the third-party vendor.",
        "1. Create a new Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume. Attach the EBS volume to the EC2 instance. 2. Log in to the EC2 instance in the production environment. Run the tcpdump command to capture the UDP data on the EBS volume. 3. Export the data from the EBS volume to Amazon S3. 4. Provide the data to the third-party vendor."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 267"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company's network engineer is configuring an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection between a transit gateway and the company's on-premises network. The Site-to-Site VPN connection is configured to use BGP over two tunnels in active/active mode with equal-cost multi-path (ECMP) routing activated on the transit gateway.\n\nWhen the network engineer attempts to send traffic from the on-premises network to an Amazon EC2 instance, traffic is sent over the first tunnel. However, return traffic is received over the second tunnel and is dropped at the customer gateway. The network engineer must resolve this issue without reducing the overall VPN bandwidth.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure the virtual tunnel interfaces on the customer gateway to allow asymmetric routing.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure the customer gateway to use AS PATH prepending and local preference to prefer one tunnel over the other.",
        "Configure the Site-to-Site VPN options to set the first tunnel as the primary tunnel to eliminate asymmetric routing.",
        "Configure the Site-to-Site VPN to use static routing in active/active mode to ensure that traffic flows over a preferred path."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 268"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company runs an application on Amazon EC2 instances. A network engineer implements a NAT gateway in the application's VPC to replace self-managed NAT instances. After the network engineer shifts traffic from the self-managed NAT instances to the NAT gateway, users begin to report issues.\n\nDuring troubleshooting, the network engineer discovers that the connection to the application is closing after approximately 6 minutes of inactivity.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to resolve this issue?",
      "correct_answer": "Check for increases in the IdleTimeoutCount Amazon CloudWatch metric for the NAT gateway. Configure TCP keepalive on the application EC2 instances.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Check for increases in the ErrorPortAllocation Amazon CloudWatch metric for the NAT gateway. Configure an HTTP timeout value on the application EC2 instances.",
        "Check for increases in the PacketsDropCount Amazon CloudWatch metric for the NAT gateway. Configure an HTTPS timeout value on the application EC2 instances.",
        "Check for decreases in the ActiveConnectionCount Amazon CloudWatch metric for the NAT gateway. Configure UDP keepalive on the application EC2 instances."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 269"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A software-as-a-service (SaaS) company is migrating its private SaaS application to AWS. The company has hundreds of customers that connect to multiple data centers by using VPN tunnels. As the number of customers has grown, the company has experienced more difficulty in its effort to manage routing and segmentation of customers with complex NAT rules.\n\nAfter the migration to AWS is complete, the company's AWS customers must be able to access the SaaS application directly from their VPCs. Meanwhile, the company's on-premises customers still must be able to connect through IPsec encrypted tunnels.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use AWS PrivateLink to connect the AWS customers. Use a third-party routing appliance in the SaaS application VPC to terminate onpremises Site-to-Site VPN connections.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Connect the AWS customer VPCs to a shared transit gateway. Use AWS Site-to-Site VPN connections to the transit gateway for the on-premises customers",
        "Peer each AWS customer's VPCs to the VPC that hosts the SaaS application. Create AWS Site-to-Site VPN connections on the SaaS VPC virtual private gateway.",
        "Use Site-to-Site VPN tunnels to connect each AWS customer's VPCs to the VPC that hosts the SaaS application. Use AWS Site-to-Site VPN to connect the on-premises customers."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 270"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company's existing AWS environment contains public application servers that run on Amazon EC2 instances. The application servers run in a VPC subnet. Each server is associated with an Elastic IP address.\n\nThe company has a new requirement for firewall inspection of all traffic from the internet before the traffic reaches any EC2 instances. A security engineer has deployed and configured a Gateway Load Balancer (GLB) in a standalone VPC with a fleet of third-party firewalls.\n\nHow should a network engineer update the environment to ensure that the traffic travels across the fleet of firewalls?",
      "correct_answer": "Provision a GLB endpoint in the application VPC in a new subnet. Create a gateway route table with a route that specifies the application subnet CIDR block as the destination and the GLB endpoint as the target. Associate the gateway route table with the internet gateway in the application VPUpdate the application subnet route table's default route destination to be the GLB endpoint.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy a transit gateway. Attach a GLB endpoint to the transit gateway. Attach the application VPC to the transit gateway. Update the application subnet route table's default route destination to be the GLB endpoint. Ensure that the EC2 instances' security group allows traffic from the GLB endpoint.",
        "Update the application subnet route table to have a default route to the GLOn the standalone VPC that contains the firewall fleet, add a route in the route table for the application VPC's CIDR block with the GLB endpoint as the destination. Update the EC2 instances' security group to allow traffic from the GLB.",
        "Instruct the security engineer to move the GLB into the application VPC. Create a gateway route table. Associate the gateway route table with the application subnet. Add a default route to the gateway route table with the GLB as its destination. Update the route table on the GLB to direct traffic from the internet gateway to the application servers. Ensure that the EC2 instances' security group allows traffic from the GLB."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 271"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an AWS Site-to-Site VPN connection between its office and its VPC. Users report occasional failure of the connection to the application that is hosted inside the VPC. A network engineer discovers in the customer gateway logs that the Internet Key Exchange (IKE) session ends when the connection to the application fails.\n\nWhat should the network engineer do to bring up the IKE session if the IKE session goes down?",
      "correct_answer": "Set the dead peer detection (DPD) timeout action to Restart. Initiate traffic from on premises to the VPC.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set the dead peer detection (DPD) timeout action to Clear. Initiate traffic from the VPC to on premises.",
        "Set the dead peer detection (DPD) timeout action to None. Initiate traffic from the VPC to on premises.",
        "Set the dead peer detection (DPD) timeout action to Cancel. Initiate traffic from on premises to the VPC."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 272"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company makes forecasts each quarter to decide how to optimize operations to meet expected demand. The company uses ML models to make these forecasts.\n\nAn AI practitioner is writing a report about the trained ML models to provide transparency and explainability to company stakeholders.\n\nWhat should the AI practitioner include in the report to meet the transparency and explainability requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Partial dependence plots (PDPs)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Code for model training",
        "Sample data for training",
        "Model convergence tables"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 1"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use language models to create an application for inference on edge devices. The inference must have the lowest latency possible.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy optimized small language models (SLMs) on edge devices.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy optimized large language models (LLMs) on edge devices.",
        "Incorporate a centralized small language model (SLM) API for asynchronous communication with edge devices.",
        "Incorporate a centralized large language model (LLM) API for asynchronous communication with edge devices."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 2"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is developing a mobile ML app that uses a phone's camera to diagnose and treat insect bites. The company wants to train an image classification model by using a diverse dataset of insect bite photos from different genders, ethnicities, and geographic locations around the world.\n\nWhich principle of responsible AI does the company demonstrate in this scenario?",
      "correct_answer": "Fairness",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Explainability",
        "Governance",
        "Transparency"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 3"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is developing an ML model to make loan approvals. The company must implement a solution to detect bias in the model. The company must also be able to explain the model's predictions.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon SageMaker Clarify",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon SageMaker Data Wrangler",
        "Amazon SageMaker Model Cards",
        "AWS AI Service Cards"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 4"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has developed a generative text summarization model by using Amazon Bedrock. The company will use Amazon Bedrock automatic model evaluation capabilities.\n\nWhich metric should the company use to evaluate the accuracy of the model?",
      "correct_answer": "BERTScore",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Area Under the ROC Curve (AUC) score",
        "F1 score",
        "Real world knowledge (RWK) score"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 5"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An AI practitioner wants to predict the classification of flowers based on petal length, petal width, sepal length, and sepal width.\n\nWhich algorithm meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "K-nearest neighbors (k-NN)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "K-mean",
        "Autoregressive Integrated Moving Average (ARIMA)",
        "Linear regression"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 6"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using custom models in Amazon Bedrock for a generative AI application. The company wants to use a company managed encryption key to encrypt the model artifacts that the model customization jobs create.\n\nWhich AWS service meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "Amazon Macie",
        "AWS Secrets Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 7"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use large language models (LLMs) to produce code from natural language code comments.\n\nWhich LLM feature meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Text generation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Text summarization",
        "Text completion",
        "Text classification"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 8"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is introducing a mobile app that helps users learn foreign languages. The app makes text more coherent by calling a large language model (LLM). The company collected a diverse dataset of text and supplemented the dataset with examples of more readable versions. The company wants the LLM output to resemble the provided examples.\n\nWhich metric should the company use to assess whether the LLM meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Recall-Oriented Understudy for Gisting Evaluation (ROUGE) score",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Value of the loss function",
        "Semantic robustness",
        "Latency of the text generation"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 9"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company notices that its foundation model (FM) generates images that are unrelated to the prompts. The company wants to modify the prompt techniques to decrease unrelated images.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use negative prompts.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use zero-shot prompts.",
        "Use positive prompts.",
        "Use ambiguous prompts."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 10"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use a large language model (LLM) to generate concise, feature-specific descriptions for the company’s products.\n\nWhich prompt engineering technique meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create prompts for each product category that highlight the key features. Include the desired output format and length for each prompt response.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create one prompt that covers all products. Edit the responses to make the responses more specific, concise, and tailored to each product.",
        "Include a diverse range of product features in each prompt to generate creative and unique descriptions.",
        "Provide detailed, product-specific prompts to ensure precise and customized descriptions."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 11"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is developing an ML model to predict customer churn. The model performs well on the training dataset but does not accurately predict churn for new data.\n\nWhich solution will resolve this issue?",
      "correct_answer": "Increase the regularization parameter to decrease model complexity.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Decrease the regularization parameter to increase model complexity.",
        "Add more features to the input data.",
        "Train the model for more epochs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 12"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to build an ML model by using Amazon SageMaker. The company needs to share and manage variables for model development across multiple teams.\n\nWhich SageMaker feature meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon SageMaker Feature Store",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon SageMaker Data Wrangler",
        "Amazon SageMaker Clarify",
        "Amazon SageMaker Model Cards"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 13"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is implementing intelligent agents to provide conversational search experiences for its customers. The company needs a database service that will support storage and queries of embeddings from a generative AI model as vectors in the database.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Athena",
        "Amazon Redshift",
        "Amazon EMR"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 14"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A financial institution is building an AI solution to make loan approval decisions by using a foundation model (FM). For security and audit purposes, the company needs the AI solution's decisions to be explainable.\n\nWhich factor relates to the explainability of the AI solution's decisions?",
      "correct_answer": "Model complexity",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Training time",
        "Number of hyperparameters",
        "Deployment time"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 15"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A pharmaceutical company wants to analyze user reviews of new medications and provide a concise overview for each medication.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create medication review summaries by using Amazon Bedrock large language models (LLMs).",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a time-series forecasting model to analyze the medication reviews by using Amazon Personalize.",
        "Create a classification model that categorizes medications into different groups by using Amazon SageMaker.",
        "Create medication review summaries by using Amazon Rekognition."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 16"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to build a lead prioritization application for its employees to contact potential customers. The application must give employees the ability to view and adjust the weights assigned to different variables in the model based on domain knowledge and expertise.\n\nWhich ML model type meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Logistic regression model",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deep learning model built on principal components",
        "K-nearest neighbors (k-NN) model",
        "Neural network"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 17"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which strategy will determine if a foundation model (FM) effectively meets business objectives?",
      "correct_answer": "Assess the model's alignment with specific use cases.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Evaluate the model's performance on benchmark datasets.",
        "Analyze the model's architecture and hyperparameters.",
        "Measure the computational resources required for model deployment."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 19"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to train an ML model to classify images of different types of animals. The company has a large dataset of labeled images and will not label more data.\n\nWhich type of learning should the company use to train the model?",
      "correct_answer": "Supervised learning",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Unsupervised learning",
        "Reinforcement learning",
        "Active learning"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 20"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which phase of the ML lifecycle determines compliance and regulatory requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Business goal identification",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Feature engineering",
        "Model training",
        "Data collection"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 21"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A food service company wants to develop an ML model to help decrease daily food waste and increase sales revenue. The company needs to continuously improve the model's accuracy.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use Amazon SageMaker and iterate with newer data.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use Amazon Personalize and iterate with historical data.",
        "Use Amazon CloudWatch to analyze customer orders.",
        "Use Amazon Rekognition to optimize the model."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 22"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has developed an ML model to predict real estate sale prices. The company wants to deploy the model to make predictions without managing servers or infrastructure.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy the model by using an Amazon SageMaker endpoint.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy the model on an Amazon EC2 instance.",
        "Deploy the model on an Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS) cluster.",
        "Deploy the model by using Amazon CloudFront with an Amazon S3 integration."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 23"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use generative AI to increase developer productivity and software development. The company wants to use Amazon Q Developer.\n\nWhat can Amazon Q Developer do to help the company meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create software snippets, reference tracking, and open source license tracking.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Run an application without provisioning or managing servers.",
        "Enable voice commands for coding and providing natural language search.",
        "Convert audio files to text documents by using ML models."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 24"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to develop an AI application to help its employees check open customer claims, identify details for a specific claim, and access documents for a claim.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use Agents for Amazon Bedrock with Amazon Bedrock knowledge bases to build the application.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use Agents for Amazon Bedrock with Amazon Fraud Detector to build the application.",
        "Use Amazon Personalize with Amazon Bedrock knowledge bases to build the application.",
        "Use Amazon SageMaker to build the application by training a new ML model."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 25"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A manufacturing company uses AI to inspect products and find any damages or defects.\n\nWhich type of AI application is the company using?",
      "correct_answer": "Computer vision",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Recommendation system",
        "Natural language processing (NLP)",
        "Image processing"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 26"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to create an ML model to predict customer satisfaction. The company needs fully automated model tuning.\n\nWhich AWS service meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon SageMaker",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Athena",
        "Amazon Comprehend"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 27"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which technique can a company use to lower bias and toxicity in generative AI applications during the post-processing ML lifecycle?",
      "correct_answer": "Human-in-the-loop",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Data augmentation",
        "Feature engineering",
        "Adversarial training"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 28"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A bank has fine-tuned a large language model (LLM) to expedite the loan approval process. During an external audit of the model, the company discovered that the model was approving loans at a faster pace for a specific demographic than for other demographics.\n\nHow should the bank fix this issue MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Include more diverse training data. Fine-tune the model again by using the new data.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) with the fine-tuned model.",
        "Use AWS Trusted Advisor checks to eliminate bias.",
        "Pre-train a new LLM with more diverse training data."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 29"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to log all requests made to its Amazon Bedrock API. The company must retain the logs securely for 5 years at the lowest possible cost.\n\nWhich combination of AWS service and storage class meets these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudTrail",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "AWS Audit Manager",
        "Amazon S3 Standard"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Amazon S3 Intelligent-Tiering",
        "code": "Question 31"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An ecommerce company wants to improve search engine recommendations by customizing the results for each user of the company’s ecommerce platform.\n\nWhich AWS service meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Personalize",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Kendra",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Transcribe"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 32"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A hospital is developing an AI system to assist doctors in diagnosing diseases based on patient records and medical images. To comply with regulations, the sensitive patient data must not leave the country the data is located in.\n\nWhich data governance strategy will ensure compliance and protect patient privacy?",
      "correct_answer": "Data residency",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Data quality",
        "Data discoverability",
        "Data enrichment"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 33"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to monitor the performance of its ML systems by using a highly scalable AWS service.\n\nWhich AWS service meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon CloudWatch",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CloudTrail",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "AWS Config"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 34"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A financial institution is using Amazon Bedrock to develop an AI application. The application is hosted in a VPC. To meet regulatory compliance standards, the VPC is not allowed access to any internet traffic.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS PrivateLink",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Macie",
        "Amazon CloudFront",
        "Internet gateway"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 35"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An AI practitioner is developing a prompt for an Amazon Titan model. The model is hosted on Amazon Bedrock. The AI practitioner is using the model to solve numerical reasoning challenges. The AI practitioner adds the following phrase to the end of the prompt: “Ask the model to show its work by explaining its reasoning step by step.”\n\nWhich prompt engineering technique is the AI practitioner using?",
      "correct_answer": "Chain-of-thought prompting",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Prompt injection",
        "Few-shot prompting",
        "Prompt templating"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 36"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service makes foundation models (FMs) available to help users build and scale generative AI applications?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Bedrock",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Q Developer",
        "Amazon Kendra",
        "Amazon Comprehend"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 37"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building a mobile app for users who have a visual impairment. The app must be able to hear what users say and provide voice responses.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use a deep learning neural network to perform speech recognition.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Build ML models to search for patterns in numeric data.",
        "Use generative AI summarization to generate human-like text.",
        "Build custom models for image classification and recognition."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 38"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to enhance response quality for a large language model (LLM) for complex problem-solving tasks. The tasks require detailed reasoning and a step-by-step explanation process.\n\nWhich prompt engineering technique meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Chain-of-thought prompting",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Few-shot prompting",
        "Zero-shot prompting",
        "Directional stimulus prompting"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 39"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to keep its foundation model (FM) relevant by using the most recent data. The company wants to implement a model training strategy that includes regular updates to the FM.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Continuous pre-training",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Batch learning",
        "Static training",
        "Latent training"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 40"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is a characteristic of AI governance frameworks for building trust and deploying human-centered AI technologies?",
      "correct_answer": "Developing policies and guidelines for data, transparency, responsible AI, and compliance",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Expanding initiatives across business units to create long-term business value",
        "Ensuring alignment with business standards, revenue goals, and stakeholder expectations",
        "Overcoming challenges to drive business transformation and growth"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 42"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An ecommerce company is using a generative AI chatbot to respond to customer inquiries. The company wants to measure the financial effect of the chatbot on the company’s operations.\n\nWhich metric should the company use?",
      "correct_answer": "Cost for each customer conversation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Number of customer inquiries handled",
        "Cost of training AI models",
        "Average handled time (AHT)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 43"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to find groups for its customers based on the customers’ demographics and buying patterns.\n\nWhich algorithm should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "K-means",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "K-nearest neighbors (k-NN)",
        "Decision tree",
        "Support vector machine"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 44"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company’s large language model (LLM) is experiencing hallucinations.\n\nHow can the company decrease hallucinations?",
      "correct_answer": "Decrease the temperature inference parameter for the model.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set up Agents for Amazon Bedrock to supervise the model training.",
        "Use data pre-processing and remove any data that causes hallucinations.",
        "Use a foundation model (FM) that is trained to not hallucinate."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 45"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to develop an educational game where users answer questions such as the following: \"A jar contains six red, four green, and three yellow marbles. What is the probability of choosing a green marble from the jar?\"\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Use code that will calculate probability by using simple rules and computations.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use supervised learning to create a regression model that will predict probability.",
        "Use reinforcement learning to train a model to return the probability.",
        "Use unsupervised learning to create a model that will estimate probability density."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 46"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using a large language model (LLM) on Amazon Bedrock to build a chatbot. The chatbot processes customer support requests. To resolve a request, the customer and the chatbot must interact a few times.\n\nWhich solution gives the LLM the ability to use content from previous customer messages?",
      "correct_answer": "Add messages to the model prompt.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Turn on model invocation logging to collect messages.",
        "Use Amazon Personalize to save conversation history.",
        "Use Provisioned Throughput for the LLM."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 47"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company’s employees provide product descriptions and recommendations to customers when customers call the customer service center. These recommendations are based on where the customers are located. The company wants to use foundation models (FMs) to automate this process.\n\nWhich AWS service meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Bedrock",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Macie",
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Textract"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 48"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to upload customer service email messages to Amazon S3 to develop a business analysis application. The messages sometimes contain sensitive data. The company wants to receive an alert every time sensitive information is found.\n\nWhich solution fully automates the sensitive information detection process with the LEAST development effort?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure Amazon Macie to detect sensitive information in the documents that are uploaded to Amazon S3.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use Amazon SageMaker endpoints to deploy a large language model (LLM) to redact sensitive data.",
        "Develop multiple regex patterns to detect sensitive data. Expose the regex patterns on an Amazon SageMaker notebook.",
        "Ask the customers to avoid sharing sensitive information in their email messages."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 49"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is a benefit of using Amazon SageMaker Model Cards to document AI models?",
      "correct_answer": "Standardizing information about a model’s purpose, performance, and limitations.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Providing a visually appealing summary of a mode’s capabilities.",
        "Reducing the overall computational requirements of a model.",
        "Physically storing models for archival purposes."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 52"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What does an F1 score measure in the context of foundation model (FM) performance?",
      "correct_answer": "Model precision and recall",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Model speed in generating responses",
        "Financial cost of operating the model",
        "Energy efficiency of the model’s computations"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 53"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company deployed an AI/ML solution to help customer service agents respond to frequently asked questions. The questions can change over time. The company wants to give customer service agents the ability to ask questions and receive automatically generated answers to common customer questions.\n\nWhich strategy will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Use Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) with prompt engineering techniques.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Fine-tune the model regularly.",
        "Train the model by using context data.",
        "Pre-train and benchmark the model by using context data."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 54"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company built an AI-powered resume screening system. The company used a large dataset to train the model. The dataset contained resumes that were not representative of all demographics.\n\nWhich core dimension of responsible AI does this scenario present?",
      "correct_answer": "Fairness",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Explainability",
        "Privacy and security",
        "Transparency"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 55"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A global financial company has developed an ML application to analyze stock market data and provide stock market trends. The company wants to continuously monitor the application development phases and to ensure that company policies and industry regulations are followed.\n\nWhich AWS services will help the company assess compliance requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Audit Manager",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "AWS CloudTrail"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS Config",
        "code": "Question 56"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which metric measures the runtime efficiency of operating AI models?",
      "correct_answer": "Average response time",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Customer satisfaction score (CSAT)",
        "Training time for each epoch",
        "Number of training instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 57"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to improve the accuracy of the responses from a generative AI application. The application uses a foundation model (FM) on Amazon Bedrock.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Use prompt engineering.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Fine-tune the FM.",
        "Retrain the FM.",
        "Train a new FM."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 58"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to identify harmful language in the comments section of social media posts by using an ML model. The company will not use labeled data to train the model.\n\nWhich strategy should the company use to identify harmful language?",
      "correct_answer": "Use Amazon Comprehend toxicity detection.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use Amazon Rekognition moderation.",
        "Use Amazon SageMaker built-in algorithms to train the model.",
        "Use Amazon Polly to monitor comments."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 59"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A media company wants to analyze viewer behavior and demographics to recommend personalized content. The company wants to deploy a customized ML model in its production environment. The company also wants to observe if the model quality drifts over time.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon SageMaker Model Monitor",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon SageMaker Clarify",
        "Amazon Comprehend"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 60"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is deploying AI/ML models by using AWS services. The company wants to offer transparency into the models’ decision-making processes and provide explanations for the model outputs.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon SageMaker Model Cards",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Lex"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 61"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A manufacturing company wants to create product descriptions in multiple languages.\n\nWhich AWS service will automate this task?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Translate",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Kendra",
        "Amazon Polly"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 62"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS feature records details about ML instance data for governance and reporting?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon SageMaker Model Cards",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon SageMaker Debugger",
        "Amazon SageMaker Model Monitor",
        "Amazon SageMaker JumpStart"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 64"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A financial company is using ML to help with some of the company’s tasks.\n\nWhich option is a use of generative AI models?",
      "correct_answer": "Summarizing customer complaints",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Classifying customers based on product usage",
        "Segmenting customers based on type of investments",
        "Forecasting revenue for certain products"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 65"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option describes embeddings in the context of AI?",
      "correct_answer": "A numerical method for data representation in a reduced dimensionality space",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A method for compressing large datasets",
        "An encryption method for securing sensitive data",
        "A method for visualizing high-dimensional data"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 67"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building a contact center application and wants to gain insights from customer conversations. The company wants to analyze and extract key information from the audio of the customer calls.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Transcribe call recordings by using Amazon Transcribe.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Build a conversational chatbot by using Amazon Lex.",
        "Extract information from call recordings by using Amazon SageMaker Model Monitor.",
        "Create classification labels by using Amazon Comprehend."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 68"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building an AI application to summarize books of varying lengths. During testing, the application fails to summarize some books.\n\nWhy does the application fail to summarize some books?",
      "correct_answer": "The input tokens exceed the model’s context size.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The temperature is set too high.",
        "The selected model does not support fine-tuning.",
        "The Top P value is too high."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 69"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An airline company wants to build a conversational AI assistant to answer customer questions about flight schedules, booking, and payments. The company wants to use large language models (LLMs) and a knowledge base to create a text-based chatbot interface.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST development effort?",
      "correct_answer": "Develop a Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) agent by using Amazon Bedrock.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Train models on Amazon SageMaker Autopilot.",
        "Create a Python application by using Amazon Q Developer.",
        "Fine-tune models on Amazon SageMaker Jumpstart."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 70"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is tokenization used for in natural language processing (NLP)?",
      "correct_answer": "To break text into smaller units for processing",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "To encrypt text data",
        "To compress text files",
        "To translate text between languages"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 71"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is a characteristic of transformer-based language models?",
      "correct_answer": "Transformer-based language models use self-attention mechanisms to capture contextual relationships.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Transformer-based language models use convolutional layers to apply filters across an input to capture local patterns through filtered views.",
        "Transformer-based language models can process only text data.",
        "Transformer-based language models process data sequences one element at a time in cyclic iterations."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 72"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A financial company is using AI systems to obtain customer credit scores as part of the loan application process. The company wants to expand to a new market in a different geographic area. The company must ensure that it can operate in that geographic area.\n\nWhich compliance laws should the company review?",
      "correct_answer": "Local algorithm accountability laws",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Local health data protection laws",
        "Local payment card data protection laws",
        "Local education privacy laws"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 73"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses Amazon Bedrock for its generative AI application. The company wants to use Amazon Bedrock Guardrails to detect and filter harmful user inputs and model-generated outputs.\n\nWhich content categories can the guardrails filter? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Hate",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Politics",
        "Gambling",
        "Religion"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Violence",
        "code": "Question 74"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which scenario describes a potential risk and limitation of prompt engineering in the context of a generative AI model?",
      "correct_answer": "Prompt engineering could expose the model to vulnerabilities such as prompt injection attacks.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Prompt engineering does not ensure that the model always produces consistent and deterministic outputs, eliminating the need for validation.",
        "Properly designed prompts reduce but do not eliminate the risk of data poisoning or model hijacking.",
        "Prompt engineering does not ensure that the model will consistently generate highly reliable outputs when working with real-world data."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 75"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A publishing company built a Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) based solution to give its users the ability to interact with published content. New content is published daily. The company wants to provide a near real-time experience to users.\n\nWhich steps in the RAG pipeline should the company implement by using offline batch processing to meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Generation of content embeddings",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Generation of embeddings for user queries",
        "Creation of the search index",
        "Retrieval of relevant content",
        "Response generation for the user"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 76"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which technique breaks a complex task into smaller subtasks that are sent sequentially to a large language model (LLM)?",
      "correct_answer": "Prompt chaining",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "One-shot prompting",
        "Tree of thoughts",
        "Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 77"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An AI practitioner needs to improve the accuracy of a natural language generation model. The model uses rapidly changing inventory data.\n\nWhich technique will improve the model's accuracy?",
      "correct_answer": "Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Transfer learning",
        "Federated learning",
        "One-shot prompting"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 78"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has petabytes of unlabeled customer data to use for an advertisement campaign. The company wants to classify its customers into tiers to advertise and promote the company's products.\n\nWhich methodology should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Unsupervised learning",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Supervised learning",
        "Reinforcement learning",
        "Reinforcement learning from human feedback (RLHF)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 79"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to collaborate with several research institutes to develop an AI model. The company needs standardized documentation of model version tracking and a record of model development.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Track the model changes by using Amazon SageMaker Model Cards.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Track the model changes by using Git.",
        "Track the model changes by using Amazon Fraud Detector.",
        "Track the model changes by using Amazon Comprehend."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 80"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company that uses multiple ML models wants to identify changes in original model quality so that the company can resolve any issues.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon SageMaker Model Monitor",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon SageMaker JumpStart",
        "Amazon SageMaker HyperPod",
        "Amazon SageMaker Data Wrangler"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 81"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is the purpose of chunking in Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG)?",
      "correct_answer": "To improve the contextual relevancy of results retrieved from the vector index",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "To avoid database storage limitations for large text documents by storing parts or chunks of the text",
        "To improve efficiency by avoiding the need to convert large text into vector embeddings",
        "To decrease the cost of storage by storing parts or chunks of the text"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 82"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is developing an editorial assistant application that uses generative AI. During the pilot phase, usage is low and application performance is not a concern. The company cannot predict application usage after the application is fully deployed and wants to minimize application costs.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use Amazon Bedrock with On-Demand Throughput.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use GPU-powered Amazon EC2 instances.",
        "Use Amazon Bedrock with Provisioned Throughput.",
        "Use Amazon SageMaker JumpStart."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 83"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company deployed a Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) application on Amazon Bedrock that gathers financial news to distribute in daily newsletters. Users have recently reported politically influenced ideas in the newsletters.\n\nWhich Amazon Bedrock guardrail can identify and filter this content?",
      "correct_answer": "Denied topics",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Word filters",
        "Sensitive information filters",
        "Content filters"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 84"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A financial company is developing a fraud detection system that flags potential fraud cases in credit card transactions. Employees will evaluate the flagged fraud cases. The company wants to minimize the amount of time the employees spend reviewing flagged fraud cases that are not actually fraudulent.\n\nWhich evaluation metric meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Precision",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Recall",
        "Accuracy",
        "Lift chart"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 85"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company designed an AI-powered agent to answer customer inquiries based on product manuals.\n\nWhich strategy can improve customer confidence levels in the AI-powered agent's responses?",
      "correct_answer": "Including referenced product manual links in the response",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Writing the confidence level in the response",
        "Designing an agent avatar that looks like a computer",
        "Training the agent to respond in the company's language style"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 86"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A hospital developed an AI system to provide personalized treatment recommendations for patients. The AI system must provide the rationale behind the recommendations and make the insights accessible to doctors and patients.\n\nWhich human-centered design principle does this scenario present?",
      "correct_answer": "Explainability",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Privacy and security",
        "Fairness",
        "Data governance"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 87"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which statement presents an advantage of using Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) for natural language processing (NLP) tasks?",
      "correct_answer": "RAG can use external knowledge sources to generate more accurate and informative responses.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "RAG is designed to improve the speed of language model training.",
        "RAG is primarily used for speech recognition tasks.",
        "RAG is a technique for data augmentation in computer vision tasks."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 88"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has created a custom model by fine-tuning an existing large language model (LLM) from Amazon Bedrock. The company wants to deploy the model to production and use the model to handle a steady rate of requests each minute.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Purchase Provisioned Throughput for the model on Amazon Bedrock.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy the model by using an Amazon EC2 compute optimized instance.",
        "Use the model with on-demand throughput on Amazon Bedrock.",
        "Store the model in Amazon S3 and host the model by using AWS Lambda."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 89"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An AI practitioner wants to use a foundation model (FM) to design a search application. The search application must handle queries that have text and images.\n\nWhich type of FM should the AI practitioner use to power the search application?",
      "correct_answer": "Multi-modal embedding model",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Text embedding model",
        "Multi-modal generation model",
        "Image generation model"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 90"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which technique involves training AI models on labeled datasets to adapt the models to specific industry terminology and requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Fine-tuning",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Data augmentation",
        "Model quantization",
        "Continuous pre-training"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 91"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is creating an agent for its application by using Amazon Bedrock Agents. The agent is performing well, but the company wants to improve the agent’s accuracy by providing some specific examples.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Modify the advanced prompts for the agent to include the examples.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a guardrail for the agent that includes the examples.",
        "Use Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth to label the examples.",
        "Run a script in AWS Lambda that adds the examples to the training dataset."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 92"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is a benefit of using infrastructure as code (IaC) in machine learning operations (MLOps)?",
      "correct_answer": "IaC streamlines the deployment of scalable and consistent ML workloads in cloud environments.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "IaC eliminates the need for hyperparameter tuning.",
        "IaC always provisions powerful compute instances, contributing to the training of more accurate models.",
        "IaC minimizes overall expenses by deploying only low-cost instances."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 93"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to fine-tune a foundation model (FM) to answer questions for a specific domain. The company wants to use instruction-based fine-tuning.\n\nHow should the company prepare the training data?",
      "correct_answer": "Create pairs of questions and answers that specifically address topics related to the company's industry domain.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Gather company internal documents and industry-specific materials. Merge the documents and materials into a single file.",
        "Collect external company reviews from various online sources. Manually label each review as either positive or negative.",
        "Create few-shot prompts to instruct the model to answer only domain knowledge."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 94"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which ML technique ensures data compliance and privacy when training AI models on AWS?",
      "correct_answer": "Federated learning",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reinforcement learning",
        "Transfer learning",
        "Unsupervised learning"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 95"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A manufacturing company has an application that ingests consumer complaints from publicly available sources. The application uses complex hard-coded logic to process the complaints. The company wants to scale this logic across markets and product lines.\n\nWhich advantage do generative AI models offer for this scenario?",
      "correct_answer": "Adaptability",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Predictability of outputs",
        "Less sensitivity to changes in inputs",
        "Explainability"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 97"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A financial company wants to flag all credit card activity as possibly fraudulent or non-fraudulent based on transaction data.\n\nWhich type of ML model meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Binary classification",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Regression",
        "Diffusion",
        "Multi-class classification"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 98"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A hospital wants to use a generative AI solution with speech-to-text functionality to help improve employee skills in dictating clinical notes.\n\nWhich AWS service meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS HealthScribe",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Q Developer",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 100"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses a foundation model (FM) from Amazon Bedrock for an AI search tool. The company wants to fine-tune the model to be more accurate by using the company's data.\n\nWhich strategy will successfully fine-tune the model?",
      "correct_answer": "Provide labeled data with the prompt field and the completion field.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Prepare the training dataset by creating a .txt file that contains multiple lines in .csv format.",
        "Purchase Provisioned Throughput for Amazon Bedrock.",
        "Train the model on journals and textbooks."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 101"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which type of AI model makes numeric predictions?",
      "correct_answer": "Regression",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Diffusion",
        "Transformer",
        "Multi-modal"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 102"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is the purpose of vector embeddings in a large language model (LLM)?",
      "correct_answer": "Providing the ability to mathematically compare texts",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Splitting text into manageable pieces of data",
        "Grouping a set of characters to be treated as a single unit",
        "Providing the count of every word in the input"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 104"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to fine-tune a foundation model (FM) by using AWS services. The company needs to ensure that its data stays private, safe, and secure in the source AWS Region where the data is stored.\n\nWhich combination of steps will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Use the Amazon Bedrock API.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Host the model on premises by using AWS Outposts.",
        "Host the Amazon Bedrock API on premises.",
        "Use Amazon CloudWatch logs and metrics."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Use AWS PrivateLink and a VPC.",
        "code": "Question 105"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A financial company uses AWS to host its generative AI models. The company must generate reports to show adherence to international regulations for handling sensitive customer data.\n\nWhich AWS service meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Artifact",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Macie",
        "AWS Secrets Manager",
        "AWS Config"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 106"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A medical company wants to modernize its onsite information processing application. The company wants to use generative AI to respond to medical questions from patients.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to ensure responsible AI for the application?",
      "correct_answer": "Guardrails for Amazon Bedrock",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 107"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which metric is used to evaluate the performance of foundation models (FMs) for text summarization tasks?",
      "correct_answer": "Bilingual Evaluation Understudy (BLEU) score",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "F1 score",
        "Accuracy",
        "Mean squared error (MSE)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 108"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is the benefit of fine-tuning a foundation model (FM)?",
      "correct_answer": "Fine-tuning improves the performance of the FM on a specific task by further training the FM on new labeled data.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Fine-tuning reduces the FM's size and complexity and enables slower inference.",
        "Fine-tuning uses specific training data to retrain the FM from scratch to adapt to a specific use case.",
        "Fine-tuning keeps the FM's knowledge up to date by pre-training the FM on more recent data."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 109"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to improve its chatbot's responses to match the company's desired tone. The company has 100 examples of high-quality conversations between customer service agents and customers. The company wants to use this data to incorporate company tone into the chatbot's responses.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an Amazon Bedrock fine-tuning job.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use Amazon Personalize to generate responses.",
        "Create an Amazon SageMaker HyperPod pre-training job.",
        "Host the model by using Amazon SageMaker. Use TensorRT for large language model (LLM) deployment."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 110"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An ecommerce company is using a chatbot to automate the customer order submission process. The chatbot is powered by AI and is available to customers directly from the company's website 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.\n\nWhich option is an AI system input vulnerability that the company needs to resolve before the chatbot is made available?",
      "correct_answer": "Prompt injection",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Data leakage",
        "Large language model (LLM) hallucinations",
        "Concept drift"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 111"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A law firm wants to build an AI application by using large language models (LLMs). The application will read legal documents and extract key points from the documents.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Develop a summarization chatbot.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Build an automatic named entity recognition system.",
        "Create a recommendation engine.",
        "Develop a multi-language translation system."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 112"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use AI to protect its application from threats. The AI solution needs to check if an IP address is from a suspicious source.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Develop an anomaly detection system.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Build a speech recognition system.",
        "Create a natural language processing (NLP) named entity recognition system.",
        "Create a fraud forecasting system."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 113"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A social media company wants to prevent users from posting discriminatory content on the company's application. The company wants to use Amazon Bedrock as part of the solution.\n\nHow can the company use Amazon Bedrock to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Block interactions related to predefined topics.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Give users the ability to interact based on user preferences.",
        "Restrict user conversations to predefined topics.",
        "Provide a variety of responses to select from for user engagement."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 114"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An education company waftion. The application will give users the ability to enter text or provide a picture of a question. The application will respond with a written answer and an explanation of the written answer.\n\nWhich model type meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Large multi-modal language model",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Computer vision model",
        "Diffusion model",
        "Text-to-speech model"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 115"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "In which stage of the generative AI model lifecycle are tests performed to examine the model's accuracy?",
      "correct_answer": "Evaluation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deployment",
        "Data selection",
        "Fine-tuning"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 116"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which statement correctly describes embeddings in generative AI?",
      "correct_answer": "Embeddings represent data as high-dimensional vectors that capture semantic relationships.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Embeddings is a technique that searches data to find the most helpful information to answer natural language questions.",
        "Embeddings reduce the hardware requirements of a model by using a less precise data type for the weights and activations.",
        "Embeddings provide the ability to store and retrieve data for generative AI applications."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 117"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to add generative AI functionality to its application by integrating a large language model (LLM). The responses from the LLM must be as deterministic and as stable as possible.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure the application to automatically set the temperature parameter to 0 when submitting the prompt to the LLM.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure the application to automatically add \"make your response deterministic\" at the end of the prompt before submitting the prompt to the LLM.",
        "Configure the application to automatically add \"make your response deterministic\" at the beginning of the prompt before submitting the prompt to the LLM.",
        "Configure the application to automatically set the temperature parameter to 1 when submitting the prompt to the LLM."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 118"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to select a generative AI model to build an application. The application must provide responses to users in real time.\n\nWhich model characteristic should the company consider to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Inference speed",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Model complexity",
        "Innovation speed",
        "Training time"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 119"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which term refers to the instructions given to foundation models (FMs) so that the FMs provide a more accurate response to a question?",
      "correct_answer": "Prompt",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Direction",
        "Dialog",
        "Translation"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 120"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A retail company wants to build an ML model to recommend products to customers. The company wants to build the model based on responsible practices.\n\nWhich practice should the company apply when collecting data to decrease model bias?",
      "correct_answer": "Ensure that the data is balanced and collected from a diverse group.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use data from only customers who match the demographics of the company's overall customer base.",
        "Collect data from customers who have a past purchase history.",
        "Ensure that the data is from a publicly available dataset."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 121"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is developing an ML model to predict customer churn.\n\nWhich evaluation metric will assess the model's performance on a binary classification task such as predicting churn?",
      "correct_answer": "F1 score",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Mean squared error (MSE)",
        "R-squared",
        "Time used to train the model"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 122"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An AI practitioner is evaluating the performance of an Amazon SageMaker model. The AI practitioner must choose a performance metric. The metric must show the ratio of the number of correctly classified items to the total number of correctly and incorrectly classified items.\n\nWhich metric meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Accuracy",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Precision",
        "F1 score",
        "Recall"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 123"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which feature of Amazon OpenSearch Service gives companies the ability to build vector database applications?",
      "correct_answer": "Scalable index management and nearest neighbor search capability",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Integration with Amazon S3 for object storage",
        "Support for geospatial indexing and queries",
        "Ability to perform real-time analysis on streaming data"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 124"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An ecommerce company receives multiple gigabytes of customer data daily. The company uses the data to train an ML model to forecast future product demand. The company needs a solution to perform inferences once each day.\n\nWhich inference type meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Batch inference",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Asynchronous inference",
        "Real-time inference",
        "Serverless inference"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 125"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has developed a generative AI model for customer segmentation. The model has been deployed in the company's production environment for a long time. The company recently noticed some inconsistency in the model's responses. The company wants to evaluate model bias and drift.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon SageMaker Model Monitor",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon SageMaker Clarify",
        "Amazon SageMaker Model Cards",
        "Amazon SageMaker Feature Store"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 126"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has signed up for Amazon Bedrock access to build applications. The company wants to restrict employee access to specific models available on Amazon Bedrock.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) policies to restrict model access.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use AWS Security Token Service (AWS STS) to generate temporary credentials for model use.",
        "Use AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) service roles to restrict model subscription.",
        "Use Amazon Inspector to monitor model access."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 127"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which ML technique uses training data that is labeled with the correct output values?",
      "correct_answer": "Supervised learning",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Unsupervised learning",
        "Reinforcement learning",
        "Transfer learning"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 128"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which large language model (LLM) parameter controls the number of possible next words or tokens considered at each step of the text generation process?",
      "correct_answer": "Top K",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Maximum tokens",
        "Temperature",
        "Batch size"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 129"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is making a chatbot. The chatbot uses Amazon Lex and Amazon OpenSearch Service. The chatbot uses the company's private data to answer questions. The company needs to convert the data into a vector representation before storing the data in a database.\n\nWhich type of foundation model (FM) meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Text embeddings model",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Text completion model",
        "Instruction following model",
        "Image generation model"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 130"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use a large language model (LLM) to generate product descriptions. The company wants to give the model example descriptions that follow a format.\n\nWhich prompt engineering technique will generate descriptions that match the format?",
      "correct_answer": "Few-shot prompting",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Zero-shot prompting",
        "Chain-of-thought prompting",
        "One-shot prompting"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 131"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A bank is fine-tuning a large language model (LLM) on Amazon Bedrock to assist customers with questions about their loans. The bank wants to ensure that the model does not reveal any private customer data.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Remove personally identifiable information (PII) from the customer data before fine-tuning the LLM.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use Amazon Bedrock Guardrails.",
        "Increase the Top-K parameter of the LLM.",
        "Store customer data in Amazon S3. Encrypt the data before fine-tuning the LLM."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 132"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A grocery store wants to create a chatbot to help customers find products in the store. The chatbot must check the inventory in real time and provide the product location in the store.\n\nWhich prompt engineering technique should the store use to build the chatbot?",
      "correct_answer": "Reasoning and acting (ReAct) prompting",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Zero-shot prompting",
        "Few-shot prompting",
        "Least-to-most prompting"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 133"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses a third-party model on Amazon Bedrock to analyze confidential documents. The company is concerned about data privacy.\n\nWhich statement describes how Amazon Bedrock protects data privacy?",
      "correct_answer": "User inputs and model outputs are not shared with any third-party model providers.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "User inputs and model outputs are anonymized and shared with third-party model providers.",
        "User inputs are kept confidential, but model outputs are shared with third-party model providers.",
        "User inputs and model outputs are redacted before the inputs and outputs are shared with third-party model providers."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 134"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is a use case for generative AI models?",
      "correct_answer": "Creating photorealistic images from text descriptions for digital marketing",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Improving network security by using intrusion detection systems",
        "Enhancing database performance by using optimized indexing",
        "Analyzing financial data to forecast stock market trends"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 135"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An animation company wants to provide subtitles for its content.\n\nWhich AWS service meets this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Transcribe",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Translate"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 136"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An ecommerce company wants to group customers based on their purchase history and preferences to personalize the user experience of the company's application.\n\nWhich ML technique should the company use?",
      "correct_answer": "Clustering",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Classification",
        "Regression",
        "Content generation"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 137"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to control employee access to publicly available foundation models (FMs).\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure Amazon SageMaker JumpStart to restrict discoverable FMs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Analyze cost and usage reports in AWS Cost Explorer.",
        "Download AWS security and compliance documents from AWS Artifact.",
        "Build a hybrid search solution by using Amazon OpenSearch Service."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 138"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has set up a translation tool to help its customer service team handle issues from customers around the world. The company wants to evaluate the performance of the translation tool. The company sets up a parallel data process that compares the responses from the tool to responses from actual humans. Both sets of responses are generated on the same set of documents.\n\nWhich strategy should the company use to evaluate the translation tool?",
      "correct_answer": "Use the Bilingual Evaluation Understudy (BLEU) score to estimate the relative translation quality of the two methods.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use the Bilingual Evaluation Understudy (BLEU) score to estimate the absolute translation quality of the two methods.",
        "Use the BERTScore to estimate the absolute translation quality of the two methods.",
        "Use the BERTScore to estimate the relative translation quality of the two methods."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 139"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An AI practitioner wants to generate more diverse and more creative outputs from a large language model (LLM).\n\nHow should the AI practitioner adjust the inference parameter?",
      "correct_answer": "Increase the temperature value.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Decrease the Top K value.",
        "Increase the response length.",
        "Decrease the prompt length."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 140"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has developed custom computer vision models. The company needs a user-friendly interface for data labeling to minimize model mistakes on new real-world data.\n\nWhich AWS service, feature, or tool meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon SageMaker Canvas",
        "Amazon Bedrock playground",
        "Amazon Bedrock Agents"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 141"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is integrating AI into its employee recruitment and hiring solution. The company wants to mitigate bias risks and ensure responsible AI practices while prioritizing equitable hiring decisions.\n\nWhich core dimensions of responsible AI should the company consider? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Fairness",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Tolerance",
        "Flexibility",
        "Open source"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Transparency",
        "code": "Question 142"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A financial company has deployed an ML model to predict customer churn. The model has been running in production for 1 week. The company wants to evaluate how accurately the model predicts churn compared to actual customer behavior.\n\nWhich metric meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "F1 score",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Root mean squared error (RMSE)",
        "Return on investment (ROI)",
        "Bilingual Evaluation Understudy (BLEU) score"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 143"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a generative AI application that uses a pre-trained foundation model (FM) on Amazon Bedrock. The company wants the FM to include more context by using company information.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Use Amazon Bedrock Knowledge Bases.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Choose a different FM on Amazon Bedrock.",
        "Use Amazon Bedrock Agents.",
        "Deploy a custom model on Amazon Bedrock."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 144"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to build a generative AI application by using Amazon Bedrock and needs to choose a foundation model (FM). The company wants to know how much information can fit into one prompt.\n\nWhich consideration will inform the company's decision?",
      "correct_answer": "Context window",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Temperature",
        "Batch size",
        "Model size"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 146"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A food service company wants to collect a dataset to predict customer food preferences. The company wants to ensure that the food preferences of all demographics are included in the data.\n\nWhich dataset characteristic does this scenario present?",
      "correct_answer": "Diversity",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Accuracy",
        "Recency bias",
        "Reliability"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 147"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to create a chatbot that answers questions about human resources policies. The company is using a large language model (LLM) and has a large digital documentation base.\n\nWhich technique should the company use to optimize the generated responses?",
      "correct_answer": "Use Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG).",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use few-shot prompting.",
        "Set the temperature to 1.",
        "Decrease the token size."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 148"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An education company is building a chatbot whose target audience is teenagers. The company is training a custom large language model (LLM). The company wants the chatbot to speak in the target audience's language style by using creative spelling and shortened words.\n\nWhich metric will assess the LLM's performance?",
      "correct_answer": "Bilingual Evaluation Understudy (BLEU) score",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "F1 score",
        "BERTScore",
        "Recall-Oriented Understudy for Gisting Evaluation (ROUGE)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 149"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A customer service team is developing an application to analyze customer feedback and automatically classify the feedback into different categories. The categories include product quality, customer service, and delivery experience.\n\nWhich A1 concept does this scenario present?",
      "correct_answer": "Natural language processing (NLP)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Computer vision",
        "Recommendation systems",
        "Fraud detection"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 150"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to make a chatbot to help customers. The chatbot will help solve technical problems without human intervention.\n\nThe company chose a foundation model (FM) for the chatbot. The chatbot needs to produce responses that adhere to company tone.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Experiment and refine the prompt until the FM produces the desired responses.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set a low limit on the number of tokens the FM can produce.",
        "Use batch inferencing to process detailed responses.",
        "Define a higher number for the temperature parameter."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 151"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use a large language model (LLM) on Amazon Bedrock for sentiment analysis. The company wants to classify the sentiment of text passages as positive or negative.\n\nWhich prompt engineering strategy meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Provide examples of text passages with corresponding positive or negative labels in the prompt followed by the new text passage to be classified.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Provide a detailed explanation of sentiment analysis and how LLMs work in the prompt.",
        "Provide the new text passage to be classified without any additional context or examples.",
        "Provide the new text passage with a few examples of unrelated tasks, such as text summarization or question answering."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 152"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A security company is using Amazon Bedrock to run foundation models (FMs). The company wants to ensure that only authorized users invoke the models. The company needs to identify any unauthorized access attempts to set appropriate AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) policies and roles for future iterations of the FMs.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to identify unauthorized users that are trying to access Amazon Bedrock?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudTrail",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Audit Manager",
        "Amazon Fraud Detector",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 153"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has developed an ML model for image classification. The company wants to deploy the model to production so that a web application can use the model.\n\nThe company needs to implement a solution to host the model and serve predictions without managing any of the underlying infrastructure.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use Amazon SageMaker Serverless Inference to deploy the model.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use Amazon CloudFront to deploy the model.",
        "Use Amazon API Gateway to host the model and serve predictions.",
        "Use AWS Batch to host the model and serve predictions."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 154"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An AI company periodically evaluates its systems and processes with the help of independent software vendors (ISVs). The company needs to receive email message notifications when an ISV's compliance reports become available.\n\nWhich AWS service can the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Artifact",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Audit Manager",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "AWS Data Exchange"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 155"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use a large language model (LLM) to develop a conversational agent. The company needs to prevent the LLM from being manipulated with common prompt engineering techniques to perform undesirable actions or expose sensitive information.\n\nWhich action will reduce these risks?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a prompt template that teaches the LLM to detect attack patterns.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Increase the temperature parameter on invocation requests to the LLM.",
        "Avoid using LLMs that are not listed in Amazon SageMaker.",
        "Decrease the number of input tokens on invocations of the LLM."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 156"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to classify human genes into 20 categories based on gene characteristics. The company needs an ML algorithm to document how the inner mechanism of the model affects the output.\n\nWhich ML algorithm meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Decision trees",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Linear regression",
        "Logistic regression",
        "Neural networks"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 157"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using the Generative AI Security Scoping Matrix to assess security responsibilities for its solutions. The company has identified four different solution scopes based on the matrix.\n\nWhich solution scope gives the company the MOST ownership of security responsibilities?",
      "correct_answer": "Building and training a generative AI model from scratch by using specific data that a customer owns.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Using a third-party enterprise application that has embedded generative AI features.",
        "Building an application by using an existing third-party generative AI foundation model (FM).",
        "Refining an existing third-party generative AI foundation model (FM) by fine-tuning the model by using data specific to the business."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 158"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An AI practitioner has a database of animal photos. The AI practitioner wants to automatically identify and categorize the animals in the photos without manual human effort.\n\nWhich strategy meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Object detection",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Anomaly detection",
        "Named entity recognition",
        "Inpainting"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 159"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to create an application by using Amazon Bedrock. The company has a limited budget and prefers flexibility without long-term commitment.\n\nWhich Amazon Bedrock pricing model meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "On-Demand",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Model customization",
        "Provisioned Throughput",
        "Spot Instance"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 160"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature can help an AI development team quickly deploy and consume a foundation model (FM) within the team's VPC?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon SageMaker JumpStart",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "PartyRock, an Amazon Bedrock Playground",
        "Amazon SageMaker endpoints"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 161"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "How can companies use large language models (LLMs) securely on Amazon Bedrock?",
      "correct_answer": "Design clear and specific prompts. Configure AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) roles and policies by using least privilege access.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Enable AWS Audit Manager for automatic model evaluation jobs.",
        "Enable Amazon Bedrock automatic model evaluation jobs.",
        "Use Amazon CloudWatch Logs to make models explainable and to monitor for bias."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 162"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has terabytes of data in a database that the company can use for business analysis. The company wants to build an AI-based application that can build a SQL query from input text that employees provide. The employees have minimal experience with technology.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Generative pre-trained transformers (GPT)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Residual neural network",
        "Support vector machine",
        "WaveNet"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 163"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company built a deep learning model for object detection and deployed the model to production.\n\nWhich AI process occurs when the model analyzes a new image to identify objects?",
      "correct_answer": "Inference",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Training",
        "Model deployment",
        "Bias correction"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 164"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An AI practitioner is building a model to generate images of humans in various professions. The AI practitioner discovered that the input data is biased and that specific attributes affect the image generation and create bias in the model.\n\nWhich technique will solve the problem?",
      "correct_answer": "Data augmentation for imbalanced classes",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Model monitoring for class distribution",
        "Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG)",
        "Watermark detection for images"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 165"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is implementing the Amazon Titan foundation model (FM) by using Amazon Bedrock. The company needs to supplement the model by using relevant data from the company's private data sources.\n\nWhich solution will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an Amazon Bedrock knowledge base.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use a different FM.",
        "Choose a lower temperature value.",
        "Enable model invocation logging."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 166"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A medical company is customizing a foundation model (FM) for diagnostic purposes. The company needs the model to be transparent and explainable to meet regulatory requirements.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Generate simple metrics, reports, and examples by using Amazon SageMaker Clarify.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure the security and compliance by using Amazon Inspector.",
        "Encrypt and secure training data by using Amazon Macie.",
        "Gather more data. Use Amazon Rekognition to add custom labels to the data."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 167"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has built an image classification model to predict plant diseases from photos of plant leaves. The company wants to evaluate how many images the model classified correctly.\n\nWhich evaluation metric should the company use to measure the model's performance?",
      "correct_answer": "Accuracy",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "R-squared score",
        "Root mean squared error (RMSE)",
        "Learning rate"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 168"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to deploy a conversational chatbot to answer customer questions. The chatbot is based on a fine-tuned Amazon SageMaker JumpStart model. The application must comply with multiple regulatory frameworks.\n\nWhich capabilities can the company show compliance for? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Threat detection",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Auto scaling inference endpoints",
        "Cost optimization",
        "Loosely coupled microservices"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Data protection",
        "code": "Question 169"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is training a foundation model (FM). The company wants to increase the accuracy of the model up to a specific acceptance level.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Increase the epochs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Decrease the batch size.",
        "Decrease the epochs.",
        "Increase the temperature parameter."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 170"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building a large language model (LLM) question answering chatbot. The company wants to decrease the number of actions call center employees need to take to respond to customer questions.\n\nWhich business objective should the company use to evaluate the effect of the LLM chatbot?",
      "correct_answer": "Average call duration",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Website engagement rate",
        "Corporate social responsibility",
        "Regulatory compliance"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 171"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which functionality does Amazon SageMaker Clarify provide?",
      "correct_answer": "Identifies potential bias during data preparation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Integrates a Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) workflow",
        "Monitors the quality of ML models in production",
        "Documents critical details about ML models"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 172"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is developing a new model to predict the prices of specific items. The model performed well on the training dataset. When the company deployed the model to production, the model's performance decreased significantly.\n\nWhat should the company do to mitigate this problem?",
      "correct_answer": "Increase the volume of data that is used in training.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reduce the volume of data that is used in training.",
        "Add hyperparameters to the model.",
        "Increase the model training time."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 173"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An ecommerce company wants to build a solution to determine customer sentiments based on written customer reviews of products.\n\nWhich AWS services meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Comprehend",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Rekognition"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Amazon Bedrock",
        "code": "Question 174"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use large language models (LLMs) with Amazon Bedrock to develop a chat interface for the company's product manuals. The manuals are stored as PDF files.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Upload PDF documents to an Amazon Bedrock knowledge base. Use the knowledge base to provide context when users submit prompts to Amazon Bedrock.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use prompt engineering to add one PDF file as context to the user prompt when the prompt is submitted to Amazon Bedrock.",
        "Use prompt engineering to add all the PDF files as context to the user prompt when the prompt is submitted to Amazon Bedrock.",
        "Use all the PDF documents to fine-tune a model with Amazon Bedrock. Use the fine-tuned model to process user prompts."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 175"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A social media company wants to use a large language model (LLM) for content moderation. The company wants to evaluate the LLM outputs for bias and potential discrimination against specific groups or individuals.\n\nWhich data source should the company use to evaluate the LLM outputs with the LEAST administrative effort?",
      "correct_answer": "Benchmark datasets",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "User-generated content",
        "Moderation logs",
        "Content moderation guidelines"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 176"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use a pre-trained generative AI model to generate content for its marketing campaigns. The company needs to ensure that the generated content aligns with the company's brand voice and messaging requirements.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create effective prompts that provide clear instructions and context to guide the model's generation.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Optimize the model's architecture and hyperparameters to improve the model's overall performance.",
        "Increase the model's complexity by adding more layers to the model's architecture.",
        "Select a large, diverse dataset to pre-train a new generative model."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 177"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A loan company is building a generative AI-based solution to offer new applicants discounts based on specific business criteria. The company wants to build and use an AI model responsibly to minimize bias that could negatively affect some customers.\n\nWhich actions should the company take to meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Detect imbalances or disparities in the data.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ensure that the model runs frequently.",
        "Use the Recall-Oriented Understudy for Gisting Evaluation (ROUGE) technique to ensure that the model is 100% accurate.",
        "Ensure that the model's inference time is within the accepted limits."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Evaluate the model's behavior so that the company can provide transparency to stakeholders.",
        "code": "Question 178"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using a pre-trained large language model (LLM) to build a chatbot for product recommendations. The company needs the LLM outputs to be short and written in a specific language.\n\nWhich solution will align the LLM response quality with the company's expectations?",
      "correct_answer": "Adjust the prompt.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Choose an LLM of a different size.",
        "Increase the temperature.",
        "Increase the Top K value."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 179"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using an Amazon Bedrock base model to summarize documents for an internal use case. The company trained a custom model to improve the summarization quality.\n\nWhich action must the company take to use the custom model through Amazon Bedrock?",
      "correct_answer": "Purchase Provisioned Throughput for the custom model.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy the custom model in an Amazon SageMaker endpoint for real-time inference.",
        "Register the model with the Amazon SageMaker Model Registry.",
        "Grant access to the custom model in Amazon Bedrock."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 180"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to choose a model from Amazon Bedrock to use internally. The company must identify a model that generates responses in a style that the company's employees prefer.\n\nWhat should the company do to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Evaluate the models by using a human workforce and custom prompt datasets.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Evaluate the models by using built-in prompt datasets.",
        "Use public model leaderboards to identify the model.",
        "Use the model InvocationLatency runtime metrics in Amazon CloudWatch when trying models."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 181"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A student at a university is copying content from generative AI to write essays.\n\nWhich challenge of responsible generative AI does this scenario represent?",
      "correct_answer": "Plagiarism",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Toxicity",
        "Hallucinations",
        "Privacy"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 182"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to build its own large language model (LLM) based on only the company's private data. The company is concerned about the environmental effect of the training process.\n\nWhich Amazon EC2 instance type has the LEAST environmental effect when training LLMs?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon EC2 Trn series",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon EC2 C series",
        "Amazon EC2 G series",
        "Amazon EC2 P series"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 183"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to build an interactive application for children that generates new stories based on classic stories. The company wants to use Amazon Bedrock and needs to ensure that the results and topics are appropriate for children.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Guardrails for Amazon Bedrock",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Bedrock playgrounds",
        "Agents for Amazon Bedrock"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 184"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building an application that needs to generate synthetic data that is based on existing data.\n\nWhich type of model can the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Generative adversarial network (GAN)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "XGBoost",
        "Residual neural network",
        "WaveNet"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 185"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A digital devices company wants to predict customer demand for memory hardware. The company does not have coding experience or knowledge of ML algorithms and needs to develop a data-driven predictive model. The company needs to perform analysis on internal data and external data.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Import the data into Amazon SageMaker Canvas. Build ML models and demand forecast predictions by selecting the values in the data from SageMaker Canvas.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Store the data in Amazon S3. Create ML models and demand forecast predictions by using Amazon SageMaker built-in algorithms that use the data from Amazon S3.",
        "Import the data into Amazon SageMaker Data Wrangler. Create ML models and demand forecast predictions by using SageMaker built-in algorithms.",
        "Import the data into Amazon SageMaker Data Wrangler. Build ML models and demand forecast predictions by using an Amazon Personalize Trending-Now recipe."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 186"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has installed a security camera. The company uses an ML model to evaluate the security camera footage for potential thefts. The company has discovered that the model disproportionately flags people who are members of a specific ethnic group.\n\nWhich type of bias is affecting the model output?",
      "correct_answer": "Sampling bias",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Measurement bias",
        "Observer bias",
        "Confirmation bias"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 187"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building a customer service chatbot. The company wants the chatbot to improve its responses by learning from past interactions and online resources.\n\nWhich AI learning strategy provides this self-improvement capability?",
      "correct_answer": "Reinforcement learning with rewards for positive customer feedback",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Supervised learning with a manually curated dataset of good responses and bad responses",
        "Unsupervised learning to find clusters of similar customer inquiries",
        "Supervised learning with a continuously updated FAQ database"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 188"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An AI practitioner has built a deep learning model to classify the types of materials in images. The AI practitioner now wants to measure the model performance.\n\nWhich metric will help the AI practitioner evaluate the performance of the model?",
      "correct_answer": "Confusion matrix",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Correlation matrix",
        "R2 score",
        "Mean squared error (MSE)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 189"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses Amazon SageMaker for its ML pipeline in a production environment. The company has large input data sizes up to 1 GB and processing times up to 1 hour. The company needs near real-time latency.\n\nWhich SageMaker inference option meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Asynchronous inference",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Real-time inference",
        "Serverless inference",
        "Batch transform"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 190"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has built a chatbot that can respond to natural language questions with images. The company wants to ensure that the chatbot does not return inappropriate or unwanted images.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Implement moderation APIs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Retrain the model with a general public dataset.",
        "Perform model validation.",
        "Automate user feedback integration."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 191"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An AI practitioner is using an Amazon Bedrock base model to summarize session chats from the customer service department. The AI practitioner wants to store invocation logs to monitor model input and output data.\n\nWhich strategy should the AI practitioner use?",
      "correct_answer": "Enable invocation logging in Amazon Bedrock.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure AWS CloudTrail as the logs destination for the model.",
        "Configure AWS Audit Manager as the logs destination for the model.",
        "Configure model invocation logging in Amazon EventBridge."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 192"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building an ML model to analyze archived data. The company must perform inference on large datasets that are multiple GBs in size. The company does not need to access the model predictions immediately.\n\nWhich Amazon SageMaker inference option will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Batch transform",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Real-time inference",
        "Serverless inference",
        "Asynchronous inference"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 193"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which term describes the numerical representations of real-world objects and concepts that AI and natural language processing (NLP) models use to improve understanding of textual information?",
      "correct_answer": "Embeddings",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Tokens",
        "Models",
        "Binaries"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 194"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A research company implemented a chatbot by using a foundation model (FM) from Amazon Bedrock. The chatbot searches for answers to questions from a large database of research papers.\n\nAfter multiple prompt engineering attempts, the company notices that the FM is performing poorly because of the complex scientific terms in the research papers.\n\nHow can the company improve the performance of the chatbot?",
      "correct_answer": "Use domain adaptation fine-tuning to adapt the FM to complex scientific terms.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use few-shot prompting to define how the FM can answer the questions.",
        "Change the FM inference parameters.",
        "Clean the research paper data to remove complex scientific terms."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 195"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use a large language model (LLM) on Amazon Bedrock for sentiment analysis. The company needs the LLM to produce more consistent responses to the same input prompt.\n\nWhich adjustment to an inference parameter should the company make to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Decrease the temperature value.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Increase the temperature value.",
        "Decrease the length of output tokens.",
        "Increase the maximum generation length."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 196"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to develop a large language model (LLM) application by using Amazon Bedrock and customer data that is uploaded to Amazon S3. The company's security policy states that each team can access data for only the team's own customers.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an Amazon Bedrock custom service role for each team that has access to only the team's customer data.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a custom service role that has Amazon S3 access. Ask teams to specify the customer name on each Amazon Bedrock request.",
        "Redact personal data in Amazon S3. Update the S3 bucket policy to allow team access to customer data.",
        "Create one Amazon Bedrock role that has full Amazon S3 access. Create IAM roles for each team that have access to only each team's customer folders."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 197"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A medical company deployed a disease detection model on Amazon Bedrock. To comply with privacy policies, the company wants to prevent the model from including personal patient information in its responses. The company also wants to receive notification when policy violations occur.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use Guardrails for Amazon Bedrock to filter content. Set up Amazon CloudWatch alarms for notification of policy violations.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use Amazon Macie to scan the model's output for sensitive data and set up alerts for potential violations.",
        "Configure AWS CloudTrail to monitor the model's responses and create alerts for any detected personal information.",
        "Implement Amazon SageMaker Model Monitor to detect data drift and receive alerts when model quality degrades."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 198"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company manually reviews all submitted resumes in PDF format. As the company grows, the company expects the volume of resumes to exceed the company's review capacity. The company needs an automated system to convert the PDF resumes into plain text format for additional processing.\n\nWhich AWS service meets this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Textract",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Transcribe"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 199"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An education provider is building a question and answer application that uses a generative AI model to explain complex concepts. The education provider wants to automatically change the style of the model response depending on who is asking the question. The education provider will give the model the age range of the user who has asked the question.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements with the LEAST implementation effort?",
      "correct_answer": "Add a role description to the prompt context that instructs the model of the age range that the response should target.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Fine-tune the model by using additional training data that is representative of the various age ranges that the application will support.",
        "Use chain-of-thought reasoning to deduce the correct style and complexity for a response suitable for that user.",
        "Summarize the response text depending on the age of the user so that younger users receive shorter responses."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 200"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using domain-specific models. The company wants to avoid creating new models from the beginning. The company instead wants to adapt pre-trained models to create models for new, related tasks.\n\nWhich ML strategy meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use transfer learning.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Increase the number of epochs.",
        "Decrease the number of epochs.",
        "Use unsupervised learning."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 201"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which strategy evaluates the accuracy of a foundation model (FM) that is used in image classification tasks?",
      "correct_answer": "Measure the model's accuracy against a predefined benchmark dataset.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Calculate the total cost of resources used by the model.",
        "Count the number of layers in the neural network.",
        "Assess the color accuracy of images processed by the model."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 202"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An accounting firm wants to implement a large language model (LLM) to automate document processing. The firm must proceed responsibly to avoid potential harms.\n\nWhat should the firm do when developing and deploying the LLM? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Include fairness metrics for model evaluation.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Adjust the temperature parameter of the model.",
        "Avoid overfitting on the training data.",
        "Apply prompt engineering techniques."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Modify the training data to mitigate bias.",
        "code": "Question 203"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building an ML model. The company collected new data and analyzed the data by creating a correlation matrix, calculating statistics, and visualizing the data.\n\nWhich stage of the ML pipeline is the company currently in?",
      "correct_answer": "Exploratory data analysis",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Data pre-processing",
        "Feature engineering",
        "Hyperparameter tuning"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 204"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has documents that are missing some words because of a database error. The company wants to build an ML model that can suggest potential words to fill in the missing text.\n\nWhich type of model meets this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "BERT-based models",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Topic modeling",
        "Clustering models",
        "Prescriptive ML models"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 205"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to display the total sales for its top-selling products across various retail locations in the past 12 months.\n\nWhich AWS solution should the company use to automate the generation of graphs?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Q in Amazon QuickSight",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Q in Amazon EC2",
        "Amazon Q Developer",
        "Amazon Q in AWS Chatbot"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 206"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building a chatbot to improve user experience. The company is using a large language model (LLM) from Amazon Bedrock for intent detection. The company wants to use few-shot learning to improve intent detection accuracy.\n\nWhich additional data does the company need to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Pairs of user messages and correct user intents",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Pairs of chatbot responses and correct user intents",
        "Pairs of user messages and correct chatbot responses",
        "Pairs of user intents and correct chatbot responses"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 207"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using few-shot prompting on a base model that is hosted on Amazon Bedrock. The model currently uses 10 examples in the prompt. The model is invoked once daily and is performing well. The company wants to lower the monthly cost.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Decrease the number of tokens in the prompt.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Customize the model by using fine-tuning.",
        "Increase the number of tokens in the prompt.",
        "Use Provisioned Throughput."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 208"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An AI practitioner is using a large language model (LLM) to create content for marketing campaigns. The generated content sounds plausible and factual but is incorrect.\n\nWhich problem is the LLM having?",
      "correct_answer": "Hallucination",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Data leakage",
        "Overfitting",
        "Underfitting"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 209"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An AI practitioner trained a custom model on Amazon Bedrock by using a training dataset that contains confidential data. The AI practitioner wants to ensure that the custom model does not generate inference responses based on confidential data.\n\nHow should the AI practitioner prevent responses based on confidential data?",
      "correct_answer": "Delete the custom model. Remove the confidential data from the training dataset. Retrain the custom model.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Mask the confidential data in the inference responses by using dynamic data masking.",
        "Encrypt the confidential data in the inference responses by using Amazon SageMaker.",
        "Encrypt the confidential data in the custom model by using AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS)."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 210"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has built a solution by using generative AI. The solution uses large language models (LLMs) to translate training manuals from English into other languages. The company wants to evaluate the accuracy of the solution by examining the text generated for the manuals.\n\nWhich model evaluation strategy meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Bilingual Evaluation Understudy (BLEU)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Root mean squared error (RMSE)",
        "Recall-Oriented Understudy for Gisting Evaluation (ROUGE)",
        "F1 score"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 211"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building a solution to generate images for protective eyewear. The solution must have high accuracy and must minimize the risk of incorrect annotations.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Human-in-the-loop validation by using Amazon SageMaker Ground Truth Plus",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Data augmentation by using an Amazon Bedrock knowledge base",
        "Image recognition by using Amazon Rekognition",
        "Data summarization by using Amazon QuickSight Q"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 212"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A large retailer receives thousands of customer support inquiries about products every day. The customer support inquiries need to be processed and responded to quickly. The company wants to implement Agents for Amazon Bedrock.\n\nWhat are the key benefits of using Amazon Bedrock agents that could help this retailer?",
      "correct_answer": "Automation of repetitive tasks and orchestration of complex workflows",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Generation of custom foundation models (FMs) to predict customer needs",
        "Automatically calling multiple foundation models (FMs) and consolidating the results",
        "Selecting the foundation model (FM) based on predefined criteria and metrics"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 213"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is a benefit of ongoing pre-training when fine-tuning a foundation model (FM)?",
      "correct_answer": "Improves model performance over time",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Helps decrease the model's complexity",
        "Decreases the training time requirement",
        "Optimizes model inference time"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 214"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What are tokens in the context of generative AI models?",
      "correct_answer": "Tokens are the basic units of input and output that a generative AI model operates on, representing words, subwords, or other linguistic units.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Tokens are the mathematical representations of words or concepts used in generative AI models.",
        "Tokens are the pre-trained weights of a generative AI model that are fine-tuned for specific tasks.",
        "Tokens are the specific prompts or instructions given to a generative AI model to generate output."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 215"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to assess the costs that are associated with using a large language model (LLM) to generate inferences. The company wants to use Amazon Bedrock to build generative AI applications.\n\nWhich factor will drive the inference costs?",
      "correct_answer": "Number of tokens consumed",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Temperature value",
        "Amount of data used to train the LLM",
        "Total training time"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 216"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using Amazon SageMaker Studio notebooks to build and train ML models. The company stores the data in an Amazon S3 bucket. The company needs to manage the flow of data from Amazon S3 to SageMaker Studio notebooks.\n\nWhich solution will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure SageMaker to use a VPC with an S3 endpoint.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use Amazon Inspector to monitor SageMaker Studio.",
        "Use Amazon Macie to monitor SageMaker Studio.",
        "Configure SageMaker to use S3 Glacier Deep Archive."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 217"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a foundation model (FM) that was customized by using Amazon Bedrock to answer customer queries about products. The company wants to validate the model's responses to new types of queries. The company needs to upload a new dataset that Amazon Bedrock can use for validation.\n\nWhich AWS service meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon S3",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)",
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
        "AWS Snowcone"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 218"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which prompting attack directly exposes the configured behavior of a large language model (LLM)?",
      "correct_answer": "Extracting the prompt template",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Prompted persona switches",
        "Exploiting friendliness and trust",
        "Ignoring the prompt template"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 219"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use Amazon Bedrock. The company needs to review which security aspects the company is responsible for when using Amazon Bedrock.\n\nWhich security aspect will the company be responsible for?",
      "correct_answer": "Securing the company's data in transit and at rest",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Patching and updating the versions of Amazon Bedrock",
        "Protecting the infrastructure that hosts Amazon Bedrock",
        "Provisioning Amazon Bedrock within the company network"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 220"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A social media company wants to use a large language model (LLM) to summarize messages. The company has chosen a few LLMs that are available on Amazon SageMaker JumpStart. The company wants to compare the generated output toxicity of these models.\n\nWhich strategy gives the company the ability to evaluate the LLMs with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Automatic model evaluation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Crowd-sourced evaluation",
        "Model evaluation with human workers",
        "Reinforcement learning from human feedback (RLHF)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 221"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is testing the security of a foundation model (FM). During testing, the company wants to get around the safety features and make harmful content.\n\nWhich security technique is this an example of?",
      "correct_answer": "Jailbreak",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Fuzzing training data to find vulnerabilities",
        "Denial of service (DoS)",
        "Penetration testing with authorization"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 222"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to create a chatbot by using a foundation model (FM) on Amazon Bedrock. The FM needs to access encrypted data that is stored in an Amazon S3 bucket. The data is encrypted with Amazon S3 managed keys (SSE-S3).\n\nThe FM encounters a failure when attempting to access the S3 bucket data.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Ensure that the role that Amazon Bedrock assumes has permission to decrypt data with the correct encryption key.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set the access permissions for the S3 buckets to allow public access to enable access over the internet.",
        "Use prompt engineering techniques to tell the model to look for information in Amazon S3.",
        "Ensure that the S3 data does not contain sensitive information."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 223"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to use Amazon SageMaker for model training and inference. The company must comply with regulatory requirements to run SageMaker jobs in an isolated environment without internet access.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Run SageMaker training and Inference by using network Isolation.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Run SageMaker training and inference by using SageMaker Experiments.",
        "Encrypt the data at rest by using encryption for SageMaker geospatial capabilities.",
        "Associate appropriate AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) roles with the SageMaker jobs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 224"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An ML research team develops custom ML models. The model artifacts are shared with other teams for integration into products and services. The ML team retains the model training code and data. The ML team wants to build a mechanism that the ML team can use to audit models.\n\nWhich solution should the ML team use when publishing the custom ML models?",
      "correct_answer": "Create Amazon SageMaker Model Cards with intended uses and training and inference details.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create documents with the relevant information. Store the documents in Amazon S3.",
        "Use AWS AI Service Cards for transparency and understanding models.",
        "Create model training scripts. Commit the model training scripts to a Git repository."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 225"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A software company builds tools for customers. The company wants to use AI to increase software development productivity.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Install code recommendation software in the company's developer tools.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use a binary classification model to generate code reviews.",
        "Install a code forecasting tool to predict potential code issues.",
        "Use a natural language processing (NLP) tool to generate code."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 226"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A retail store wants to predict the demand for a specific product for the next few weeks by using the Amazon SageMaker DeepAR forecasting algorithm.\n\nWhich type of data will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Time series data",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Text data",
        "Image data",
        "Binary data"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 227"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A large retail bank wants to develop an ML system to help the risk management team decide on loan allocations for different demographics.\n\nWhat must the bank do to develop an unbiased ML model?",
      "correct_answer": "Measure class imbalance on the training dataset. Adapt the training process accordingly.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reduce the size of the training dataset.",
        "Ensure that the ML model predictions are consistent with historical results.",
        "Create a different ML model for each demographic group."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 228"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which prompting technique can protect against prompt injection attacks?",
      "correct_answer": "Adversarial prompting",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Zero-shot prompting",
        "Least-to-most prompting",
        "Chain-of-thought prompting"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 229"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has fine-tuned a large language model (LLM) to answer questions for a help desk. The company wants to determine if the fine-tuning has enhanced the model's accuracy.\n\nWhich metric should the company use for the evaluation?",
      "correct_answer": "F1 score",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Precision",
        "Time to first token",
        "Word error rate"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 230"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) with Amazon Bedrock and Stable Diffusion to generate product images based on text descriptions. The results are often random and lack specific details. The company wants to increase the specificity of the generated images.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Increase the classifier-free guidance (CFG) scale.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Increase the number of generation steps.",
        "Use the MASK_IMAGE_BLACK mask source option.",
        "Increase the prompt strength."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 231"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to implement a large language model (LLM) based chatbot to provide customer service agents with real-time contextual responses to customers' inquiries. The company will use the company's policies as the knowledge base.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Implement Retrieval Augmented Generation (RAG) for in-context responses.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Retrain the LLM on the company policy data.",
        "Fine-tune the LLM on the company policy data.",
        "Use pre-training and data augmentation on the company policy data."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 232"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to create a new solution by using AWS Glue. The company has minimal programming experience with AWS Glue.\n\nWhich AWS service can help the company use AWS Glue?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Q Developer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Config",
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Comprehend"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 233"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company plans to use an Amazon Snowball Edge device to transfer files to the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich activities related to a Snowball Edge device are available to the company at no cost?",
      "correct_answer": "The transfer of data from the Snowball Edge appliance into Amazon S3",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use of the Snowball Edge appliance for a 10-day period",
        "The transfer of data out of Amazon S3 and to the Snowball Edge appliance",
        "Daily use of the Snowball Edge appliance after 10 days"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 1"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following are benefits of using AWS Trusted Advisor? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Detecting underutilized resources to save costs",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Providing high-performance container orchestration",
        "Creating and rotating encryption keys",
        "Implementing enforced tagging across AWS resources"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Improving security by proactively monitoring the AWS environment",
        "code": "Question 2"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to automate infrastructure deployment by using infrastructure as code (IaC). The company wants to scale production stacks so the stacks can be deployed in multiple AWS Regions.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudFormation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "AWS Config",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 3"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is an AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) platform perspective capability?",
      "correct_answer": "Data architecture",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Data protection",
        "Data governance",
        "Data science"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 4"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is running a workload in the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich AWS best practice ensures the MOST cost-effective architecture for the workload?",
      "correct_answer": "Rightsizing",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Loose coupling",
        "Caching",
        "Redundancy"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 5"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company plans to use an Amazon Snowball Edge device to transfer files to the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich activities related to a Snowball Edge device are available to the company at no cost?",
      "correct_answer": "The transfer of data from the Snowball Edge appliance into Amazon S3",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use of the Snowball Edge appliance for a 10-day period",
        "The transfer of data out of Amazon S3 and to the Snowball Edge appliance",
        "Daily use of the Snowball Edge appliance after 10 days"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 1"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following are benefits of using AWS Trusted Advisor? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Detecting underutilized resources to save costs",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Providing high-performance container orchestration",
        "Creating and rotating encryption keys",
        "Implementing enforced tagging across AWS resources"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Improving security by proactively monitoring the AWS environment",
        "code": "Question 2"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to automate infrastructure deployment by using infrastructure as code (IaC). The company wants to scale production stacks so the stacks can be deployed in multiple AWS Regions.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudFormation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "AWS Config",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 3"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is an AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) platform perspective capability?",
      "correct_answer": "Data architecture",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Data protection",
        "Data governance",
        "Data science"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 4"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is running a workload in the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich AWS best practice ensures the MOST cost-effective architecture for the workload?",
      "correct_answer": "Rightsizing",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Loose coupling",
        "Caching",
        "Redundancy"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 5"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using a third-party service to back up 10 TB of data to a tape library. The on-premises backup server is running out of space. The company wants to use AWS services for the backups without changing its existing backup workflows.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Storage Gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)",
        "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)",
        "AWS Lambda"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 6"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS tool gives users the ability to plan their service usage, service costs, and instance reservations, and also allows them to set custom alerts when their costs or usage exceed established thresholds?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Budgets",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cost Explorer",
        "AWS Cost and Usage Report",
        "Reserved Instance reporting"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 7"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which tasks are the customer’s responsibility, according to the AWS shared responsibility model? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Perform client-side data encryption.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Establish the global infrastructure.",
        "Secure edge locations.",
        "Patch Amazon RDS DB instances."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Configure IAM credentials.",
        "code": "Question 8"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A developer has been hired by a large company and needs AWS credentials.\n\nWhich are security best practices that should be followed? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Grant the developer access to only the AWS resources needed to perform the job.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Share the AWS account root user credentials with the developer.",
        "Add the developer to the administrator’s group in AWS IAM.",
        "Configure a password policy that ensures the developer’s password cannot be changed."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Ensure the account password policy requires a minimum length.",
        "code": "Question 9"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has multiple AWS accounts that include compute workloads that cannot be interrupted. The company wants to obtain billing discounts that are based on the company’s use of AWS services.\n\nWhich AWS feature or purchasing option will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Consolidated billing",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Resource tagging",
        "Pay-as-you-go pricing",
        "Spot Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 10"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A user wants to allow applications running on an Amazon EC2 instance to make calls to other AWS services. The access granted must be secure.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature should be used?",
      "correct_answer": "IAM roles",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security groups",
        "AWS Firewall Manager",
        "IAM user SSH keys"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 11"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants a fully managed Windows file server for its Windows-based applications.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon FSx",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS)",
        "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)",
        "Amazon EMR"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 12"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following is an advantage that users experience when they move on-premises workloads to the AWS Cloud?",
      "correct_answer": "Elimination of expenses for running and maintaining data centers",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Price discounts that are identical to discounts from hardware providers",
        "Distribution of all operational controls to AWS",
        "Elimination of operational expenses"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 13"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate its NFS on-premises workload to AWS.\n\nWhich AWS Storage Gateway type should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon S3 File Gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Tape Gateway",
        "Volume Gateway",
        "Amazon FSx File Gateway"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 14"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to track the activity in its AWS accounts, and needs to know when an API call is made against its AWS resources.\n\nWhich AWS tool or service can be used to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudTrail",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "AWS IAM"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 15"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an uninterruptible application that runs on Amazon EC2 instances. The application constantly processes a backlog of files in an Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS) queue. This usage is expected to continue to grow for years.\n\nWhat is the MOST cost-effective EC2 instance purchasing model to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Savings Plans",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Spot Instances",
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Dedicated Hosts"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 16"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants an AWS service to provide product recommendations based on its customer data.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Personalize",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Rekognition"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 17"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning its migration to the AWS Cloud. The company is identifying its capability gaps by using the AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) perspectives.\n\nWhich phase of the cloud transformation journey includes these identification activities?",
      "correct_answer": "Align",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Envision",
        "Scale",
        "Launch"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 18"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A social media company wants to protect its web application from common web exploits such as SQL injections and cross-site scripting.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS WAF",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "Amazon CloudWatch"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 19"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which fully managed AWS service assists with the creation, testing, and management of custom Amazon EC2 images?",
      "correct_answer": "EC2 Image Builder",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Machine Image (AMI)",
        "AWS Launch Wizard",
        "AWS Elastic Beanstalk"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 20"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants an automated process to continuously scan its Amazon EC2 instances for software vulnerabilities.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Inspector",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "Amazon Detective",
        "Amazon Cognito"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 21"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to perform data processing once a week that typically takes about 5 hours to complete.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use for this workload?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon EC2",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Lambda",
        "AWS CodeDeploy",
        "AWS Wavelength"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 22"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature provides log information of the inbound and outbound traffic on network interfaces in a VPC?",
      "correct_answer": "VPC Flow Logs",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CloudWatch Logs",
        "AWS CloudTrail",
        "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 23"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to manage deployed IT services and govern its infrastructure as code (IaC) templates.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Service Catalog",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Resource Explorer",
        "AWS Organizations",
        "AWS Systems Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 24"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to design a centralized storage system to manage the configuration data and passwords for its critical business applications.\n\nWhich AWS service or capability will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Systems Manager Parameter Store",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Secrets Manager",
        "AWS Config",
        "Amazon S3"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 25"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company plans to deploy containers on AWS. The company wants full control of the compute resources that host the containers. Which AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon EC2",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS)",
        "AWS Fargate",
        "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 26"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature allows users to create new AWS accounts, group multiple accounts to organize workflows, and apply policies to groups of accounts?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Organizations",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "AWS CloudFormation"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 27"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to store and retrieve files in Amazon S3 for its existing on-premises applications by using industry-standard file system protocols.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon S3 File Gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS DataSync",
        "AWS Snowball Edge",
        "AWS Transfer Family"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 28"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to block SQL injection attacks.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS WAF",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Network ACLs",
        "Security groups",
        "AWS Certificate Manager (ACM)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 29"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants a unified tool to provide a consistent method to interact with AWS services.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CLI",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)",
        "AWS Cloud9",
        "AWS Virtual Private Network (AWS VPN)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 30"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to evaluate its AWS environment and provide best practice recommendations in five categories: cost, performance, service limits, fault tolerance and security.\n\nWhich AWS service can the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Trusted Advisor",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Shield",
        "AWS WAF",
        "AWS Service Catalog"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 31"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which perspective in the AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) includes capabilities for configuration management and patch management?",
      "correct_answer": "Operations",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Platform",
        "Security",
        "Governance"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 32"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a compute workload that is steady, predictable, and uninterruptible.\n\nWhich Amazon EC2 instance purchasing options meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Reserved Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Spot Instances",
        "Dedicated Hosts"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Saving Plans",
        "code": "Question 33"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which Amazon EC2 pricing model is the MOST cost efficient for an uninterruptible workload that runs once a year for 24 hours?",
      "correct_answer": "On-Demand Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reserved Instances",
        "Spot Instances",
        "Dedicated Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 34"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or tool helps users visualize, understand, and manage spending and usage over time?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Cost Explorer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Organizations",
        "AWS Pricing Calculator",
        "AWS Service Catalog"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 35"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is a shared responsibility between AWS and its customers under the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Patch management",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configuration of Amazon EC2 instance operating systems",
        "Application file system server-side encryption",
        "Security of the physical infrastructure"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 36"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate its on-premises workloads to the AWS Cloud. The company wants to separate workloads for chargeback to different departments.\n\nWhich AWS services or features will meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Consolidated billing",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Placement groups",
        "Edge locations",
        "AWS Config"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Multiple AWS accounts",
        "code": "Question 37"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which task is a responsibility of AWS, according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Apply updates to the Nitro Hypervisor.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Enable client-side encryption for objects that are stored in Amazon S3.",
        "Configure IAM security policies to comply with the principle of least privilege.",
        "Patch the guest operating system on an Amazon EC2 instance."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 38"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is a benefit of using AWS for cloud computing?",
      "correct_answer": "Pay-as-you-go pricing",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Trade variable expense for fixed expense",
        "Decreased speed and agility",
        "Spending money running and maintaining data centers"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 39"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is an AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) business perspective capability?",
      "correct_answer": "Data monetization",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Culture evolution",
        "Event management",
        "Platform architecture"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 40"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is assessing its AWS Business Support plan to determine if the plan still meets the company’s needs. The company is considering switching to AWS Enterprise Support.\n\nWhich additional benefit will the company receive with AWS Enterprise Support?",
      "correct_answer": "A designated technical account manager (TAM) to assist in monitoring and optimization",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A full set of AWS Trusted Advisor checks",
        "Phone, email, and chat access to cloud support engineers 24 hours a day, 7 days a week",
        "A consultative review and architecture guidance for the company’s applications"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 41"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which pricing model will interrupt a running Amazon EC2 instance if capacity becomes temporarily unavailable?",
      "correct_answer": "Spot Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Standard Reserved Instances",
        "Convertible Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 42"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which options are AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) security perspective capabilities? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Incident response",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Observability",
        "Incident and problem management",
        "Availability and continuity"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Infrastructure protection",
        "code": "Question 43"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to run its workload on Amazon EC2 instances for more than 1 year. This workload will run continuously.\n\nWhich option offers a discounted hourly rate compared to the hourly rate of On-Demand Instances?",
      "correct_answer": "EC2 Instance Savings Plans",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Graviton processor",
        "Dedicated Hosts",
        "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 44"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which characteristic of the AWS Cloud helps users eliminate underutilized CPU capacity?",
      "correct_answer": "Elasticity",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Agility",
        "Reliability",
        "Durability"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 45"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using a central data platform to manage multiple types of data for its customers. The company wants to use AWS services to discover, transform, and visualize the data.\n\nWhich combination of AWS services should the company use to meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Glue",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
        "Amazon Redshift",
        "Amazon Quantum Ledger Database (Amazon QLDB)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Amazon QuickSight",
        "code": "Question 46"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS services can a company use to achieve a loosely coupled architecture? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon WorkSpaces",
        "Amazon Connect",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS Step Functions",
        "code": "Question 47"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS Cloud service can send alerts to customers if custom spending thresholds are exceeded?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Budgets",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Cost Explorer",
        "AWS Cost Allocation Tags",
        "AWS Organizations"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 48"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company plans to migrate to the AWS Cloud. The company wants to use the AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) to define and track business outcomes as part of its cloud transformation journey.\n\nWhich AWS CAF governance perspective capability will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Benefits management",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Risk management",
        "Application portfolio management",
        "Cloud financial management"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 49"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to quickly and securely move files over long distances between its client and an Amazon S3 bucket.\n\nWhich S3 feature will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "S3 Transfer Acceleration",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "S3 Versioning",
        "S3ACLs",
        "S3 Intelligent-Tiering"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 50"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to continuously run an experimental workload on an Amazon EC2 instance and stop the instance after 12 hours.\n\nWhich instance purchasing option will meet this requirement MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "On-Demand Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reserved Instances",
        "Spot Instances",
        "Dedicated Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 51"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which cloud transformation journey phase of the AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) focuses on demonstrating how the cloud helps accelerate business outcomes?",
      "correct_answer": "Envision",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Scale",
        "Align",
        "Launch"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 52"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is a customer responsibility under the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Application data security",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Maintenance of underlying hardware of Amazon EC2 instances",
        "Physical security of data centers",
        "Maintenance of VPC components"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 53"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants its Amazon EC2 instances to operate in a highly available environment, even if there is a natural disaster in a particular geographic area.\n\nWhich approach will achieve this goal?",
      "correct_answer": "Use EC2 instances in multiple AWS Regions.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use EC2 instances in multiple Amazon CloudFront locations.",
        "Use EC2 instances in multiple edge locations.",
        "Use EC2 instances in AWS Local Zones."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 54"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to modernize and convert a monolithic application into microservices. The company wants to move the application to AWS.\n\nWhich migration strategy should the company use?",
      "correct_answer": "Refactor",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Rehost",
        "Replatform",
        "Repurchase"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 55"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A systems administrator created a new IAM user for a developer and assigned the user an access key instead of a user name and password. What is the access key used for?",
      "correct_answer": "To access the AWS account through a CLI",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "To access the AWS account as the AWS account root user",
        "To access the AWS account through the AWS Management Console",
        "To access all of a company’s AWS accounts"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 56"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A global company wants to migrate its third-party applications to the AWS Cloud. The company wants help from a global team of experts to complete the migration faster and more reliably in accordance with AWS internal best practices.\n\nWhich AWS service or resource will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Professional Services",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Support",
        "AWS Launch Wizard",
        "AWS Managed Services (AMS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 57"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is an environment that consists of one or more data centers?",
      "correct_answer": "Availability Zone",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CloudFront",
        "VPC",
        "AWS Outposts"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 58"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is moving an on-premises data center to the AWS Cloud. The company must migrate 50 petabytes of file storage data to AWS with the least possible operational overhead.\n\nWhich AWS service or resource should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Snowmobile",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Snowball Edge",
        "AWS Data Exchange",
        "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 59"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an application with robust hardware requirements. The application must be accessed by students who are using lightweight, low-cost laptops.\n\nWhich AWS service will help the company deploy the application without investing in backend infrastructure or high-end client hardware?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon AppStream 2.0",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS AppSync",
        "Amazon WorkLink",
        "AWS Elastic Beanstalk"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 60"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to query its server logs to gain insights about its customers’ experiences.\n\nWhich AWS service will store this data MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon S3",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Aurora",
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 61"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following is a recommended design principle for AWS Cloud architecture?",
      "correct_answer": "Avoid monolithic architecture by segmenting workloads.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Design tightly coupled components.",
        "Build a single application component that can handle all the application functionality.",
        "Make large changes on fewer iterations to reduce chances of failure."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 62"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service helps users audit API activity across their AWS account?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudTrail",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "AWS WAF",
        "AWS Config"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 63"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which task is a customer’s responsibility, according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Management of the guest operating systems",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Maintenance of the configuration of infrastructure devices",
        "Management of the host operating systems and virtualization",
        "Maintenance of the software that powers Availability Zones"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 64"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to automatically add and remove Amazon EC2 instances. The company wants the EC2 instances to adjust to varying workloads dynamically.\n\nWhich service or feature will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "Amazon EC2 Spot Instances",
        "AWS Snow Family"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 65"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A user wants to securely automate the management and rotation of credentials that are shared between applications, while spending the least amount of time on managing tasks.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature can be used to accomplish this?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Secrets Manager",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CloudHSM",
        "AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS)",
        "Server-side encryption"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 66"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which security service automatically recognizes and classifies sensitive data or intellectual property on AWS?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Macie",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "AWS Shield"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 67"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An e-learning platform needs to run an application for 2 months each year. The application will be deployed on Amazon EC2 instances. Any application downtime during those 2 months must be avoided.\n\nWhich EC2 purchasing option will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "On-Demand Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reserved Instances",
        "Dedicated Hosts",
        "Spot Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 68"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which actions are best practices for an AWS account root user? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Enable multi-factor authentication (MFA) on the root user.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Share root user credentials with team members.",
        "Create multiple root users for the account, separated by environment.",
        "Use programmatic access instead of the root user and password."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create an IAM user with administrator privileges for daily administrative tasks, instead of using the root user.",
        "code": "Question 69"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is running a critical workload on an Amazon RDS DB instance. The company needs the DB instance to be highly available with a recovery time of less than 5 minutes.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Modify the DB instance to be a Multi-AZ deployment.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create a read replica of the DB instance.",
        "Create a template of the DB instance by using AWS CloudFormation.",
        "Take frequent snapshots of the DB instance. Store the snapshots in Amazon S3."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 70"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company plans to migrate its application to AWS and run the application on Amazon EC2 instances. The application will have continuous usage for 1 year.\n\nWhich EC2 instance purchasing option will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Reserved Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Spot Instances",
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Dedicated Hosts"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 71"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to transfer data between an Amazon S3 bucket and an on-premises application.\n\nWho is responsible for the security of this data, according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "The company",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS",
        "Firewall vendor",
        "AWS Marketplace partner"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 72"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework refers to the ability of a system to recover from infrastructure or service disruptions and dynamically acquire computing resources to meet demand?",
      "correct_answer": "Reliability",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security",
        "Performance efficiency",
        "Cost optimization"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 73"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to identify Amazon S3 buckets that are shared with another AWS account.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "IAM Access Analyzer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Lake Formation",
        "IAM credential report",
        "Amazon CloudWatch"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 74"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service gives users the ability to build interactive business intelligence dashboards that include machine learning insights?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon QuickSight",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Athena",
        "Amazon Kendra",
        "Amazon Redshift"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 75"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following is an AWS value proposition that describes a user’s ability to scale infrastructure based on demand?",
      "correct_answer": "Resource elasticity",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Speed of innovation",
        "Decoupled architecture",
        "Global deployment"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 76"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which action is a security best practice for access to sensitive data that is stored in an Amazon S3 bucket?",
      "correct_answer": "Use IAM roles for applications that require access to the S3 bucket.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Enable S3 Cross-Region Replication (CRR) on the S3 bucket.",
        "Configure AWS WAF to prevent unauthorized access to the S3 bucket.",
        "Configure Amazon GuardDuty to prevent unauthorized access to the S3 bucket."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 77"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to know more about the benefits offered by cloud computing. The company wants to understand the operational advantage of agility. How does AWS provide agility for users?",
      "correct_answer": "The ability to provision and deprovision resources quickly with minimal effort",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The ability the ensure high availability by deploying workloads to multiple regions",
        "A pay-as-you-go model for many services and resources",
        "The ability to transfer infrastructure management to the AWS Cloud"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 78"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A developer wants to deploy an application quickly on AWS without manually creating the required resources.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon EC2",
        "AWS CodeBuild",
        "Amazon Personalize"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 79"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs a central user portal so that users can log in to third-party business applications that support Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML) 2.0.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS IAM Identity Center (AWS Single Sign-On)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)",
        "Amazon Cognito",
        "AWS CLI"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 80"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service should users use to learn about AWS service availability and operations?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Health Dashboard",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon EventBridge",
        "AWS Service Catalog",
        "AWS Control Tower"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 81"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or tool can be used to capture information about inbound and outbound traffic in an Amazon VPC?",
      "correct_answer": "VPC Flow Logs",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "VPC endpoint services",
        "NAT gateway"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 82"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is the customer ALWAYS responsible for managing, according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Customer data",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Software licenses",
        "Networking",
        "Encryption keys"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 83"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service can be used to retrieve compliance reports on demand?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Artifact",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Secrets Manager",
        "AWS Security Hub",
        "AWS Certificate Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 84"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service enables users to check for vulnerabilities on Amazon EC2 instances by using predefined assessment templates?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Inspector",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS WAF",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "AWS Shield"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 85"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company plans to migrate to the AWS Cloud. The company is gathering information about its on-premises infrastructure and requires information such as the hostname, IP address, and MAC address.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Application Discovery Service",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS DataSync",
        "AWS Application Migration Service",
        "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 86"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which action will help increase security in the AWS Cloud?",
      "correct_answer": "Rotate access keys on a reoccurring basis.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Enable programmatic access for all IAM users.",
        "Use IAM users instead of IAM roles to delegate permissions.",
        "Use inline policies instead of customer managed policies."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 87"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to migrate its application to the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich AWS tool or set of resources should the company use to analyze and assess its readiness for migration?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Pricing Calculator",
        "AWS Well-Architected Framework",
        "AWS Budgets"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 88"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following describes some of the core functionality of Amazon S3?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon S3 is an object storage service that provides high-level performance, security, scalability, and data availability.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon S3 is a high-performance block storage service that is designed for use with Amazon EC2.",
        "Amazon S3 is a fully managed, highly reliable, and scalable file storage system that is accessible over the industry-standard SMB protocol.",
        "Amazon S3 is a scalable, fully managed elastic NFS for use with AWS Cloud services and on-premises resources."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 89"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is storing sensitive customer data in an Amazon S3 bucket. The company wants to protect the data from accidental deletion or overwriting.\n\nWhich S3 feature should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "S3 Versioning",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "S3 Lifecycle rules",
        "S3 bucket policies",
        "S3 server-side encryption"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 90"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS benefit is demonstrated by on-demand technology services that enable companies to replace upfront fixed expenses with variable expenses?",
      "correct_answer": "Pay-as-you-go pricing",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "High availability",
        "Economies of scale",
        "Global reach"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 91"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS services or features enable users to connect on-premises networks to a VPC? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS VPN",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Elastic Load Balancing",
        "VPC peering",
        "Amazon CloudFront"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS Direct Connect",
        "code": "Question 92"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A user needs to quickly deploy a nonrelational database on AWS. The user does not want to manage the underlying hardware or the database software.\n\nWhich AWS service can be used to accomplish this?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon RDS",
        "Amazon Aurora",
        "Amazon Redshift"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 93"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which actions are examples of a company’s effort to rightsize its AWS resources to control cloud costs? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Base the selection of Amazon EC2 instance types on past utilization patterns.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Switch from Amazon RDS to Amazon DynamoDB to accommodate NoSQL datasets.",
        "Use Multi-AZ deployments for Amazon RDS.",
        "Replace existing Amazon EC2 instances with AWS Elastic Beanstalk."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Use Amazon S3 Lifecycle policies to move objects that users access infrequently to lower-cost storage tiers.",
        "code": "Question 94"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature can a company use to apply security rules to specific Amazon EC2 instances?",
      "correct_answer": "Security groups",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Network ACLs",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "AWS WAF"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 95"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which design principles support the reliability pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Automatically scale to meet demand.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Perform operations as code.",
        "Enable traceability.",
        "Deploy resources globally to improve response time."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Automatically recover from failure.",
        "code": "Question 96"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company that uses AWS needs to transfer 2 TB of data.\n\nWhich type of transfer of that data would result in no cost for the company?",
      "correct_answer": "Inbound data transfer from the internet",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Outbound data transfer to the internet",
        "Data transfer between AWS Regions",
        "Data transfer between Availability Zones"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 97"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to create templates that the company can reuse to deploy multiple AWS resources.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature can the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudFormation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Marketplace",
        "Amazon Machine Image (AMI)",
        "AWS OpsWorks"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 98"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building an application that requires the ability to send, store, and receive messages between application components. The company has another requirement to process messages in first-in, first-out (FIFO) order.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Step Functions",
        "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)",
        "Amazon Kinesis Data Streams"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 99"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature is a browser-based, pre-authenticated service that can be launched directly from the AWS Management Console?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudShell",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS API",
        "AWS Lightsail",
        "AWS Cloud9"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 100"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service provides the ability to manage infrastructure as code?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudFormation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CodePipeline",
        "AWS CodeDeploy",
        "AWS Direct Connect"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 101"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate its database to a managed AWS service that is compatible with PostgreSQL.\n\nWhich AWS services will meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon RDS",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Athena",
        "Amazon EC2",
        "Amazon DynamoDB"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Amazon Aurora",
        "code": "Question 102"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a fleet of cargo ships. The cargo ships have sensors that collect data at sea, where there is intermittent or no internet connectivity. The company needs to collect, format, and process the data at sea and move the data to AWS later.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Snowball Edge",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS IoT Core",
        "Amazon Lightsail",
        "AWS Storage Gateway"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 103"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company hosts an application on multiple Amazon EC2 instances. The application uses Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS) to send messages.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature will give the application permission to access required AWS services?",
      "correct_answer": "IAM roles",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Certificate Manager (ACM)",
        "AWS Security Hub",
        "Amazon GuardDuty"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 104"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A user has limited knowledge of AWS services, but wants to quickly deploy a scalable Node.js application in the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich service should be used to deploy the application?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CloudFormation",
        "Amazon EC2",
        "AWS OpsWorks"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 105"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs a content delivery network that provides secure delivery of data, videos, applications, and APIs to users globally with low latency and high transfer speeds.\n\nWhich AWS service meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon CloudFront",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Elastic Load Balancing",
        "Amazon S3",
        "Amazon Elastic Transcoder"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 106"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to use third-party software for its workload on AWS.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature can the company use to purchase the software?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Marketplace",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Resource Access Manager",
        "AWS Managed Services",
        "AWS License Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 107"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs fully managed, highly reliable, and scalable file storage that is accessible over the Server Message Block (SMB) protocol.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon FSx for Windows File Server",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon S3",
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 108"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to centrally configure and manage Amazon VPC security groups across multiple AWS accounts within an organization in AWS Organizations.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Firewall Manager",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "Amazon Detective",
        "AWS WAF"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 109"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which task is a responsibility of AWS, according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Maintain the physical hardware of the infrastructure.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure identity and access management for applications.",
        "Manage encryption options for data that is stored on AWS.",
        "Configure security groups for Amazon EC2 instances."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 110"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an Amazon EC2 instance in a private subnet. The company wants to initiate a connection to the internet to pull operating system updates while preventing traffic from the internet from accessing the EC2 instance.\n\nWhich AWS managed service allows this?",
      "correct_answer": "NAT gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "VPC endpoint",
        "Amazon PrivateLink",
        "VPC peering"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 111"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has deployed applications on Amazon EC2 instances. The company needs to assess application vulnerabilities and must identify infrastructure deployments that do not meet best practices.\n\nWhich AWS service can the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Inspector",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "AWS Config",
        "Amazon GuardDuty"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 112"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An online gaming company needs to choose a purchasing option to run its Amazon EC2 instances for 1 year. The web traffic is consistent, and any increases in traffic are predictable. The EC2 instances must be online and available without any disruption.\n\nWhich EC2 instance purchasing option will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Reserved Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Spot Instances",
        "Spot Fleet"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 113"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which actions are the responsibility of AWS, according to the AWS shared responsibility model? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Securing the virtualization layer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Patching the operating system on Amazon EC2 instances",
        "Enforcing a strict password policy for IAM users",
        "Configuring security groups and network ACLs"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Patching the operating system on Amazon RDS instances",
        "code": "Question 114"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is storing data that will not be frequently accessed in the AWS Cloud. If the company needs to access the data, the data needs to be retrieved within 12 hours. The company wants a solution that is cost-effective for storage costs for each gigabyte.\n\nWhich Amazon S3 storage class will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "S3 Glacier Flexible Retrieval",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "S3 Standard",
        "S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA)",
        "S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 115"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or resource can be used to identify services that have been used by a user within a specified date range?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Identity and Access Management Access Analyzer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon S3 access control lists (ACLs)",
        "AWS Certificate Manager (ACM)",
        "Network Access Analyzer"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 116"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to engage third-party consultants to help maintain and support its AWS environment and the company’s business needs.\n\nWhich AWS service or resource will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Partner Network (APN)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Support",
        "AWS Organizations",
        "AWS Service Catalog"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 117"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to create Amazon QuickSight dashboards every week by using its billing data.\n\nWhich AWS feature or tool can the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Cost and Usage Report",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Budgets",
        "AWS Cost Explorer",
        "AWS Cost Anomaly Detection"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 118"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to move data backups to the AWS Cloud. The company needs to replace on-premises storage with storage that is cloud-based but locally cached.\n\nWhich AWS service meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Storage Gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Snowcone",
        "AWS Backup",
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 119"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to organize its resources and track AWS costs on a detailed level. The company needs to categorize costs by business department, environment, and application.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use tags to organize the resources. Activate cost allocation tags to track AWS costs on a detailed level.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Access the AWS Cost Management console to organize resources, set an AWS budget, and receive notifications of unintentional usage.",
        "Create Amazon CloudWatch dashboards to visually organize and track costs individually.",
        "Access the AWS Billing and Cost Management dashboard to organize and track resource consumption on a detailed level."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 120"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to plan, schedule, and run hundreds of thousands of computing jobs on AWS.\n\nWhich AWS service can the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Batch",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Step Functions",
        "AWS Service Catalog",
        "Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 121"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS services or features provide high availability and low latency by enabling failover across different AWS Regions? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Route 53",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Network Load Balancer",
        "Amazon S3 Transfer Acceleration",
        "Application Load Balancer"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS Global Accelerator",
        "code": "Question 122"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following is a way to use Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling groups to scale capacity in the AWS Cloud?",
      "correct_answer": "Scale the number of EC2 instances in or out automatically, based on demand.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use serverless EC2 instances.",
        "Scale the size of EC2 instances up or down automatically, based on demand.",
        "Transfer unused CPU resources between EC2 instances."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 123"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature allows a user to establish a dedicated network connection between a company’s on-premises data center and the AWS Cloud?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Direct Connect",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "VPC peering",
        "AWS VPN",
        "Amazon Route 53"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 124"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which abilities are benefits of the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Deploy globally in minutes.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Trade variable expenses for capital expenses.",
        "Plan capacity in advance of deployments.",
        "Reduce dependencies on network connectivity."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Take advantage of economies of scale.",
        "code": "Question 125"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS security service protects applications from distributed denial of service attacks with always-on detection and automatic inline mitigations?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Shield",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "AWS Web Application Firewall (AWS WAF)",
        "Elastic Load Balancing (ELB)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 126"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service allows users to model and provision AWS resources using common programming languages?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CloudFormation",
        "AWS CodePipeline",
        "AWS Systems Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 127"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which Amazon EC2 instance pricing model can provide discounts of up to 90%?",
      "correct_answer": "Spot Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reserved Instances",
        "On-Demand",
        "Dedicated Hosts"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 128"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following acts as an instance-level firewall to control inbound and outbound access?",
      "correct_answer": "Security groups",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Network access control list",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "Virtual private gateways"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 129"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company must be able to develop, test, and launch an application in the AWS Cloud quickly.\n\nWhich advantage of cloud computing will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Increase speed and agility",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Stop guessing capacity",
        "Trade fixed expense for variable expense",
        "Achieve economies of scale"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 130"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has teams that have different job roles and responsibilities. The company’s employees often change teams. The company needs to manage permissions for the employees so that the permissions are appropriate for the job responsibilities.\n\nWhich IAM resource should the company use to meet this requirement with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "IAM roles",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "IAM user groups",
        "IAM instance profiles",
        "IAM policies for individual users"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 131"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service can a company use to securely store and encrypt passwords for a database?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Secrets Manager",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Shield",
        "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)",
        "Amazon Cognito"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 132"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What can a cloud practitioner use to retrieve AWS security and compliance documents and submit them as evidence to an auditor or regulator?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Artifact",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Certificate Manager",
        "AWS Systems Manager",
        "Amazon Inspector"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 133"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which encryption types can be used to protect objects at rest in Amazon S3? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Server-side encryption with Amazon S3 managed encryption keys (SSE-S3)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "TLS",
        "SSL",
        "Transparent Data Encryption (TDE)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Server-side encryption with AWS KMS managed keys (SSE-KMS)",
        "code": "Question 134"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is a physical location of the AWS global infrastructure?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Region",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS DataSync",
        "Amazon Connect",
        "AWS Organizations"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 135"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to integrate its online shopping website with social media login credentials.\n\nWhich AWS service can the company use to make this integration?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Cognito",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Directory Service",
        "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)",
        "AWS IAM Identity Center (AWS Single Sign-On)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 136"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service is used to track, record, and audit configuration changes made to AWS resources?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Config",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Shield",
        "AWS IAM",
        "Amazon Inspector"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 137"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A customer runs an On-Demand Amazon Linux EC2 instance for 3 hours, 5 minutes, and 6 seconds.\n\nFor how much time will the customer be billed?",
      "correct_answer": "3 hours, 5 minutes, and 6 seconds",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "3 hours, 5 minutes",
        "3 hours, 6 minutes",
        "4 hours"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 138"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company website is experiencing DDoS attacks.\n\nWhich AWS service can help protect the company website against these attacks?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Shield",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Resource Access Manager",
        "AWS Amplify",
        "Amazon GuardDuty"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 139"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants a customized assessment of its current on-premises environment. The company wants to understand its projected running costs in the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Migration Evaluator",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "AWS Control Tower"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 140"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company that has multiple business units wants to centrally manage and govern its AWS Cloud environments. The company wants to automate the creation of AWS accounts, apply service control policies (SCPs), and simplify billing processes.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Organizations",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cost Explorer",
        "AWS Budgets",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 141"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is hosting an application in the AWS Cloud. The company wants to verify that underlying AWS services and general AWS infrastructure are operating normally.\n\nWhich combination of AWS services can the company use to gather the required information? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Personal Health Dashboard",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Systems Manager",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "AWS Service Catalog"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS Service Health Dashboard",
        "code": "Question 142"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to migrate a PostgreSQL database from on-premises to Amazon RDS.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cloud Adoption Readiness Tool",
        "AWS Migration Hub",
        "AWS Application Migration Service"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 143"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which cloud concept is demonstrated by using AWS Compute Optimizer?",
      "correct_answer": "Rightsizing",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security validation",
        "Elasticity",
        "Global reach"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 144"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company hosts a large amount of data in AWS. The company wants to identify if any of the data should be considered sensitive.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet the requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Macie",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)",
        "Amazon CloudWatch"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 145"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to protect its AWS Cloud information, systems, and assets while performing risk assessment and mitigation tasks.\n\nWhich pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework is supported by these goals?",
      "correct_answer": "Security",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reliability",
        "Operational excellence",
        "Performance efficiency"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 146"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A user has a stateful workload that will run on Amazon EC2 for the next 3 years.\n\nWhat is the MOST cost-effective pricing model for this workload?",
      "correct_answer": "Reserved Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Dedicated Instances",
        "Spot Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 147"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who enables encryption of data at rest for Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS customers",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Support",
        "AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS)",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 148"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What can a user accomplish using AWS CloudTrail?",
      "correct_answer": "Record API calls made to AWS services.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Generate an IAM user credentials report.",
        "Assess the compliance of AWS resource configurations with policies and guidelines.",
        "Ensure that Amazon EC2 instances are patched with the latest security updates."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 149"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to host its workloads on AWS.\n\nWhich AWS service requires the company to update and patch the guest operating system?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon EC2",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "Amazon S3",
        "Amazon Aurora"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 150"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature will search for and identify AWS resources that are shared externally?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS IAM Access Analyzer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon OpenSearch Service",
        "AWS Control Tower",
        "AWS Fargate"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 151"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is migrating its workloads to the AWS Cloud. The company must retain full control of patch management for the guest operating systems that host its applications.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon EC2",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "AWS Lambda",
        "Amazon RDS"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 152"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "At what support level do users receive access to a support concierge?",
      "correct_answer": "Enterprise Support",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Basic Support",
        "Developer Support",
        "Business Support"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 153"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service can a company use to visually design and build serverless applications?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Application Composer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Lambda",
        "AWS Batch",
        "AWS App Runner"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 154"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate to AWS and use the same security software it uses on premises. The security software vendor offers its security software as a service on AWS.\n\nWhere can the company purchase the security solution?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Marketplace",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Partner Solutions Finder",
        "AWS Support Center",
        "AWS Management Console"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 155"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has deployed an Amazon EC2 instance.\n\nWhich option is an AWS responsibility under the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Configuration of infrastructure devices",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Managing and encrypting application data",
        "Installing updates and security patches of guest operating system",
        "Configuration of security groups on each instance"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 156"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is the purpose of having an internet gateway within a VPC?",
      "correct_answer": "To allow communication between the VPC and the internet",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "To create a VPN connection to the VPC",
        "To impose bandwidth constraints on internet traffic",
        "To load balance traffic from the internet across Amazon EC2 instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 157"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate its PostgreSQL database to AWS. The company does not use the database frequently.\n\nWhich AWS service or resource will meet these requirements with the LEAST management overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Aurora Serverless",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "PostgreSQL on Amazon EC2",
        "Amazon RDS for PostgreSQL",
        "Amazon Aurora PostgreSQL-Compatible Edition"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 158"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using Amazon DynamoDB for its application database.\n\nWhich tasks are the responsibility of AWS, according to the AWS shared responsibility model? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Provide public endpoints to store and retrieve data.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Classify data.",
        "Configure access permissions.",
        "Manage encryption options."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Manage the infrastructure layer and the operating system.",
        "code": "Question 159"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to create a globally accessible ecommerce platform for its customers. The company wants to use a highly available and scalable DNS web service to connect users to the platform.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Route 53",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon EC2",
        "Amazon VPC",
        "Amazon RDS"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 160"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which maintenance task is the customer’s responsibility, according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon EC2 updates and security patches",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Physical connectivity among Availability Zones",
        "Network switch maintenance",
        "Hardware updates and firmware patches"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 161"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to improve its security posture by reviewing user activity through API calls.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudTrail",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS WAF",
        "Amazon Detective",
        "Amazon CloudWatch"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 162"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is migrating to the AWS Cloud and plans to run experimental workloads for 3 to 6 months on AWS.\n\nWhich pricing model will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use On-Demand Instances.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use Savings Plans for a 3-year term.",
        "Use Dedicated Hosts.",
        "Buy Reserved Instances."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 163"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company that has AWS Enterprise Support is launching a new version of a popular product in 2 months. The company expects a large increase in traffic to its website. The website is hosted on Amazon EC2 instances.\n\nWhich action should the company take to assess its readiness to scale for this launch?",
      "correct_answer": "Use AWS Infrastructure Event Management (IEM) support.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Replace the EC2 instances with AWS Lambda functions.",
        "Submit a request on AWS Marketplace to monitor the event.",
        "Review the coverage reports in the AWS Cost Management console."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 164"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to launch multiple workloads on AWS. Each workload is related to a different business unit. The company wants to separate and track costs for each business unit.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Use AWS Organizations and create one account for each business unit.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use a spreadsheet to control the owners and cost of each resource.",
        "Use an Amazon DynamoDB table to record costs for each business unit.",
        "Use the AWS Billing console to assign owners to resources and track costs."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 165"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants a time-series database service that makes it easier to store and analyze trillions of events each day.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Timestream",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Neptune",
        "Amazon Forecast",
        "Amazon DocumentDB (with MongoDB compatibility)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 166"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is a shared control between AWS and the customer, according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Configuration management",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Physical and environmental controls",
        "Data integrity authentication",
        "Identity and access management"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 167"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is running a monolithic on-premises application that does not scale and is difficult to maintain. The company has a plan to migrate the application to AWS and divide the application into microservices.\n\nWhich best practice of the AWS Well-Architected Framework is the company following with this plan?",
      "correct_answer": "Implement loosely coupled dependencies.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Integrate functional testing as part of AWS deployment.",
        "Use automation to deploy changes.",
        "Deploy the application to multiple locations."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 168"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company often does not use all of its current Amazon EC2 capacity to run stateless workloads. The company wants to optimize its EC2 costs.\n\nWhich EC2 instance type will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Spot Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Dedicated Instances",
        "Reserved Instances",
        "On-Demand Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 169"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to store data in Amazon S3. The company rarely access the data, and the data can be regenerated if necessary. The company wants to store the data in the most cost-effective storage class.\n\nWhich S3 storage class will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "S3 Standard",
        "S3 Intelligent-Tiering",
        "S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 170"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has migrated its workloads to AWS. The company wants to adopt AWS at scale and operate more efficiently and securely. Which AWS service or framework should the company use for operational support?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Managed Services (AMS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Support",
        "AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF)",
        "AWS Well-Architected Framework"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 171"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to provision and manage its AWS infrastructure by using the common programming languages Typescript, Python, Java, and .NET.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CodeBuild",
        "AWS CloudFormation",
        "AWS CLI"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 172"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which Amazon EC2 pricing model provides the MOST cost savings for an always-up, right-sized database server running for a project that will last 1 year?",
      "correct_answer": "Standard Reserved Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Convertible Reserved Instances",
        "Spot Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 173"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a physical tape library to store data backups. The tape library is running out of space. The company needs to extend the tape library's capacity to the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Storage Gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)",
        "Amazon S3"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 174"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using the AWS Free Tier for several AWS services for an application.\n\nWhat will happen if the Free Tier usage period expires or if the application use exceeds the Free Tier usage limits?",
      "correct_answer": "The company will be charged the standard pay-as-you-go service rates for the usage that exceeds the Free Tier usage.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Support will contact the company to set up standard service charges.",
        "The company will be charged for the services it consumed during the Free Tier period, plus additional charges for service consumption after the Free Tier period.",
        "The company's AWS account will be frozen and can be restarted after a payment plan is established."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 175"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to monitor its workload performance. The company wants to ensure that the cloud services are delivered at a level that meets its business needs.\n\nWhich AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) perspective will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Operations",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Business",
        "Governance",
        "Platform"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 176"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate its applications to the AWS Cloud. The company plans to identify and prioritize any business transformation opportunities and evaluate its AWS Cloud readiness.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Managed Services (AMS)",
        "AWS Well-Architected Framework",
        "AWS Migration Hub"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 177"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company need an AWS service that provides a clear baseline of what the company runs in its on-premises data centers. The company needs the projected cost to run its on-premises workloads in the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhat AWS service or tool will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Migration Evaluator",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Compute Optimizer",
        "AWS Cost Explorer",
        "AWS Systems Manager Agent (SSM Agent)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 178"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an AWS account. The company wants to audit its password and access key rotation details for compliance purposes.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "IAM credential report",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "IAM Access Analyzer",
        "AWS Artifact",
        "AWS Audit Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 179"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company acquired another corporation. The company now has two AWS accounts.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool can the company use to consolidate the billing for these two accounts?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Organizations",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Systems Manager",
        "AWS License Manager",
        "Cost Explorer"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 180"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to set up its workloads to perform their intended functions and recover quickly from failure.\n\nWhich pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework aligns with these goals?",
      "correct_answer": "Reliability",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Performance efficiency",
        "Sustainability",
        "Security"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 181"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following is a managed AWS service that is used specifically for extract, transform, and load (ETL) data?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Glue",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Athena",
        "Amazon S3",
        "AWS Snowball Edge"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 182"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate petabytes of data from its on-premises data center to AWS. The company does not want to use an internet connection to perform the migration.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Snowmobile",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS DataSync",
        "Amazon Connect",
        "AWS Direct Connect"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 183"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to receive alerts to monitor its overall operating costs for its AWS public cloud infrastructure.\n\nWhich AWS offering will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Budgets",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon EventBridge",
        "Compute Savings Plans",
        "Migration Evaluator"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 184"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "How does the AWS Enterprise Support Concierge team help users?",
      "correct_answer": "Answering billing and account inquiries",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Supporting application development",
        "Providing architecture guidance",
        "Answering questions regarding technical support cases"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 185"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to run a simulation for 3 years without interruptions.\n\nWhich Amazon EC2 instance purchasing option will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Reserved Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Spot Instances",
        "Dedicated Hosts",
        "On-Demand Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 186"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or resource can provide discounts on some AWS service costs in exchange for a spending commitment?",
      "correct_answer": "Savings Plans",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Detective",
        "AWS Pricing Calculator",
        "Basic Support"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 187"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following are pillars of the AWS Well-Architected Framework? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Performance efficiency",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "High availability",
        "Cost optimization",
        "Going global in minutes",
        "Continuous development"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 188"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use Amazon EC2 instances to provide a static website to users all over the world. The company needs to minimize latency for the users.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use Amazon CloudFront with the EC2 instances configured as the source.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use EC2 instances in multiple edge locations.",
        "Use EC2 instances in the same Availability Zone but in different AWS Regions.",
        "Use EC2 instances in the same Availability Zone but in different AWS accounts."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 189"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to receive a notification when a specific AWS cost threshold is reached.\n\nWhich AWS services or tools can the company use to meet this requirement? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Budgets",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS)",
        "Cost Explorer",
        "AWS Cost and Usage Report"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "code": "Question 190"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A team of researchers is going to collect data at remote locations around the world. Many locations do not have internet connectivity. The team needs to capture the data in the field, and transfer it to the AWS Cloud later.\n\nWhich AWS service will support these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Snow Family",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Outposts",
        "AWS Transfer Family",
        "AWS Migration Hub"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 191"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following are benefits that a company receives when it moves an on-premises production workload to AWS? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS offers high availability.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS trains the company's staff on the use of all the AWS services.",
        "AWS manages all security in the cloud.",
        "AWS offers free support from technical account managers (TAMs)."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS provides economies of scale.",
        "code": "Question 192"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has decided to adopt Amazon EC2 infrastructure and wants to scale various stateless services for short-term usage.\n\nWhich EC2 pricing model is MOST cost-efficient to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Spot Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Reserved Instances",
        "Dedicated Hosts"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 193"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following are benefits of AWS Trusted Advisor? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Cost optimization recommendations",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Access to Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS)",
        "Hourly refresh of the service limit checks",
        "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) approval management"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Security checks",
        "code": "Question 194"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to save costs by archiving data that is no longer frequently accessed by end users.\n\nWhich Amazon S3 feature will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "S3 Lifecycle",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "S3 Versioning",
        "S3 Object Lock",
        "S3 Inventory"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 195"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which cloud computing advantage is a company applying when it uses AWS Regions to increase application availability to users in different countries?",
      "correct_answer": "Global reach",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Pay-as-you-go pricing",
        "Capacity forecasting",
        "Economies of scale"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 196"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants an AWS service to collect and process 10 TB of data locally and transfer the data to AWS. The company has intermittent connectivity.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Snowball Edge",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)",
        "AWS DataSync",
        "AWS Backup"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 197"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following is an AWS Well-Architected Framework design principle for operational excellence in the AWS Cloud?",
      "correct_answer": "Make frequent, small, reversible changes.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Go global in minutes.",
        "Implement a strong foundation of identity and access management",
        "Stop spending money on hardware infrastructure for data center operations."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 198"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is a benefit of using AWS serverless computing?",
      "correct_answer": "Management of infrastructure is offloaded to AWS.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Application deployment and management are not required.",
        "Application security will be fully managed by AWS.",
        "Monitoring and logging are not needed."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 199"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A developer wants AWS users to access AWS services by using temporary security credentials.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature should the developer use to provide these credentials?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Security Token Service (AWS STS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "IAM policies",
        "IAM user groups",
        "AWS IAM Identity Center (AWS Single Sign-On)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 200"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or resource provides answers to the most frequently asked security-related questions that AWS receives from its users?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Knowledge Center",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Artifact",
        "Amazon Connect",
        "AWS Chatbot"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 201"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A global company wants to use a managed security service for protection from SQL injection attacks. The service also must provide detailed logging information about access to the company's ecommerce applications.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS WAF",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Network Firewall",
        "Amazon RDS for SQL Server",
        "Amazon GuardDuty"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 202"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is migrating its on-premises server to an Amazon EC2 instance. The server must stay active at all times for the next 12 months.\n\nWhich EC2 pricing option is the MOST cost-effective for the company's workload?",
      "correct_answer": "Reserved Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "On-Demand",
        "Dedicated Hosts",
        "Spot Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 203"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following is the customer's responsibility under the AWS shared responsibility model? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Maintain the configuration of guest operating systems and applications.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Maintain the configuration of infrastructure devices.",
        "Maintain patching and updates within the hardware infrastructure.",
        "Maintain infrastructure hardware."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Manage decisions involving encryption options.",
        "code": "Question 204"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to verify if multi-factor authentication (MFA) is enabled for all users within its AWS accounts.\n\nWhich AWS service or resource will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "IAM credential reports",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Cost and Usage Report",
        "AWS Artifact",
        "Amazon CloudFront reports"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 205"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses AWS security services and tools. The company needs a service to help manage the security alerts and must organize the alerts into a single dashboard.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Security Hub",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "Amazon Macie"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 206"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to run its workloads in the AWS Cloud effectively, reduce management overhead, and improve processes.\n\nWhich AWS Well-Architected Framework pillar represents these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Operational excellence",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reliability",
        "Performance efficiency",
        "Cost optimization"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 207"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses Amazon S3 to store records that can contain personally identifiable information (PII). The company wants a solution that can monitor all S3 buckets for PII and immediately alert staff about vulnerabilities.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Macie",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "Amazon Detective",
        "AWS Shield"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 208"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service allows users to download security and compliance reports about the AWS infrastructure on demand?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Artifact",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "AWS Security Hub",
        "AWS Shield"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 209"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An external auditor has requested that a company provide a list of all its IAM users, including the status of users' credentials and access keys.\n\nWhat is the SIMPLEST way to provide this information?",
      "correct_answer": "Download the IAM credential report, then provide the report to the auditor.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an IAM user account for the auditor, granting the auditor administrator permissions.",
        "Take a screenshot of each user's page in the AWS Management Console, then provide the screenshots to the auditor.",
        "Download the AWS Trusted Advisor report, then provide the report to the auditor."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 210"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which task can a company perform by using security groups in the AWS Cloud?",
      "correct_answer": "Allow access to an Amazon EC2 instance through only a specific port.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deny access to malicious IP addresses at a subnet level.",
        "Protect data that is cached by Amazon CloudFront.",
        "Apply a stateless firewall to an Amazon EC2 instance."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 211"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which tasks are customer responsibilities, according to the AWS shared responsibility model? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Configure the AWS provided security group firewall.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Determine which Availability Zones to use for Amazon S3 buckets.",
        "Patch or upgrade Amazon DynamoDB.",
        "Select Amazon EC2 instances to run AWS Lambda on."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Classify company assets in the AWS Cloud.",
        "code": "Question 212"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company plans to run a compute-intensive workload that uses graphics processing units (GPUs).\n\nWhich Amazon EC2 instance type should the company use?",
      "correct_answer": "Accelerated computing",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Compute optimized",
        "Storage optimized",
        "General purpose"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 213"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following are features of network ACLs as they are used in the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "They are stateless.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "They are stateful.",
        "They evaluate all rules before allowing traffic.",
        "They operate at the instance level."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "They process rules in order, starting with the lowest numbered rule, when deciding whether to allow traffic.",
        "code": "Question 214"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which capabilities are in the platform perspective of the AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF)? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Data engineering",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Performance and capacity management",
        "Infrastructure protection",
        "Change and release management"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Continuous integration and continuous delivery (CI/CD)",
        "code": "Question 215"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "According to the AWS shared responsibility model, the customer is responsible for applying the latest security updates and patches for which of the following?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon EC2 instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "Amazon RDS instances",
        "Amazon S3"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 216"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which Amazon S3 storage class is MOST cost-effective for unknown access patterns?",
      "correct_answer": "S3 Intelligent-Tiering",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "S3 Standard",
        "S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA)",
        "S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 217"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which options are AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) security perspective capabilities? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Incident response",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Observability",
        "Incident and problem management",
        "Availability and continuity"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Infrastructure protection",
        "code": "Question 218"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a managed IAM policy that does not grant the necessary permissions for users to accomplish required tasks.\n\nHow can this be resolved?",
      "correct_answer": "Create a custom IAM policy.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Enable AWS Shield Advanced.",
        "Use a third-party web application firewall (WAF) managed rule from the AWS Marketplace.",
        "Use AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) to create a customer-managed key."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 219"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who is responsible for managing IAM user access and secret keys according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "The customer is responsible for rotating keys.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "IAM access and secret keys are static, so there is no need to rotate them.",
        "AWS will rotate the keys whenever required.",
        "The AWS Support team will rotate keys when requested by the customer."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 220"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to run a pre-installed third-party firewall on an Amazon EC2 instance.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature can provide this solution?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Marketplace",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Network ACLs",
        "Security groups",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 221"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS Cloud benefit gives a company the ability to quickly deploy cloud resources to access compute, storage, and database infrastructures in a matter of minutes?",
      "correct_answer": "Agility",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Elasticity",
        "Cost savings",
        "Reliability"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 222"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a centralized group of users with large file storage requirements that have exceeded the space available on premises. The company wants to extend its file storage capabilities for this group while retaining the performance benefit of sharing content locally.\n\nWhat is the MOST operationally efficient AWS solution for this scenario?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure and deploy an AWS Storage Gateway file gateway. Connect each user’s workstation to the file gateway.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an Amazon S3 bucket for each user. Mount each bucket by using an S3 file system mounting utility.",
        "Move each user’s working environment to Amazon WorkSpaces. Set up an Amazon WorkDocs account for each user.",
        "Deploy an Amazon EC2 instance and attach an Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) Provisioned IOPS volume. Share the EBS volume directly with the users."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 223"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following are pillars of the AWS Well-Architected Framework? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Reliability",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Availability",
        "Scalability",
        "Responsive design"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Operational excellence",
        "code": "Question 224"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following is entirely the responsibility of AWS, according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Physical and environmental controls",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security awareness and training",
        "Development of an IAM password policy",
        "Patching of the guest operating system"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 225"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following is a characteristic of the AWS account root user?",
      "correct_answer": "The root user is the first sign-in identity that is available when an AWS account is created.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The root user is the only user that can be configured with multi-factor authentication (MFA).",
        "The root user is the only user that can access the AWS Management Console.",
        "The root user has a password that cannot be changed."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 226"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An Amazon EC2 instance previously used for development is inaccessible and no longer appears in the AWS Management Console.\n\nWhich AWS service should be used to determine what action made this EC2 instance inaccessible?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudTraiI",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CloudWatch Logs",
        "AWS Security Hub",
        "Amazon Inspector"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 227"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company's application developers need to quickly provision and manage AWS services by using scripts.\n\nWhich AWS offering should the developers use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CLI",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CodeBuild",
        "AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF)",
        "AWS Systems Manager Session Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 228"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate unstructured data to AWS. The data needs to be securely moved with inflight encryption and end-to-end data validation.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS DataSync",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Application Migration Service",
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
        "AWS Migration Hub"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 229"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A development team wants to deploy multiple test environments for an application in a fast, repeatable manner.\n\nWhich AWS service should the team use?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudFormation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon EC2",
        "Amazon QuickSight",
        "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 230"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to quickly implement a continuous integration/continuous delivery (CI/CD) pipeline.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CodeStar",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Config",
        "Amazon Cognito",
        "AWS DataSync"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 231"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS Cloud deployment model uses AWS Outposts as part of the application deployment infrastructure?",
      "correct_answer": "Hybrid",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "On-premises",
        "Serverless",
        "Cloud-native"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 232"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following is a fully managed graph database service on AWS?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Neptune",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Aurora",
        "Amazon FSx",
        "Amazon DynamoDB"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 233"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service could an administrator use to provide desktop environments for several employees?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS WorkSpaces",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Organizations",
        "AWS Fargate",
        "AWS WAF"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 234"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature is used to send both text and email messages from distributed applications?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Simple Email Service (Amazon SES)",
        "Amazon CloudWatch alerts",
        "Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 235"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature gives users the ability to capture information about network traffic in a VPC?",
      "correct_answer": "VPC Flow Logs",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "VPC route tables",
        "AWS CloudTrail"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 236"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which type of AWS storage is ephemeral and is deleted when an Amazon EC2 instance is stopped or terminated?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon EC2 instance store",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)",
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
        "Amazon S3"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 237"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to provide access to Windows file shares in AWS from its on-premises workloads. The company does not want to provision any additional infrastructure or applications in its data center.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon FSx File Gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS DataSync",
        "Amazon S3",
        "AWS Snow Family"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 238"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants durable storage for static content and infinitely scalable data storage infrastructure at the lowest cost.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company choose?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon S3",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)",
        "AWS Storage Gateway",
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 239"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An ecommerce company wants to use Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling to add and remove EC2 instances based on CPU utilization.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature can initiate an Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling action to achieve this goal?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon CloudWatch alarm",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS)",
        "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)",
        "AWS Systems Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 240"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to transform its workforce by attracting and developing a digitally fluent high-performance workforce. The company wants to attract a diverse and inclusive workforce with appropriate mix of technical and non-technical skills.\n\nWhich AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) perspective will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "People",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Business",
        "Platform",
        "Operations"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 241"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to move its on-premises databases to managed cloud database services by using a simplified migration process.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool can help the company meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Storage Gateway",
        "AWS Application Migration Service",
        "AWS DataSync"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 242"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs a fully managed file server that natively supports Microsoft workloads and file systems. The file server must also support the SMB protocol.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon FSx for Windows File Server",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
        "Amazon FSx for Lustre",
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 243"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has been storing monthly reports in an Amazon S3 bucket. The company exports the report data into comma-separated values (.csv) files. A developer wants to write a simple query that can read all of these files and generate a summary report.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature should the developer use to meet these requirements with the LEAST amount of operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Athena",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon S3 Select",
        "Amazon Redshift",
        "Amazon EC2"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 244"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS feature provides a no-cost platform for AWS users to join community groups, ask questions, find answers, and read community-generated articles about best practices?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS re:Post",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Knowledge Center",
        "AWS IQ",
        "AWS Enterprise Support"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 245"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A user needs programmatic access to AWS resources through the AWS CLI or the AWS API.\n\nWhich option will provide the user with the appropriate access?",
      "correct_answer": "Access keys",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "SSH public keys",
        "AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS) keys"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 246"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to search for text in documents that are stored in Amazon S3.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Kendra",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Lex"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 247"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS services make use of global edge locations? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon CloudFront",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Fargate",
        "AWS Wavelength",
        "Amazon VPC"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS Global Accelerator",
        "code": "Question 248"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A user needs a relational database but does not have the resources to manage the hardware, resiliency, and replication.\n\nWhich AWS service option meets the user's requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Choose Amazon RDS for MySQL.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Run MySQL on Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS).",
        "Run MySQL on Amazon EC2.",
        "Choose Amazon ElastiCache for Redis."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 249"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to deploy applications in the AWS Cloud as quickly as possible. The company also needs to minimize the complexity that is related to the management of AWS resources.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Config",
        "Amazon EC2",
        "Amazon Personalize"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 250"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which mechanism allows developers to access AWS services from application code?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Software Development Kit",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Management Console",
        "AWS CodePipeline",
        "AWS Config"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 251"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is migrating to the AWS Cloud. The company wants to understand and identify potential security misconfigurations or unexpected behaviors. The company wants to prioritize any protective controls it might need.\n\nWhich AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) security perspective capability will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Threat detection",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Identity and access management",
        "Platform engineering",
        "Availability and continuity management"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 252"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to establish a private network connection between AWS and its corporate network.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Direct Connect",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Connect",
        "Amazon Route 53",
        "VPC peering"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 253"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS services or features give users the ability to create a network connection between two VPCs? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "VPC peering",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "VPC endpoints",
        "Amazon Route 53",
        "AWS Direct Connect"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS Transit Gateway",
        "code": "Question 254"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service converts text to lifelike voices?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Polly",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Textract"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 255"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use application stacks to run a workload in the AWS Cloud. The company wants to use pre-configured instances.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Lightsail",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Athena",
        "AWS Outposts",
        "Amazon EC2"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 256"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company runs thousands of simultaneous simulations using AWS Batch. Each simulation is stateless, is fault tolerant, and runs for up to 3 hours.\n\nWhich pricing model enables the company to optimize costs and meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Spot Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reserved Instances",
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Dedicated Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 257"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS services are supported by Savings Plans? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon EC2",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon RDS",
        "Amazon Redshift",
        "Amazon DynamoDB"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Amazon SageMaker",
        "code": "Question 258"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or tool can provide rightsizing recommendations for Amazon EC2 resources at no additional cost?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Cost Explorer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Well-Architected Tool",
        "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "Amazon S3 analytics"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 259"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company operates a petabyte-scale data warehouse to analyze its data. The company wants a solution that will not require manual hardware and software management.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Redshift",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon DocumentDB (with MongoDB compatibility)",
        "Amazon Neptune",
        "Amazon ElastiCache"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 260"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A library wants to automate the classification of electronic books based on the contents of the books.\n\nWhich AWS service should the library use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Comprehend",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Redshift",
        "Amazon CloudSearch",
        "Amazon Aurora"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 261"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which task is a responsibility of AWS, according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Protection of physical network infrastructure",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Encryption of application data",
        "Authentication of application users",
        "Configuration of firewalls"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 262"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which options are AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) cloud transformation journey recommendations? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Envision phase",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Assess phase",
        "Mobilize phase",
        "Migrate and modernize phase"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Align phase",
        "code": "Question 263"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to generate a list of IAM users. The company also wants to view the status of various credentials that are associated with the users, such as password, access keys, and multi-factor authentication (MFA) devices.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "IAM credential report",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS IAM Identity Center (AWS Single Sign-On)",
        "AWS Identity and Access Management Access Analyzer",
        "AWS Cost and Usage Report"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 264"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is designing its AWS workloads so that components can be updated regularly and so that changes can be made in small, reversible increments.\n\nWhich pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework does this design support?",
      "correct_answer": "Operational excellence",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security",
        "Performance efficiency",
        "Reliability"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 265"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to track tags, buckets, and prefixes for its Amazon S3 objects.\n\nWhich S3 feature will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "S3 Inventory report",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "S3 Lifecycle",
        "S3 Versioning",
        "S3 ACLs"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 266"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to allow users to authenticate and authorize multiple AWS accounts by using a single set of credentials.\n\nWhich AWS service or resource will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS IAM Identity Center (AWS Single Sign-On)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Organizations",
        "IAM user",
        "AWS Control Tower"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 267"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What does the concept of agility mean in AWS Cloud computing? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "The speed at which AWS resources are implemented",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The speed at which AWS creates new AWS Regions",
        "The elimination of wasted capacity",
        "The low cost of entry into cloud computing"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "The ability to experiment quickly",
        "code": "Question 268"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company created an Amazon EC2 instance. The company wants to control the incoming and outgoing network traffic at the instance level.\n\nWhich AWS resource or service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Security groups",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Shield",
        "Network Access Analyzer",
        "VPC endpoints"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 269"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use the AWS Cloud to deploy an application globally.\n\nWhich architecture deployment model should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Multi-Region",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Single-Region",
        "Multi-AZ",
        "Single-AZ"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 270"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants a web application to interact with various AWS services.\n\nWhich AWS service or resource will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Management Console",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CloudShell",
        "AWS Marketplace",
        "AWS CLI"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 271"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is migrating its applications from on-premises to the AWS Cloud. The company wants to ensure that the applications are assigned only the minimum permissions that are needed to perform all operations.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "Amazon Macie",
        "Amazon GuardDuty"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 272"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which options are AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) governance perspective capabilities? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Cloud financial management",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Identity and access management",
        "Innovation management",
        "Product management"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Application portfolio management",
        "code": "Question 273"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service provides a single location to track the progress of application migrations?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Migration Hub",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Application Discovery Service",
        "AWS Application Migration Service",
        "AWS Service Catalog"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 274"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company launched an Amazon EC2 instance with the latest Amazon Linux 2 Amazon Machine Image (AMI).\n\nWhich actions can a system administrator take to connect to the EC2 instance? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Use Amazon EC2 Instance Connect.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use a Remote Desktop Protocol (RDP) connection.",
        "Use AWS Batch.",
        "Use Amazon Connect."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Use AWS Systems Manager Session Manager.",
        "code": "Question 275"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which architecture concept describes the ability to deploy resources on demand and release resources when they are no longer needed?",
      "correct_answer": "Elasticity",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "High availability",
        "Decoupled architecture",
        "Resilience"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 276"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which task requires a user to sign in as the AWS account root user?",
      "correct_answer": "The deletion of an AWS account",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The deletion of IAM users",
        "The creation of an organization in AWS Organizations",
        "The deletion of Amazon EC2 instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 277"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What does the Amazon S3 Intelligent-Tiering storage class offer?",
      "correct_answer": "Automatic cost savings by moving objects between tiers based on access pattern changes",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Payment flexibility by reserving storage capacity",
        "Long-term retention of data by copying the data to an encrypted Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume",
        "Secure, durable, and lowest cost storage for data archival"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 278"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to block SQL injection attacks.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature can meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS WAF",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Shield",
        "Network ACLs",
        "Security groups"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 279"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs Amazon EC2 instances for a workload that can tolerate interruptions.\n\nWhich EC2 instance purchasing option meets this requirement with the LARGEST discount compared to On-Demand prices?",
      "correct_answer": "Spot Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Convertible Reserved Instances",
        "Standard Reserved Instances",
        "Dedicated Hosts"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 280"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to migrate to the AWS Cloud. The company wants to identify measurable business outcomes that will explain the value of the company's decision to migrate.\n\nWhich phase of the cloud transformation journey includes these activities?",
      "correct_answer": "Envision",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Align",
        "Scale",
        "Launch"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 281"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or component allows inbound traffic from the internet to access a VPC?",
      "correct_answer": "Internet gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "NAT gateway",
        "AWS WAF",
        "VPC peering"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 282"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service can companies use to create infrastructure from code?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudFormation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS)",
        "AWS Outposts",
        "AWS CodePipeline"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 283"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which guideline is a well-architected design principle for building cloud applications?",
      "correct_answer": "Design for automated recovery from failure.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Keep static data closer to compute resources.",
        "Provision resources for peak capacity.",
        "Use tightly coupled components."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 284"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to move 75 petabytes of data from its on-premises data centers to AWS.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Snowmobile",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Snowball Edge Storage Optimized",
        "AWS Direct Connect",
        "AWS Storage Gateway"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 285"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following are pillars of the AWS Well-Architected Framework? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Performance efficiency",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Resource scalability",
        "System elasticity",
        "Agile development"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Operational excellence",
        "code": "Question 286"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to connect its on-premises data center to the AWS Cloud. The company needs a dedicated, low-latency connection with consistent network performance.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Direct Connect",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Global Accelerator",
        "Amazon CloudFront",
        "AWS Managed VPN"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 287"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which design principles should a company apply to AWS Cloud workloads to maximize sustainability and minimize environmental impact? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Maximize utilization of Amazon EC2 instances.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Minimize utilization of Amazon EC2 instances.",
        "Minimize usage of managed services.",
        "Force frequent application reinstallations by users."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Reduce the need for users to reinstall applications.",
        "code": "Question 288"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "In which ways does the AWS Cloud offer lower total cost of ownership (TCO) of computing resources than on-premises data centers? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS replaces upfront capital expenditures with pay-as-you-go costs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS is designed for high availability, which eliminates user downtime.",
        "AWS eliminates the need for on-premises IT staff.",
        "AWS offers a single pricing model for Amazon EC2 instances."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS uses economies of scale to continually reduce prices.",
        "code": "Question 289"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature identifies whether an Amazon S3 bucket or an IAM role has been shared with an external entity?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS IAM Access Analyzer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Service Catalog",
        "AWS Systems Manager",
        "AWS Organizations"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 290"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to deploy some of its resources in the AWS Cloud. To meet regulatory requirements, the data must remain local and on premises. There must be low latency between AWS and the company resources.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature can be used to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Outposts",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Local Zones",
        "Availability Zones",
        "AWS Wavelength Zones"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 291"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following AWS services are serverless? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Fargate",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Outposts",
        "Amazon EC2",
        "Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS Lambda",
        "code": "Question 292"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "When a user wants to utilize their existing per-socket, per-core, or per-virtual machine software licenses for a Microsoft Windows server running on AWS, which Amazon EC2 instance type is required?",
      "correct_answer": "Dedicated Hosts",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Spot Instances",
        "Dedicated Instances",
        "Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 293"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A solutions architect needs to maintain a fleet of Amazon EC2 instances so that any impaired instances are replaced with new ones.\n\nWhich AWS service should the solutions architect use?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Auto Scaling",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)",
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "AWS Shield"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 294"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service provides on-premises applications with low-latency access to data that is stored in the AWS Cloud?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Storage Gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CloudFront",
        "AWS Backup",
        "AWS DataSync"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 295"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What does Amazon CloudFront provide?",
      "correct_answer": "Secure delivery of data, videos, applications, and APIs to users globally with low latency",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Automatic scaling for all resources to power an application from a single unified interface",
        "Ability to directly manage traffic globally through a variety of routing types, including latency-based routing, geo DNS, geoproximity, and weighted round robin",
        "Automatic distribution of incoming application traffic across multiple targets, such as Amazon EC2 instances, containers, IP addresses, and AWS Lambda functions"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 296"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service supports the deployment and management of applications in the AWS Cloud?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CodeGuru",
        "AWS Fargate",
        "AWS CodeCommit"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 297"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to integrate natural language processing (NLP) into business intelligence (BI) dashboards. The company wants to ask questions and receive answers with relevant visualizations.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon QuickSight Q",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Macie",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Lex"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 298"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which Amazon S3 feature or storage class uses the AWS backbone network and edge locations to reduce latencies from the end user to Amazon S3?",
      "correct_answer": "S3 Transfer Acceleration",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "S3 Cross-Region Replication",
        "S3 Event Notifications",
        "S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 299"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service provides the ability to host a NoSQL database in the AWS Cloud?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Aurora",
        "Amazon RDS",
        "Amazon Redshift"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 300"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A cloud practitioner needs to obtain AWS compliance reports before migrating an environment to the AWS Cloud.\n\nHow can these reports be generated?",
      "correct_answer": "Download the reports from AWS Artifact.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Contact the AWS Compliance team.",
        "Open a case with AWS Support.",
        "Generate the reports with Amazon Macie."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 301"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service is a relational database compatible with MySQL and PostgreSQL?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Aurora",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Redshift",
        "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "Amazon Neptune"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 302"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which architecture design principle describes the need to isolate failures between dependent components in the AWS Cloud?",
      "correct_answer": "Loosely couple components.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use a monolithic design.",
        "Design for automation.",
        "Design for single points of failure."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 303"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which benefit of cloud computing gives a company the ability to deploy applications to users all over the world through a network of AWS Regions, Availability Zones, and edge locations?",
      "correct_answer": "Global reach",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Economy of scale",
        "Agility",
        "High availability"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 304"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service makes it easier to monitor and troubleshoot application logs and cloud resources?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon CloudWatch",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon EC2",
        "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)",
        "AWS CloudTrail"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 305"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service uses AWS Compute Optimizer to provide sizing recommendations based on workload metrics?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon EC2",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon RDS",
        "Amazon Lightsail",
        "AWS Step Functions"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 306"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service will help a company plan a migration to AWS by collecting the configuration, usage, and behavior data of on-premises data centers?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Application Discovery Service",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Resource Groups",
        "AWS Service Catalog",
        "AWS Systems Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 307"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service uses a combination of publishers and subscribers?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Lambda",
        "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "AWS CloudFormation"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 308"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is in the early stages of planning a migration to AWS. The company wants to obtain the monthly predicted total AWS cost of ownership for future Amazon EC2 instances and associated storage.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Pricing Calculator",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Compute Optimizer",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "AWS Application Migration Service"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 309"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or tool will monitor AWS resources and applications in real time?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon CloudWatch",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "AWS CloudTrail",
        "AWS Cost Explorer"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 310"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) capability belongs to the business perspective?",
      "correct_answer": "Data science",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Program and project management",
        "Observability",
        "Change and release management"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 311"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An ecommerce company has migrated its IT infrastructure from an on-premises data center to the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich cost is the company’s direct responsibility?",
      "correct_answer": "Cost of application software licenses",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cost of the hardware infrastructure on AWS",
        "Cost of power for the AWS servers",
        "Cost of physical security for the AWS data center"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 312"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS resource can help a company reduce its costs in exchange for a usage commitment when using Amazon EC2 instances?",
      "correct_answer": "Compute Savings Plans",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Auto Scaling group",
        "On-Demand Instance",
        "EC2 instance store"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 313"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which perspective in the AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) includes a capability for well-designed data and analytics architecture?",
      "correct_answer": "Platform",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security",
        "Governance",
        "Operations"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 314"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which options are AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) people perspective capabilities? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Organizational alignment",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Portfolio management",
        "Risk management",
        "Modern application development"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Organization design",
        "code": "Question 315"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs a bridge between technology and business to help evolve to a culture of continuous growth and learning.\n\nWhich perspective in the AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) serves as this bridge?",
      "correct_answer": "People",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Governance",
        "Operations",
        "Security"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 316"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is a responsibility of AWS under the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Patch management of the underlying infrastructure for managed services",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Application data security",
        "Patch management for applications that run on Amazon EC2 instances",
        "Application identity and access management"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 317"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or resource can identify and provide reports on IAM resources in one AWS account that is shared with another AWS account?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Identity and Access Management Access Analyzer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "IAM credential report",
        "AWS IAM Identity Center (AWS Single Sign-On)",
        "Amazon Cognito user pool"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 318"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS Well-Architected Framework pillar focuses on structured and streamlined allocation of computing resources?",
      "correct_answer": "Performance efficiency",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reliability",
        "Operational excellence",
        "Sustainability"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 319"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) capabilities belong to the governance perspective? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Program and project management",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Product management",
        "Portfolio management",
        "Event management"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Risk management",
        "code": "Question 320"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use AWS Managed Services (AMS) for operational support and wants to understand the scope of AMS.\n\nWhich AMS feature will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Landing zone and network management",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Customer application development",
        "DevSecOps pipeline configuration",
        "Application log monitoring"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 321"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate its on-premises NoSQL workload to Amazon DynamoDB.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Migration Hub",
        "Migration Evaluator",
        "AWS Application Migration Service"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 322"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is setting up AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) on an AWS account.\n\nWhich recommendation complies with IAM security best practices?",
      "correct_answer": "Turn on multi-factor authentication (MFA) for added security during the login process.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use the account root user access keys for administrative tasks.",
        "Grant broad permissions so that all company employees can access the resources they need.",
        "Avoid rotating credentials to prevent issues in production applications."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 323"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is in the process of finding correct Amazon EC2 instance types and sizes to meet its performance and capacity requirements. The company wants to find the lowest possible cost.\n\nWhich option accurately characterizes the company's actions?",
      "correct_answer": "Rightsizing",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Auto Scaling",
        "Storage tiering",
        "Instance scheduling"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 324"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to manage sign-in security for workforce users. The company needs to create workforce users and centrally manage their access across all the company's AWS accounts and applications.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS IAM Identity Center (AWS Single Sign-On)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Audit Manager",
        "Amazon Cognito",
        "AWS Security Hub"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 325"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants a report that lists the status of multi-factor authentication (MFA) devices that all users in the company's AWS account use.\n\nWhich AWS feature or service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "IAM credential reports",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Cost and Usage Reports",
        "Detailed Billing Reports - D AWS Cost Explorer reports"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 326"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use machine learning capabilities to analyze log data from its Amazon EC2 instances and efficiently conduct security investigations.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Detective - D Amazon GuardDuty",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "Amazon QuickSight"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 327"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is launching a mobile app in the AWS Cloud. The company wants the app's users to sign in through social media identity providers (IdPs).\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Cognito",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Lambda",
        "AWS Secrets Manager",
        "Amazon CloudFront"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 328"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which complimentary AWS service or tool creates data-driven business cases for cloud planning?",
      "correct_answer": "Migration Evaluator",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Billing Conductor",
        "AWS Billing Console",
        "Amazon Forecast"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 329"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which cloud concept is demonstrated by using AWS Cost Explorer?",
      "correct_answer": "Rightsizing",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reliability",
        "Resilience",
        "Modernization"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 330"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to deploy a non-containerized Java-based web application on AWS. The company wants to use a managed service to quickly deploy the application. The company wants the service to automatically provision capacity, load balance, scale, and monitor application health.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)",
        "AWS Lambda",
        "Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 331"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or tool gives users the ability to connect with AWS and deploy resources programmatically?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS SDKs",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon QuickSight",
        "AWS PrivateLink",
        "AWS Direct Connect"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 332"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has deployed a web application to Amazon EC2 instances. The EC2 instances have low usage.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature should the company use to rightsize the EC2 instances?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Compute Optimizer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Config",
        "AWS Cost Anomaly Detection",
        "AWS Budgets"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 333"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "According to security best practices, how should an Amazon EC2 instance be given access to an Amazon S3 bucket?",
      "correct_answer": "Have the EC2 instance assume a role to obtain the privileges to upload the file.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Hard code an IAM user’s secret key and access key directly in the application, and upload the file.",
        "Store the IAM user’s secret key and access key in a text file on the EC2 instance, read the keys, then upload the file.",
        "Modify the S3 bucket policy so that any service can upload to it at any time."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 334"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Elasticity in the AWS Cloud refers to which of the following? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "The ability to rightsize resources as demand shifts",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "How quickly an Amazon EC2 instance can be restarted",
        "The maximum amount of RAM an Amazon EC2 instance can use",
        "The pay-as-you-go billing model"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "How easily resources can be procured when they are needed",
        "code": "Question 335"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to define a central data protection policy that works across AWS services for compute, storage, and database resources.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Backup",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Batch",
        "AWS Elastic Disaster Recovery",
        "Amazon FSx"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 336"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to categorize and track AWS usage cost based on business categories.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Cost allocation tags",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Organizations",
        "AWS Security Hub",
        "AWS Cost and Usage Report"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 337"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service can migrate data between AWS storage services?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS DataSync",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Direct Connect",
        "AWS Lake Formation",
        "Amazon S3"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 338"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which statements represent the cost-effectiveness of the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Users can trade fixed expenses for variable expenses.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Users can deploy all over the world in minutes.",
        "AWS offers increased speed and agility.",
        "AWS is responsible for patching the infrastructure."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Users benefit from economies of scale.",
        "code": "Question 339"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to design its cloud architecture so that it can support development innovations, and continuously improve processes and procedures.\n\nThis is an example of which pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework?",
      "correct_answer": "Operational excellence",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security",
        "Performance efficiency",
        "Reliability"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 340"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to consolidate the billing for multiple AWS accounts. The company needs to use one account to pay on behalf of all the other accounts.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Organizations",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "AWS Budgets",
        "AWS Service Catalog"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 341"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is moving some of its on-premises IT services to the AWS Cloud. The finance department wants to see the entire bill so it can forecast spending limits.\n\nWhich AWS service can the company use to set spending limits and receive notifications if those limits are exceeded?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Budgets",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Cost and Usage Reports",
        "AWS Organizations consolidated billing",
        "Cost Explorer"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 342"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS Support plans provide access to an AWS technical account manager (TAM)? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Enterprise On-Ramp Support",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Basic Support",
        "AWS Developer Support",
        "AWS Business Support"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS Enterprise Support",
        "code": "Question 343"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Where can users find examples of AWS Cloud solution designs?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Architecture Center",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Marketplace",
        "AWS Service Catalog",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 344"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which task is the responsibility of a company that is using Amazon RDS?",
      "correct_answer": "Create IAM policies to control administrative access to the service.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Provision the underlying infrastructure.",
        "Install the cables to connect the hardware for compute and storage.",
        "Install and patch the RDS operating system."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 345"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which service enables customers to audit API calls in their AWS accounts?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudTrail",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "AWS X-Ray"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 346"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following is an advantage that the AWS Cloud provides to users?",
      "correct_answer": "Users eliminate the need to guess about infrastructure capacity requirements.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Users decrease their variable costs by maintaining sole ownership of IT hardware.",
        "Users maintain control of underlying IT infrastructure hardware.",
        "Users maintain control of operating systems for managed services."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 347"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which feature of Amazon RDS provides the ability to automatically create a primary database instance and to synchronously replicate data to an instance in another Availability Zone?",
      "correct_answer": "Multi-AZ deployment",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Read replicas",
        "Blue/green deployment",
        "Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 348"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to check for IAM access keys that have not been rotated recently.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Trusted Advisor",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS WAF",
        "AWS Shield",
        "Amazon Cognito"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 349"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company runs many Amazon EC2 instances in its VPC. The company wants to use a native AWS security resource to control network traffic between certain EC2 instances.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Security groups",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Network ACLs",
        "AWS WAF",
        "Amazon GuardDuty"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 350"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following can be components of a VPC in the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Internet gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon API Gateway",
        "Amazon S3 buckets and objects",
        "AWS Storage Gateway"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Subnet",
        "code": "Question 351"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building a new application on AWS. The company needs the application to remain available if an individual application component fails.\n\nWhich design principle should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Loose coupling",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Disposable resources",
        "Automation",
        "Rightsizing"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 352"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use a managed service to identify and protect sensitive data that is stored in Amazon S3.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Macie",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS IAM Access Analyzer",
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "Amazon Inspector"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 353"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature can a user configure to limit network access at the subnet level?",
      "correct_answer": "Network ACL",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Shield",
        "AWS WAF",
        "Security group"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 354"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service can a company use to manage encryption keys in the cloud?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudHSM",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS License Manager",
        "AWS Certificate Manager (ACM)",
        "AWS Directory Service"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 355"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to enhance security by launching a third-party ISP intrusion detection system from its AWS account.\n\nWhich AWS service or resource should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Marketplace",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Security Hub",
        "AWS Quick Starts",
        "AWS Security Center"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 356"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is a customer responsibility when using AWS Lambda according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Managing the code within the Lambda function",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Confirming that the hardware is working in the data center",
        "Patching the operating system",
        "Shutting down Lambda functions when they are no longer in use"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 357"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "How does the AWS Cloud help companies build agility into their processes and cloud infrastructure?",
      "correct_answer": "Companies can access a range of technologies to experiment and innovate quickly.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Companies can avoid provisioning too much capacity when they do not know how much capacity is required.",
        "Companies can expand into new geographic regions.",
        "Companies can pay for IT resources only when they use the resources."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 358"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or tool gives a company the ability to release application changes in an automated way?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CodeDeploy",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon AppFlow",
        "AWS PrivateLink",
        "Amazon EKS Distro"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 359"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) perspective focuses on managing identities and permissions at scale?",
      "correct_answer": "Security",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Operations",
        "Platform",
        "Governance"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 360"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature allows users to securely store encrypted credentials and retrieve these credentials when required?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Secrets Manager",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Encryption SDK",
        "AWS Security Hub",
        "AWS Artifact"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 361"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework aligns with the ability to make frequent, small, and reversible changes to AWS Cloud architecture?",
      "correct_answer": "Operational excellence",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security",
        "Cost optimization",
        "Performance efficiency"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 362"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or resource can a company use to deploy AWS WAF rules?",
      "correct_answer": "Application Load Balancer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon EC2",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "Network Load Balancer"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 363"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company hosts its website on Amazon EC2 instances. The company needs to ensure that the website reaches a global audience and provides minimum latency to users.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon CloudFront",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Route 53",
        "Elastic Load Balancing",
        "AWS Lambda"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 364"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS design principle emphasizes the reduction of interdependencies between components of an application?",
      "correct_answer": "Loose coupling",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Scalability",
        "Automation",
        "Caching"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 365"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to provide one of its employees with access to Amazon RDS. The company also wants to limit the interaction to only the AWS CLI and AWS software development kits (SDKs).\n\nWhich combination of actions should the company take to meet these requirements while following the principles of least privilege? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create an IAM user and provide programmatic access only.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create an IAM user and provide AWS Management Console access only.",
        "Create an IAM role and provide AWS Management Console access only.",
        "Create an IAM policy with administrator access and attach it to the IAM user."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Create an IAM policy with Amazon RDS access and attach it to the IAM user.",
        "code": "Question 366"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is running a reporting web server application on Amazon EC2 instances. The application runs once every week and once again at the end of the month. The EC2 instances can be shut down when they are not in use.\n\nWhat is the MOST cost-effective billing model for this use case?",
      "correct_answer": "On-Demand Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Standard Reserved Instances",
        "Convertible Reserved Instances",
        "On-Demand Capacity Reservations"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 367"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has 5 TB of data stored in Amazon S3. The company plans to occasionally run queries on the data for analysis.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to run these queries in the MOST cost-effective manner?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Athena",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Redshift",
        "Amazon Kinesis",
        "Amazon RDS"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 368"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to discover, prepare, move, and integrate data from multiple sources for data analytics and machine learning.\n\nWhich AWS serverless data integration service should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Glue",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Data Exchange",
        "Amazon Athena",
        "Amazon EMR"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 369"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is moving its development and test environments to AWS to increase agility and reduce cost. Because these are not production workloads and the servers are not fully utilized, occasional unavailability is acceptable.\n\nWhat is the MOST cost-effective Amazon EC2 pricing model that will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Spot Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reserved Instances",
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Dedicated Hosts"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 370"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company deploys its application on Amazon EC2 instances. The application occasionally experiences sudden increases in demand. The company wants to ensure that its application can respond to changes in demand at the lowest possible cost.\n\nWhich AWS service or concept will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Auto Scaling",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Compute Optimizer",
        "AWS Cost Explorer",
        "AWS Well-Architected Framework"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 371"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to organize its users so that the company can grant permissions to the users as a group.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool can the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security groups",
        "Resource groups",
        "AWS Security Hub"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 372"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to build an application that uses AWS Lambda to run Python code.\n\nUnder the AWS shared responsibility model, which tasks will be the company’s responsibility? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Writing the business logic code.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Management of the underlying infrastructure.",
        "Management of the operating system.",
        "Installation of the computer language runtime."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Providing AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) access to the Lambda service.",
        "code": "Question 373"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to identify who accessed an AWS service and what action was performed for a given time period.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudTrail",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "AWS Security Hub",
        "Amazon Inspector"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 374"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use a centralized AWS service to enforce compliance with the organizational business standards. The company wants to use an AWS service that can govern and control who can deploy, manage, and decommission AWS resources.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Service Catalog",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "AWS Security Hub"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 375"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What does \"security of the cloud” refer to in the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Security of the cloud infrastructure that runs all the AWS services",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Availability of AWS services such as Amazon EC2",
        "Implementation of password policies for IAM users",
        "Security of customer environments by using AWS Network Firewall partners"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 376"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an application that produces unstructured data continuously. The company needs to store the data so that the data is durable and easy to query.\n\nWhich AWS service can the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon RDS",
        "Amazon Aurora",
        "Amazon QuickSight"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 377"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which options are AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) perspectives? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Security",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cloud fluency",
        "Change acceleration",
        "Architecture"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Business",
        "code": "Question 378"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service can be used at no additional cost?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Organizations",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon SageMaker",
        "AWS Config",
        "Amazon CloudWatch"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 379"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate a company’s on-premises container infrastructure to the AWS Cloud. The company wants to prevent unplanned administration and operation cost and adapt to a serverless architecture.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Fargate",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Connect",
        "Amazon Lightsail",
        "Amazon EC2"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 380"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants its Amazon EC2 instances to be in different locations but share the same geographic area. The company also wants to use multiple power grids and independent networking connectivity for the EC2 instances.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Use EC2 instances in multiple Availability Zones in the same AWS Region.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use EC2 instances in multiple edge locations in the same AWS Region.",
        "Use EC2 instances in multiple Amazon Connect locations in the same AWS Region.",
        "Use EC2 instances in multiple AWS Artifact locations in the same AWS Region."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 381"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An ecommerce company has deployed a new web application on Amazon EC2 instances. The company wants to distribute incoming HTTP traffic evenly across all running instances.\n\nWhich AWS service or resource will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Application Load Balancer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon EC2 Auto Scaling",
        "Gateway Load Balancer",
        "Network Load Balancer"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 382"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature gives users the ability to connect VPCs and on-premises networks to a central hub?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Transit Gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Virtual private gateway",
        "Internet gateway",
        "Customer gateway"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 383"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to run CPU-intensive workload across multiple Amazon EC2 instances.\n\nWhich EC2 instance type should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Compute optimized instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "General purpose instances",
        "Memory optimized instances",
        "Storage optimized instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 384"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is connecting multiple VPCs and on-premises networks. The company needs to use an AWS service as a cloud router to simplify peering relationships.\n\nWhich AWS service can the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Transit Gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Direct Connect",
        "Amazon Connect",
        "Amazon Route 53"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 385"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company stores a large amount of data that auditors access only twice each year.\n\nWhich Amazon S3 storage class should the company use to store the data with the LOWEST cost?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon S3 Glacier Instant Retrieval",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon S3 Outposts",
        "Amazon S3 Standard",
        "Amazon S3 Intelligent-Tiering"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 386"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which action should a company take to improve security in its AWS account?",
      "correct_answer": "Require multi-factor authentication (MFA) for privileged users.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Remove the root user account.",
        "Create an access key for the AWS account root user.",
        "Create an access key for each privileged user."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 387"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following are ways to improve security on AWS? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Enabling multi-factor authentication (MFA) with Amazon Cognito",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Using AWS Artifact",
        "Granting the broadest permissions to all IAM roles",
        "Running application code with AWS Cloud"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Using AWS Trusted Advisor security checks",
        "code": "Question 388"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service can a company use to manage encryption keys in the cloud?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudHSM",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS License Manager",
        "AWS Certificate Manager (ACM)",
        "AWS Directory Service"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 389"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) capability belongs to the people perspective?",
      "correct_answer": "Cloud fluency",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Data architecture",
        "Event management",
        "Strategic partnership"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 390"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to store its files in the AWS Cloud. Users need to be able to download these files directly using a public URL.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon S3",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Redshift",
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)",
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 391"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using AWS for all its IT infrastructure. The company's developers are allowed to deploy applications on their own. The developers want to deploy their applications without having to provision the infrastructure themselves.\n\nWhich AWS service should the developers use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CloudFormation",
        "AWS CodeBuild",
        "AWS CodeDeploy"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 392"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to gain insights from its data and build interactive data visualization dashboards.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon QuickSight",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon SageMaker",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Kinesis"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 393"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A cloud engineer wants to store data in Amazon S3. The engineer will access some of the data yearly and some of the data daily.\n\nWhich S3 storage class will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "S3 Intelligent-Tiering",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "S3 Standard",
        "S3 Glacier Deep Archive",
        "S3 One Zone-Infrequent Access (S3 One Zone-IA)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 394"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following are economic benefits of using the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Consumption-based pricing",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Perpetual licenses",
        "AWS Enterprise Support at no additional cost",
        "Bring-your-own-hardware model"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Economies of scale",
        "code": "Question 395"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A user is moving a workload from a local data center to an architecture that is distributed between the local data center and the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich type of migration is this?",
      "correct_answer": "On-premises to hybrid",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "On-premises to cloud native",
        "Hybrid to cloud native",
        "Cloud native to hybrid"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 396"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to store infrequently used data for data archives and long-term backups.\n\nWhich AWS service or storage class will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon S3 Glacier Flexible Retrieval",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon FSx for Lustre",
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)",
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 397"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service provides users with AWS issued reports, certifications, accreditations, and third-party attestations?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Artifact",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "AWS Health Dashboard",
        "AWS Config"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 398"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to create and publish interactive business intelligence dashboards. The dashboards require insights that are powered by machine learning.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon QuickSight",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Glue Studio",
        "Amazon Redshift",
        "Amazon Athena"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 399"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use AWS. The company has stringent requirements about low-latency access to on-premises systems and data residency.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to design a solution that meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Outposts",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Wavelength",
        "AWS Transit Gateway",
        "AWS Ground Station"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 400"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to make an upfront commitment for continued use of its production Amazon EC2 instances in exchange for a reduced overall cost.\n\nWhich pricing options meet these requirements with the LOWEST cost? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Reserved Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Spot Instances",
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Dedicated Hosts"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Savings Plans",
        "code": "Question 401"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company runs an on-premises contact center for customers. The company needs to migrate to a cloud-based solution that can deliver artificial intelligence features to improve user experience.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Connect",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Wavelength",
        "AWS IAM Identity Center (AWS Single Sign-On)",
        "AWS Direct Connect"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 402"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs the ability to acquire resources when the resources are needed. The company also needs the ability to release the resources when the resources are no longer needed.\n\nWhich AWS concept represents the company's goals?",
      "correct_answer": "Elasticity",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Scalability",
        "Sustainability",
        "Operational excellence"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 403"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use Amazon EC2 instances for a stable production workload that will run for 1 year.\n\nWhich instance purchasing option meets these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Reserved Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Dedicated Hosts",
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Spot Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 404"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to log in securely to Linux Amazon EC2 instances.\n\nHow can the company accomplish this goal?",
      "correct_answer": "Use SSH keys.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use a VPN.",
        "Use end-to-end encryption.",
        "Use Amazon Route 53."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 405"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use a serverless compute service for an application.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Lambda",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CloudFormation",
        "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
        "Elastic Load Balancing"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 406"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants a solution that will automatically adjust the number of Amazon EC2 instances that are being used based on the current load.\n\nWhich AWS offering will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Auto Scaling groups",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Dedicated Hosts",
        "Placement groups",
        "Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 407"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building AWS architecture to deliver real-time data feeds from an on-premises data center into an application that runs on AWS. The company needs a consistent network connection with minimal latency.\n\nWhat should the company use to connect the application and the data center to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Direct Connect",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Public internet",
        "AWS VPN",
        "Amazon Connect"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 408"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company plans to migrate its custom marketing application and order-processing application to AWS. The company needs to deploy the applications on different types of instances with various configurations of CPU, memory, storage, and networking capacity.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon EC2",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Lambda",
        "Amazon Cognito",
        "Amazon Athena"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 409"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to monitor and block malicious HTTP and HTTPS requests that its Amazon CloudFront distributions receive.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS WAF",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "Amazon Detective"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 410"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS services can host PostgreSQL databases? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Aurora",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon S3",
        "Amazon OpenSearch Service",
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Amazon EC2",
        "code": "Question 411"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate its on-premises relational databases to the AWS Cloud. The company wants to use infrastructure as close to its current geographical location as possible.\n\nWhich AWS service or resource should the company use to select its Amazon RDS deployment area?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Regions",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Connect",
        "AWS Wavelength",
        "AWS Direct Connect"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 412"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service can generate information that can be used by external auditors?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Config",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Cognito",
        "Amazon FSx",
        "Amazon Inspector"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 413"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature requires an internet service provider (ISP) and a colocation facility to be implemented?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Direct Connect",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS VPN",
        "Amazon Connect",
        "Internet gateway"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 414"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants its Amazon EC2 instances to operate in a highly available environment, even if there is a natural disaster in a particular geographic area.\n\nWhich solution achieves this goal?",
      "correct_answer": "Use EC2 instances in multiple AWS Regions.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use EC2 instances in multiple edge locations.",
        "Use EC2 instances in the same Availability Zone but in different AWS Regions.",
        "Use Amazon CloudFront with the EC2 instances configured as the source."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 415"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service allows for file sharing between multiple Amazon EC2 instances?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Direct Connect",
        "AWS Snowball Edge",
        "AWS Backup"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 416"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to manage multiple logins across AWS accounts within the same organization in AWS Organizations.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS IAM Identity Center",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon VPC",
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "Amazon Cognito"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 417"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses Amazon WorkSpaces.\n\nWhich task is the responsibility of AWS, according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Ensure the environmental safety and security of the AWS infrastructure that hosts WorkSpaces.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Set up multi-factor authentication (MFA) for each WorkSpaces user account.",
        "Provide security for WorkSpaces user accounts through AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM).",
        "Configure AWS CloudTrail to log API calls and user activity."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 418"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is migrating its public website to AWS. The company wants to host the domain name for the website on AWS.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Route 53",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Lambda",
        "Amazon CloudFront",
        "AWS Direct Connect"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 419"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses a third-party identity provider (IdP). The company wants to provide its employees with access to AWS accounts and services without requiring another set of login credentials.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS IAM Identity Center",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Directory Service",
        "Amazon Cognito",
        "AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 420"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which combination of AWS services can be used to move a commercial relational database to an Amazon-managed open-source database? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS software development kits (SDKs)",
        "AWS Systems Manager",
        "Amazon EMR"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS Schema Conversion Tool",
        "code": "Question 421"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service gives users on-demand, self-service access to AWS compliance control reports?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Artifact",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Config",
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 422"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is exploring the use of the AWS Cloud, and needs to create a cost estimate for a project before the infrastructure is provisioned.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature can be used to estimate costs before deployment?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Pricing Calculator",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Free Tier",
        "AWS Billing and Cost Management",
        "AWS Cost and Usage Report"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 423"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company runs a legacy workload in an on-premises data center. The company wants to migrate the workload to AWS. The company does not want to make any changes to the workload.\n\nWhich migration strategy should the company use?",
      "correct_answer": "Rehost",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Repurchase",
        "Replatform",
        "Refactor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 424"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to migrate applications to the AWS Cloud. During a system audit, the company finds that its content management system (CMS) application is incompatible with cloud environments.\n\nWhich migration strategies will help the company to migrate the CMS application with the LEAST effort? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Rehost",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Retire",
        "Replatform",
        "Refactor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Repurchase",
        "code": "Question 425"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following are AWS best practice recommendations for the use of AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Rotate credentials on a regular basis.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use the AWS account root user for daily access.",
        "Use access keys and secret access keys on Amazon EC2.",
        "Create a shared set of access keys for system administrators."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Configure multi-factor authentication (MFA).",
        "code": "Question 426"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is AWS responsible for under the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Hardware and infrastructure",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Network and firewall configuration",
        "Client-side data encryption",
        "Management of user permissions"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 427"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to run a graph query that provides credit card users’ names, addresses, and transactions. The company wants the graph to show if the names, addresses, and transactions indicates possible fraud.\n\nWhich AWS database service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Neptune",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon DocumentDB (with MongoDB compatibility)",
        "Amazon Timestream",
        "Amazon DynamoDB"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 428"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service provides machine learning capability to detect and analyze content in images and videos?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Rekognition",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Connect",
        "Amazon Lightsail",
        "Amazon Personalize"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 429"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants its AWS usage to be more sustainable. The company wants to track, measure, review, and forecast polluting emissions that result from its AWS applications.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool can the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS customer carbon footprint tool",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Health Dashboard",
        "AWS Support Center",
        "Amazon QuickSight"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 430"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service gives users the ability to deploy highly repeatable infrastructure configurations?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudFormation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CodeDeploy",
        "AWS CodeBuild",
        "AWS Systems Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 431"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to provide customer service by using voice calls and web chat features.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Connect",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Aurora",
        "Amazon WorkSpaces",
        "AWS Organizations"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 432"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service is designed to help users handle large amounts of data in a data warehouse environment?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Redshift",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon RDS",
        "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "Amazon Aurora"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 433"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building an application that needs to deliver images and videos globally with minimal latency.\n\nWhich approach can the company use to accomplish this in a cost effective manner?",
      "correct_answer": "Deliver the content through Amazon CloudFront.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Store the content on Amazon S3 and enable S3 cross-region replication.",
        "Implement a VPN across multiple AWS Regions.",
        "Deliver the content through AWS PrivateLink."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 434"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building a web application using AWS.\n\nWhich AWS service will help prevent network layer DDoS attacks against the web application?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Shield",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS WAF",
        "AWS Firewall Manager",
        "Amazon GuardDuty"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 435"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS compute service gives users the ability to securely and reliably run containers at scale?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Aurora",
        "Amazon Athena",
        "Amazon Polly"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 436"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS tool or feature acts as a VPC firewall at the subnet level?",
      "correct_answer": "Network ACL",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security group",
        "Traffic Mirroring",
        "Internet gateway"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 437"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company runs an application on AWS that performs batch jobs. The application is fault-tolerant and can handle interruptions. The company wants to optimize the cost to run the application.\n\nWhich AWS offering will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon EC2 Spot Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Macie",
        "Amazon Neptune",
        "Amazon EC2 On-Demand Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 438"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service can be used to send alerts when a specific Amazon CloudWatch alarm is invoked?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CloudTrail",
        "Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS)",
        "Amazon EventBridge"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 439"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A cloud practitioner wants to use a highly available and scalable DNS service for its AWS workload.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Route 53",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Lightsail",
        "AWS Amplify Hosting",
        "Amazon S3"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 440"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "According to the AWS shared responsibility model, which task is the customer's responsibility?",
      "correct_answer": "Updating the guest operating system on Amazon EC2 instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Maintaining the infrastructure needed to run AWS Lambda",
        "Updating the operating system of Amazon DynamoDB instances",
        "Maintaining Amazon S3 infrastructure"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 441"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is learning about its responsibilities that are related to the management of Amazon EC2 instances.\n\nWhich tasks for EC2 instances are the company’s responsibility, according to the AWS shared responsibility model? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Patch the guest operating system.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Install and patch the machine hypervisor.",
        "Install the physical hardware and cabling.",
        "Provide physical security for the EC2 instances."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Encrypt data at rest on associated storage.",
        "code": "Question 442"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company runs MySQL database workloads on self-managed servers in an on-premises data center. The company wants to migrate the database workloads to an AWS managed service.\n\nWhich migration strategy should the company use?",
      "correct_answer": "Replatform",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Rehost",
        "Repurchase",
        "Refactor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 443"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is a customer responsibility when using Amazon DynamoDB under the AWS Shared Responsibility Model?",
      "correct_answer": "Access to DynamoDB tables",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Physical security of DynamoDB",
        "Patching of DynamoDB",
        "Encryption of data at rest in DynamoDB"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 444"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is a benefit of the economies of scale based on the advantages of cloud computing?",
      "correct_answer": "Lower variable costs over fixed costs",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The ability to trade variable expense for fixed expense",
        "Increased speed and agility",
        "Increased operational costs across data centers"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 445"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to migrate a monolithic application to AWS. The company wants to modernize the application by splitting it into microservices. The company will deploy the microservices on AWS.\n\nWhich migration strategy should the company use?",
      "correct_answer": "Refactor",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Rehost",
        "Repurchase",
        "Replatform"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 446"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to implement detailed tracking of its cloud costs by department and project.\n\nWhich AWS feature or service should the company use?",
      "correct_answer": "Cost allocation tags",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Consolidated billing",
        "AWS Marketplace",
        "AWS Budgets"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 447"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A user wants to invoke an AWS Lambda function when an Amazon EC2 instance enters the “stopping” state.\n\nWhich AWS service is appropriate for this use case?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon EventBridge",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Config",
        "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)",
        "AWS CloudFormation"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 448"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a MariaDB database on premises. The company wants to move the data to the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich AWS service will host this database with the LEAST amount of operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon RDS",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Neptune",
        "Amazon S3",
        "Amazon DynamoDB"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 449"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature supports governance, compliance, and risk auditing of AWS accounts?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudTrail",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Multi-factor authentication (MFA)",
        "AWS Lambda",
        "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 450"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS Cloud design principle is a company using when the company implements AWS CloudTrail?",
      "correct_answer": "Activate traceability.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use serverless compute architectures.",
        "Perform operations as code.",
        "Go global in minutes."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 451"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs a threat detection service that will continuously monitor its AWS accounts, workloads, and Amazon S3 buckets for malicious activity and unauthorized behavior.\n\nWhich AWS service meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon GuardDuty",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Shield",
        "AWS Firewall Manager",
        "Amazon Inspector"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 452"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to migrate to the AWS Cloud. The company is conducting organizational transformation and wants to become more responsive to customer inquiries and feedback.\n\nWhich task should the company perform to meet these requirements, according to the AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF)?",
      "correct_answer": "Realign teams to focus on products and value streams.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create new value propositions with new products and services.",
        "Use a new data and analytics platform to create actionable insights.",
        "Migrate and modernize legacy infrastructure."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 453"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to rightsize its Amazon EC2 instances.\n\nWhich configuration change will meet this requirement with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Change the size and type of the EC2 instances based on utilization.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Add EC2 instances in another Availability Zone.",
        "Convert the payment method from On-Demand to Savings Plans.",
        "Reprovision the EC2 instances with a larger instance type."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 454"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service supports user sign-up functionality and authentication to mobile and web applications?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Cognito",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Config",
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "AWS Systems Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 455"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following is a software development framework that a company can use to define cloud resources as code and provision the resources through AWS CloudFormation?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CLI",
        "AWS Developer Center",
        "AWS CodeStar"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 456"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which benefit of the AWS Cloud helps companies achieve lower usage costs because of the aggregate usage of all AWS users?",
      "correct_answer": "Economies of scale",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "No need to guess capacity",
        "Ability to go global in minutes",
        "Increased speed and agility"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 457"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which task is the responsibility of the customer, according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Use AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) according to the principle of least privilege.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Patch the Amazon DynamoDB operating system.",
        "Secure Amazon CloudFront edge locations by allowing physical access according to the principle of least privilege.",
        "Protect the hardware that runs AWS services."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 458"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to manage its cloud resources by using infrastructure as code (IaC) templates. The company needs to meet compliance requirements.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Service Catalog",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Artifact",
        "AWS Resource Explorer",
        "AWS License Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 459"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A systems administrator wants to monitor the CPU utilization of a company's Amazon EC2 instances.\n\nWhich AWS service can provide this information?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon CloudWatch",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Config",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "AWS CloudTrail"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 460"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate all of its on-premises infrastructure to the AWS Cloud. Before migration, the company wants estimate of costs for running its as-is infrastructure.\n\nWhich AWS service or principle should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Pricing Calculator",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Well-Architected Framework",
        "AWS shared responsibility model",
        "AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 461"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An independent software vendor wants to deliver and share its custom Amazon Machine Images (AMIs) to prospective customers.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Marketplace",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Data Exchange",
        "Amazon EC2",
        "AWS Organizations"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 462"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which component must be attached to a VPC to enable inbound internet access?",
      "correct_answer": "Internet gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "NAT gateway",
        "VPC endpoint",
        "VPN connection"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 463"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service supports a company's ability to treat infrastructure as code?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudFormation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CodeDeploy",
        "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
        "Amazon API Gateway"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 464"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is building an application that will receive millions of database queries each second. The company needs the data store for the application to scale to meet these needs.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Cloud9",
        "Amazon ElastiCache for Memcached",
        "Amazon Neptune"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 465"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An AWS user wants to proactively detect when an instance or account might be compromised or if there are threats from attacks.\n\nWhich AWS service should the user choose?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon GuardDuty",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS WAF",
        "AWS Shield",
        "Amazon Inspector"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 466"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is developing an application that uses multiple AWS services. The application needs to use temporary, limited-privilege credentials for authentication with other AWS APIs.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature should the company use to meet these authentication requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Security Token Service (AWS STS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon API Gateway",
        "IAM users",
        "IAM instance profiles"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 467"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS Support plan provides the full set of AWS Trusted Advisor checks at the LOWEST cost?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Business Support",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Developer Support",
        "AWS Enterprise On-Ramp Support",
        "AWS Enterprise Support"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 468"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company's application is running on Amazon EC2 instances. The company is planning a partial migration to a serverless architecture in the next year and wants to pay for resources up front.\n\nWhich AWS purchasing option will optimize the company's costs?",
      "correct_answer": "Compute Savings Plan",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Convertible Reserved Instances",
        "Spot Instances",
        "EC2 Instance Savings Plans"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 469"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A retail company is building a new mobile app. The company is evaluating whether to build the app at an on-premises data center or in the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich of the following are benefits of building this app in the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Increased speed for trying out new projects",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A large, upfront capital expense and low variable expenses",
        "Complete control over the physical security of the infrastructure",
        "Ability to pick the specific data centers that will host the application servers"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Flexibility to scale up in minutes as the application becomes popular",
        "code": "Question 470"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company must archive its documents by using a write-once, read-many (WORM) model to meet legal and compliance obligations.\n\nWhich feature of Amazon S3 can the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "S3 Glacier Vault Lock",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "S3 Versioning",
        "S3 bucket policy",
        "S3 multi-factor authentication (MFA) delete"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 471"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has batch workloads that need to run for short periods of time on Amazon EC2. The workloads can handle interruptions and can start again from where they ended.\n\nWhat is the MOST cost-effective EC2 instance purchasing option to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Spot Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reserved Instances",
        "Dedicated Instances",
        "On-Demand Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 472"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to deploy a PostgreSQL database into Amazon RDS. The database must be highly available and fault tolerant.\n\nWhich AWS solution should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon RDS with multiple Availability Zones",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon RDS with a single Availability Zone",
        "Amazon RDS snapshots",
        "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 473"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is the MOST secure way to store passwords on AWS?",
      "correct_answer": "Store passwords in AWS Secrets Manager.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Store passwords in an Amazon S3 bucket.",
        "Store passwords as AWS CloudFormation parameters.",
        "Store passwords in AWS Storage Gateway."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 474"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which statements accurately describe the relationships among components of AWS global infrastructure? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "There are more edge locations than AWS Regions.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "There are more AWS Regions than Availability Zones.",
        "An edge location is an Availability Zone.",
        "There are more AWS Regions than edge locations."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "There are more Availability Zones than AWS Regions.",
        "code": "Question 475"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service provides DNS resolution?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Route 53",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CloudFront",
        "Amazon VPC",
        "AWS Direct Connect"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 476"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to host an application in a specific geographic area to comply with regulations.\n\nWhich feature of the AWS global infrastructure will help the company meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Global footprint",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Scalability",
        "Availability",
        "Performance"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 477"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service is a cloud security posture management (CSPM) service that aggregates alerts from various AWS services and partner products in a standardized format?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Security Hub",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "Amazon EventBridge",
        "Amazon GuardDuty"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 478"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An ecommerce company plans to move its data center workload to the AWS Cloud to support highly dynamic usage patterns.\n\nWhich benefits make the AWS Cloud cost-effective for the migration of this type of workload? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Elasticity",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reliability",
        "Security",
        "High availability"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Pay-as-you-go resource",
        "code": "Question 479"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "When designing AWS workloads to be operational even when there are component failures, what is an AWS best practice?",
      "correct_answer": "Design for automatic failover to healthy resources.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Perform quarterly disaster recovery tests.",
        "Place the main component on the us-east-1 Region.",
        "Design workloads to fit on a single Amazon EC2 instance."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 480"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following can the AWS Pricing Calculator do?",
      "correct_answer": "Project monthly AWS costs.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Calculate historical AWS costs.",
        "Provide in-depth information about AWS pricing strategies.",
        "Provide users with access to their monthly bills."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 481"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS solution gives companies the ability to use protocols such as NFS to store and retrieve objects in Amazon S3?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Storage Gateway file gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon FSx for Lustre",
        "AWS Storage Gateway volume gateway",
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 482"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A user has been granted permission to change their own IAM user password.\n\nWhich AWS services can the user use to change the password? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Command Line Interface (AWS CLI)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Key Management Sen/ice (AWS KMS)",
        "AWS Resource Access Manager (AWS RAM)",
        "AWS Secrets Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS Management Console",
        "code": "Question 483"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which task is the customer's responsibility, according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Patch a guest operating system that is deployed on an Amazon EC2 instance.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Control physical access to an AWS data center.",
        "Control access to AWS underlying hardware.",
        "Patch a host operating system that is deployed on Amazon S3."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 484"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature provides a firewall at the subnet level within a VPC?",
      "correct_answer": "Network ACL",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security group",
        "Elastic network interface",
        "AWS WAF"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 485"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use automated video analysis to identify employees that are accessing its offices.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Rekognition",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Cognito",
        "AWS Lambda"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 486"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to host a web server on Amazon EC2 instances for at least 1 year. The web server cannot tolerate interruption.\n\nWhich EC2 instance purchasing option will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Partial Upfront Reserved Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Spot Instances",
        "No Upfront Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 487"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which guidelines are best practices for using AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Create individual IAM users.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Share access keys.",
        "Use inline policies instead of customer managed policies.",
        "Grant maximum privileges to IAM users."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Use groups to assign permissions to IAM users.",
        "code": "Question 488"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service is always provided at no charge?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon S3",
        "Elastic Load Balancers",
        "AWS WAF"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 489"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which advantage of cloud computing allows users to scale resources up and down based on the amount of load that an application supports?",
      "correct_answer": "Stop guessing capacity",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Go global in minutes",
        "Benefit from massive economies of scale",
        "Trade fixed expense for variable expense"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 490"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is requesting Payment Card Industry (PCI) reports that validate the operating effectiveness of AWS security controls.\n\nHow should the company obtain these reports?",
      "correct_answer": "Download reports from AWS Artifact.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Contact AWS Support.",
        "Download reports from AWS Security Hub.",
        "Contact an AWS technical account manager (TAM)."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 491"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An ecommerce company wants to distribute traffic between the Amazon EC2 instances that host its website.\n\nWhich AWS service or resource will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Application Load Balancer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS WAF",
        "AWS CloudHSM",
        "AWS Direct Connect"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 492"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS services or features form the AWS Cloud global infrastructure? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Availability Zones",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon ElastiCache",
        "Amazon S3",
        "Amazon VPC"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS Regions",
        "code": "Question 493"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "According to the AWS shared responsibility model, which of the following are AWS responsibilities? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Network infrastructure and virtualization of infrastructure",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security of application data",
        "Guest operating systems",
        "Credentials and policies"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Physical security of hardware",
        "code": "Question 494"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses Amazon Aurora as its database service. The company wants to encrypt its databases and database backups.\n\nWhich party manages the encryption of the database clusters and database snapshots, according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "The company",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS",
        "AWS Marketplace partners",
        "Third-party partners"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 495"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is hosting a web application on Amazon EC2 instances. The company wants to implement custom conditions to filter and control inbound web traffic.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS WAF",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "Amazon Macie",
        "AWS Shield"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 496"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to maintain bandwidth throughput and provide a more consistent network experience than public internet-based connections.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company choose?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Direct Connect",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS VPN",
        "Amazon Connect",
        "Amazon CloudFront"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 497"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has temporary workload that is also variable. The company needs to use Amazon EC2 instances for the workload. The EC2 instances need to handle short bursts of work that cannot stop before finishing.\n\nWhich purchase option will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "On-Demand Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Spot Instances",
        "Savings Plan",
        "Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 498"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company's employees are working from home. The company wants its employees to use their personal devices to connect to a managed workstation in the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to provide the remote environment?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Workspaces",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Cloud9",
        "AWS Outposts",
        "Amazon Lightsail"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 499"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "To reduce costs, a company is planning to migrate a NoSQL database to AWS.\n\nWhich AWS service is fully managed and can automatically scale throughput capacity to meet database workload demands?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Redshift",
        "Amazon Aurora",
        "Amazon RDS"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 500"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to use SQL syntax to perform a direct query of objects in an Amazon S3 bucket.\n\nWhich AWS service can the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Athena",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Glue",
        "AWS Lambda",
        "Amazon Kinesis"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 501"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses Amazon RDS for a product database. The company wants to ensure the database is highly available.\n\nWhich feature of Amazon RDS will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Multi-AZ deployment",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Read replicas",
        "Blue/green deployment",
        "Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 502"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service provides serverless compute for use with containers?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Fargate",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS)",
        "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
        "Amazon SageMaker"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 503"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using multiple AWS accounts for different business teams. The finance team wants to receive one bill for all of the company's accounts.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool should the finance team use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Organizations",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "Cost Explorer",
        "AWS Budgets"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 504"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs a firewall that will control network connections to and from a single Amazon EC2 instance. This firewall will not control network connections to and from other instances that are in the same subnet.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature can the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Security group",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Network ACL",
        "AWS WAF",
        "Route table"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 505"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to use the Amazon EC2 instances as web servers. Customers from around the world will use the web servers. Most customers will use the web servers only during certain hours of the day.\n\nHow should the company deploy the EC2 instances to achieve the LOWEST operational cost?",
      "correct_answer": "In an Auto Scaling group",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "In multiple Availability Zones",
        "In a placement group",
        "In private subnets"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 506"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which benefit is always free of charge with AWS, regardless of a user’s AWS Support plan?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Developer Forums",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Developer Support",
        "Programmatic case management",
        "AWS technical account manager (TAM)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 507"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company uses Amazon EC2 instances to run its application. The application needs to be available and running continuously for three or more years.\n\nWhat type of EC2 instance should the company purchase for a discount on the EC2 pricing?",
      "correct_answer": "Reserved Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Spot Instances",
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "EC2 Fleet"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 508"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to perform an audit of recent AWS account activity. The audit will investigate who initiated an event and what actions were performed.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudTrail",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Config",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 509"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which design principles are included in the reliability pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Automatically recover from failure.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Grant everyone access to increase AWS service quotas.",
        "Design applications to run in a single Availability Zone.",
        "Plan to increase AWS service quotas first in a secondary AWS Region."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Stop guessing capacity.",
        "code": "Question 510"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using Amazon DynamoDB.\n\nWhich task is the company’s responsibility, according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Manage database access permissions.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Patch the operating system.",
        "Provision hosts.",
        "Secure the operating system."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 511"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to use AWS technology to deploy a static website.\n\nWhich solution meets this requirement with the LEAST amount of operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Host the website on Amazon S3.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Deploy the website on Amazon EC2.",
        "Host the website on AWS Elastic Beanstalk.",
        "Deploy the website with Amazon Lightsail."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 512"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which recommendation can AWS Cost Explorer provide to help reduce cost?",
      "correct_answer": "Terminate an idle instance.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Use a specific database engine.",
        "Change the programming language for an application.",
        "Deploy a specific operating system."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 513"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to deploy an application in multiple Availability Zones in a single AWS Region.\n\nWhich benefit will this deployment provide to the company?",
      "correct_answer": "Resilient architecture and a highly available solution",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Improved connection performance for global customers",
        "Reduced overall data storage costs",
        "Ability to shut down an Availability Zone during periods of low demand"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 514"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service can companies use to subscribe to RSS feeds for updates about all AWS service issues?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Health Dashboard",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)",
        "AWS Config",
        "AWS CodeCommit"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 515"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which Amazon EC2 Reserved Instances term commitment will give users the MOST cost savings?",
      "correct_answer": "3 years",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "1 year",
        "2 years",
        "5 years"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 516"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is running big data analytics and massive parallel computations on its AWS test and development servers. The company can tolerate occasional downtime.\n\nWhat is the MOST cost-effective Amazon EC2 purchasing option for the company to use?",
      "correct_answer": "Spot Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Reserved Instances",
        "Savings Plans"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 517"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company runs Amazon EC2 instances in a research lab. The instances run for 3 hours each week and cannot be interrupted.\n\nWhat is the MOST cost-effective instance purchasing option to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "On-Demand Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Compute Savings Plan",
        "Convertible Reserved Instances",
        "Spot Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 518"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A new AWS user needs to interact with AWS Support by using API calls.\n\nWhich AWS Support plan will meet this requirement MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Business Support",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Basic Support",
        "AWS Developer Support",
        "AWS Enterprise Support"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 519"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company migrated to the AWS Cloud. Now the company pays for services on an as-needed basis.\n\nWhich advantage of cloud computing is the company benefiting from?",
      "correct_answer": "Trade fixed expense for variable expense",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Stop spending money running and maintaining data centers",
        "Increase speed and agility",
        "Go global in minutes"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 520"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company will run a predictable compute workload on Amazon EC2 instances for the next 3 years. The workload is critical for the company. The company wants to optimize costs to run the workload.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Savings Plans",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Spot Instances",
        "Dedicated Hosts",
        "On-Demand Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 521"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a test AWS environment. A company is planning on testing an application within AWS. The application testing can be interrupted and does not need to run continuously.\n\nWhich Amazon EC2 purchasing option will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Spot Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Dedicated Instances",
        "Reserved Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 522"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to estimate the cost for its AWS architecture solution before migration.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Pricing Calculator",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Detective",
        "AWS Budgets",
        "AWS Resource Explorer"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 523"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to centrally manage its employee's access to multiple AWS accounts.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS IAM Identity Center",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Identity and Access Management Access Analyzer",
        "AWS Secrets Manager",
        "AWS Security Token Service (AWS STS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 524"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A university receives a grant to conduct research by using AWS services. The research team needs to make sure the grant money lasts for the entire school year. The team has decided on a monthly allocation that adds up to the total grant amount.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature will notify the team if spending exceeds the planned amount?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Budgets",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cost Explorer",
        "Cost allocation tags",
        "Cost categories"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 525"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has migrated its workload to the AWS Cloud. The company wants to optimize existing Amazon EC2 resources.\n\nWhich AWS services or tools provide this functionality? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Cost Explorer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
        "Amazon Detective",
        "AWS Billing Conductor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS Compute Optimizer",
        "code": "Question 526"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company with multiple accounts and teams wants to set up a new multi-account AWS environment.\n\nWhich AWS service supports this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Control Tower",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CloudFormation",
        "AWS Config",
        "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 527"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs access to checks and recommendations that help the company follow AWS best practices for cost optimization, security, fault tolerance, performance, and service quotas.\n\nWhich combination of an AWS service and AWS Support plan on the AWS account will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Trusted Advisor with AWS Business Support",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Trusted Advisor with AWS Developer Support",
        "AWS Health Dashboard with AWS Enterprise Support",
        "AWS Health Dashboard with AWS Enterprise On-Ramp Support"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 528"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service helps users plan and track their server and application inventory migration data to AWS?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Migration Hub",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "AWS DataSync",
        "AWS Application Migration Service"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 529"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS team or offering helps users accelerate cloud adoption through paid engagements in any of several specialty practice areas?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Professional Services",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Enterprise Support",
        "AWS solutions architects",
        "AWS account managers"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 530"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to purchase Amazon EC2 instances to support an application that will run continuously for more than 1 year.\n\nWhich EC2 instance purchasing option meets these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Reserved Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Dedicated Instances",
        "Spot Instances",
        "On-Demand Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 531"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which programming languages does AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK) currently support? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Python",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Swift",
        "Ruby",
        "PHP"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "TypeScript",
        "code": "Question 532"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service gives users the ability to discover and protect sensitive data that is stored in Amazon S3 buckets?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Macie",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Detective",
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "AWS IAM Access Analyzer"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 533"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature gives users the ability to provision AWS infrastructure programmatically?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Cloud Development Kit (AWS CDK)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CodeGuru",
        "AWS Config",
        "AWS CodeCommit"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 534"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature allows a company to have its own logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS VPN",
        "Availability Zones",
        "AWS Regions"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 535"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following actions are controlled with AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Control access to AWS service APIs and to other specific resources.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Provide intelligent threat detection and continuous monitoring.",
        "Grant users access to AWS data centers.",
        "Provide firewall protection for applications from common web attacks."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Protect the AWS environment using multi-factor authentication (MFA).",
        "code": "Question 536"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Why are AWS CloudFormation templates used?",
      "correct_answer": "To reduce provisioning time by using automation.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "To transfer existing infrastructure to another company.",
        "To reuse on-premises infrastructure in the AWS Cloud.",
        "To deploy large infrastructure with no cost implications."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 537"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is using AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM).\n\nWho can manage the access keys of the AWS account root user?",
      "correct_answer": "The AWS account owner",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "IAM users in the same account that have been granted permission",
        "IAM roles in any account that have been granted permission",
        "IAM users and roles that have been granted permission"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 538"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which group shares responsibility with AWS for security and compliance of AWS accounts and resources?",
      "correct_answer": "Customers",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Third-party vendors",
        "Reseller partners",
        "Internet providers"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 539"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs an event history of which AWS resources the company has created.\n\nWhich AWS service will provide this information?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudTrail",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "Amazon Aurora",
        "Amazon EventBridge"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 540"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to run relationship databases in the AWS Cloud. The company wants to use a managed service that will install the database and run regular software updates.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon RDS",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon S3",
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)",
        "Amazon DynamoDB"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 541"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service provides a fully managed graph database for highly connected datasets?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Neptune",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "Amazon RDS",
        "Amazon Aurora"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 542"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company's cloud environment includes Amazon EC2 instances and Application Load Balancers. The company wants to improve protections for its cloud resources against DDoS attacks. The company also wants to have real-time visibility into any DDoS attacks.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Shield Advanced",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Shield Standard",
        "AWS Firewall Manager",
        "Amazon GuardDuty"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 543"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following services can be used to block network traffic to an instance? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Security groups",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC) flow logs",
        "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "AWS CloudTrail"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Network ACLs",
        "code": "Question 544"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to update its online data processing application by implementing container-based services that run for 4 hours at a time. The company does not want to provision or manage server instances.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Fargate",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Lambda",
        "Amazon EC2",
        "AWS Elastic Beanstalk"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 545"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service enables users to create copies of resources across AWS Regions?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudFormation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon ElastiCache",
        "AWS CloudTrail",
        "AWS Systems Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 546"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which task is the responsibility of AWS, according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Perform automated backups of Amazon RDS instances.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Apply guest operating system patches to Amazon EC2 instances.",
        "Provide monitoring of human resources information management (HRIM) systems.",
        "Optimize the costs of running AWS services."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 547"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A user needs to perform a one-time backup of an Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) volume that is attached to an Amazon EC2 instance.\n\nWhat is the MOST operationally efficient way to perform this backup?",
      "correct_answer": "Create an EBS snapshot of the volume.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Attach another EBS volume to the EC2 instance, and copy the contents.",
        "Copy the EBS volume to a server that is running outside AWS and is connected with AWS Direct Connect.",
        "Create a custom script to copy the EBS file contents to Amazon S3."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 548"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A developer who has no AWS Cloud experience wants to use AWS technology to build a web application.\n\nWhich AWS service should the developer use to start building the application?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Lightsail",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon SageMaker",
        "AWS Lambda",
        "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 549"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to manage access and permissions for its third-party software as a service (SaaS) applications. The company wants to use a portal where end users can access assigned AWS accounts and AWS Cloud applications.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS IAM Identity Center (AWS Single Sign-On)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Cognito",
        "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)",
        "AWS Directory Service for Microsoft Active Directory"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 550"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service is designed for users running workloads that include a NoSQL database?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon RDS",
        "Amazon S3",
        "Amazon Redshift"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 551"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a website on AWS. The company wants to deliver the website to a worldwide audience and provide low-latency response times for global users.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon CloudFront",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CloudFormation",
        "Amazon ElastiCache",
        "Amazon DynamoDB"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 552"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to add a conversational chatbot to its website.\n\nWhich AWS service can the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Lex",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Textract",
        "AWS Glue",
        "Amazon Rekognition"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 553"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature can be used to monitor for potential disk write spikes on a system that is running on Amazon EC2?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon CloudWatch",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CloudTrail",
        "AWS Health Dashboard",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 554"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is a perspective that includes foundational capabilities of the AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF)?",
      "correct_answer": "Governance",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Sustainability",
        "Performance efficiency",
        "Reliability"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 555"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service can identify when an Amazon EC2 instance was terminated?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudTrail",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)",
        "AWS Compute Optimizer",
        "Amazon EventBridge"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 556"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has applications that control on-premises factory equipment.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to run these applications with the LEAST latency?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Outposts",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon EC2",
        "AWS Lambda",
        "AWS Fargate"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 557"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) perspective focuses on organizing an inventory of data products in a data catalog?",
      "correct_answer": "Governance",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Operations",
        "Business",
        "Platform"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 558"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company runs its production workload in the AWS Cloud. The company needs to choose one of the AWS Support Plans.\n\nWhich of the AWS Support Plans will meet these requirements at the LOWEST cost?",
      "correct_answer": "Business",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Developer",
        "Enterprise On-Ramp",
        "Enterprise"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 559"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is the primary use case for Amazon GuardDuty?",
      "correct_answer": "Automatic monitoring for threats to AWS workloads",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Prevention of DDoS attacks",
        "Protection against SQL injection attacks",
        "Automatic provisioning of AWS resources"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 560"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which VPC component can a company use to set up a virtual firewall at the Amazon EC2 instance level?",
      "correct_answer": "Security group",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Network ACL",
        "Route table",
        "NAT gateway"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 561"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A developer needs to interact with AWS by using the AWS CLI.\n\nWhich security feature or AWS service must be provisioned in the developer's account to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS access key",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "User name and password",
        "AWS Systems Manager",
        "Root password access"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 562"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A food delivery company needs to block users in certain countries from accessing its website.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS WAF",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Control Tower",
        "Amazon Fraud Detector",
        "Amazon Pinpoint"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 563"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to use Amazon S3 to store audio files that are each 5 megabytes in size. The company will rarely access the files, but the company must be able to retrieve the files immediately.\n\nWhich S3 storage class will meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "S3 Standard-Infrequent Access (S3 Standard-IA)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "S3 Standard",
        "S3 Glacier Flexible Retrieval",
        "S3 Glacier Deep Archive"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 564"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to set up a secure network connection from on premises to the AWS Cloud within 1 week.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Site-to-Site VPN",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Direct Connect",
        "Amazon VPC",
        "Edge location"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 565"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is a customer responsibility under the AWS shared responsibility model when using AWS Lambda?",
      "correct_answer": "The code and libraries that run in the Lambda functions.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Maintenance of the underlying Lambda hardware.",
        "Maintenance of the Lambda networking infrastructure.",
        "The Lambda server software."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 566"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following is a fully managed MySQL-compatible database?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Aurora",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon S3",
        "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "Amazon Redshift"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 567"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which tasks are the responsibility of AWS according to the AWS shared responsibility model? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Secure the access of physical AWS facilities.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM).",
        "Configure security groups on Amazon EC2 instances.",
        "Patch applications that run on Amazon EC2 instances."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Perform infrastructure patching and maintenance.",
        "code": "Question 568"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company's compliance officer wants to review the AWS Service Organization Control (SOC) reports.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature should the compliance officer use to complete this task?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Artifact",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Concierge Support",
        "AWS Support",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 569"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a compliance requirement to record and evaluate configuration changes, as well as perform remediation actions on AWS resources.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Config",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Secrets Manager",
        "AWS CloudTrail",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 570"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company plans to perform a one-time migration of a large dataset with millions of files from its on-premises data center to the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use for the migration?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS DataSync",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)",
        "AWS Migration Hub",
        "AWS Application Migration Service"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 571"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS network services or features allow CIDR block notation when providing an IP address range? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Security groups",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Machine Image (AMI)",
        "AWS Budgets",
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Network access control list (network ACL)",
        "code": "Question 572"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to develop an accessibility application that will convert text into audible speech.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Polly",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon MQ",
        "Amazon Neptune",
        "Amazon Timestream"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 573"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to set up dedicated network connectivity between its on-premises data center and the AWS Cloud. The network cannot use the public internet.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Direct Connect",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Transit Gateway",
        "AWS VPN",
        "Amazon CloudFront"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 574"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to use dashboards and charts to analyze insights from business data.\n\nWhich AWS service will provide the dashboards and charts for these insights?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon QuickSight",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Macie",
        "Amazon Aurora",
        "AWS CloudTrail"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 575"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate its on-premises infrastructure to the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich advantage of cloud computing will help the company reduce upfront costs?",
      "correct_answer": "Trade fixed expense for variable expense",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Go global in minutes",
        "Increase speed and agility",
        "Benefit from massive economies of scale"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 576"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is designing workloads in the AWS Cloud. The company wants the workloads to perform their intended function correctly and consistently throughout their lifecycle.\n\nWhich pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework does this goal represent?",
      "correct_answer": "Reliability",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Operational excellence",
        "Security",
        "Performance efficiency"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 577"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service supports a hybrid architecture that gives users the ability to extend AWS infrastructure, AWS services, APIs, and tools to data centers, co-location environments, or on-premises facilities?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Outposts",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Snowmobile",
        "AWS Local Zones",
        "AWS Fargate"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 578"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service is used to temporarily provide federated security credentials to access AWS resources?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Simple Token Service (AWS STS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "AWS Secrets Manager",
        "AWS Certificate Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 579"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is a benefit of using an Elastic Load Balancing (ELB) load balancer with applications running in the AWS Cloud?",
      "correct_answer": "An ELB can balance traffic across multiple compute resources.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "An ELB will automatically scale resources to meet capacity needs.",
        "An ELB can span multiple AWS Regions.",
        "An ELB can balance traffic between multiple internet gateways."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 580"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to convert video files and audio files to a format that will play on smartphones.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Elastic Transcoder",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Rekognition",
        "Amazon Polly"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 581"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to securely store Amazon RDS database credentials and automatically rotate user passwords periodically.\n\nWhich AWS service or capability will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Secrets Manager",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon S3",
        "AWS Systems Manager Parameter Store",
        "AWS CloudTrail"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 582"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to have the ability to set up infrastructure for new applications in minutes.\n\nWhich advantage of cloud computing will help the company meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Increase speed and agility",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Trade fixed expense for variable expense",
        "Go global in minutes",
        "Stop guessing capacity"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 583"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs a managed NFS file system that the company can use with its AWS compute resources.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)",
        "AWS Storage Gateway Tape Gateway",
        "Amazon S3 Glacier Flexible Retrieval"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 584"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company plans to migrate to the AWS Cloud. The company wants to gather information about its on-premises data center.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Application Discovery Service",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS DataSync",
        "AWS Storage Gateway",
        "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 585"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which tasks are responsibilities of the customer, according to the AWS shared responsibility model? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Encrypt data and maintain data integrity.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Secure the virtualization layer.",
        "Patch the Amazon RDS operating system.",
        "Secure Availability Zones."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Maintain identity and access management controls.",
        "code": "Question 586"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An online retail company wants to migrate its on-premises workload to AWS. The company needs to automatically handle a seasonal workload increase in a cost-effective manner.\n\nWhich AWS Cloud features will help the company meet this requirement? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Pay-as-you-go pricing",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cross-Region workload deployment",
        "Built-in AWS CloudTrail audit capabilities",
        "Centralized logging"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Auto Scaling policies",
        "code": "Question 587"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A developer needs to use a standardized template to create copies of a company's AWS architecture for development, test, and production environments.\n\nWhich AWS service should the developer use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudFormation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Cloud Map",
        "Amazon Cloud Front",
        "AWS CloudTrail"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 588"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service can run a managed PostgreSQL database that provides online transaction processing (OLTP)?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon RDS",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "Amazon Athena",
        "Amazon EMR"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 589"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service can create a private network connection from on premises to the AWS Cloud?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Direct Connect",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Config",
        "Virtual Private Cloud (Amazon VPC)",
        "Amazon Route 53"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 590"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Under the AWS shared responsibility model, which of the following is a responsibility of the customer?",
      "correct_answer": "Patch the guest operating system with the latest security patches.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Shred disk drives before they leave a data center.",
        "Prevent customers from gathering packets or collecting traffic at the hypervisor level.",
        "Maintain security systems that provide physical monitoring of data centers."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 591"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service uses speech-to-text conversion to help users create meeting notes?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Transcribe",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Polly",
        "Amazon Textract",
        "Amazon Rekognition"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 592"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or tool provides users with a graphical interface that they can use to manage AWS services?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Management Console",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Copilot",
        "AWS CLI",
        "AWS software development kits (SDKs)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 593"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a workload that will run continuously for 1 year. The workload cannot tolerate service interruptions.\n\nWhich Amazon EC2 purchasing option will be MOST cost-effective?",
      "correct_answer": "All Upfront Reserved Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Partial Upfront Reserved Instances",
        "Dedicated Instances",
        "On-Demand Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 594"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company migrated its systems to the AWS Cloud. The systems are rightsized, and a security review did not reveal any issues. The company must ensure that additional developments, integrations, changes, and system usage growth do not jeopardize this optimized AWS infrastructure.\n\nWhich AWS service should the company use to report ongoing optimization and security?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Trusted Advisor",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Health Dashboard",
        "Amazon Connect",
        "AWS Systems Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 595"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service integrates with other AWS services to provide the ability to encrypt data at rest?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Key Management Service (AWS KMS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Certificate Manager (ACM)",
        "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)",
        "AWS Security Hub"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 596"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to track the monthly cost and usage of all Amazon EC2 instances in a specific AWS environment.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Budgets",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Cost Anomaly Detection",
        "AWS Compute Optimizer",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 597"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants the ability to automatically acquire resources as needed and release the resources when they are no longer needed.\n\nWhich cloud concept describes this functionality?",
      "correct_answer": "Elasticity",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Availability",
        "Durability",
        "Reliability"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 598"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants a cost-effective option when running its applications in an Amazon EC2 instance for short time periods. The applications can be interrupted.\n\nWhich EC2 instance type will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Spot Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Reserved Instances",
        "Dedicated Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 599"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to provide managed Windows virtual desktops and applications to its remote employees over secure network connections.\n\nWhich AWS services can the company use to meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon AppStream 2.0",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Connect",
        "AWS Site-to-Site VPN",
        "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Amazon WorkSpaces",
        "code": "Question 600"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an AWS Business Support plan. The company needs to gain access to the AWS DDoS Response Team (DRT) to help mitigate DDoS events.\n\nWhich AWS service or resource must the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Shield Advanced",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Shield Standard",
        "AWS Enterprise Support",
        "AWS WAF"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 601"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or tool provides a visualization of historical AWS spending patterns and projections of future AWS costs?",
      "correct_answer": "Cost Explorer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Cost and Usage Report",
        "AWS Budgets",
        "Amazon Cloud Watch"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 602"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is migrating to the AWS Cloud instead of running its infrastructure on premises.\n\nWhich of the following are advantages of this migration? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Increased global reach and agility",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Elimination of the need to perform security auditing",
        "Elimination of the cost of IT staff members",
        "Redundancy by default for all compute services"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Ability to deploy globally in minutes",
        "code": "Question 603"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service uses edge locations to cache content?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon CloudFront",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Kinesis",
        "Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS)",
        "Amazon Route 53"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 604"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to securely access an Amazon S3 bucket from an Amazon EC2 instance without accessing the internet.\n\nWhat should the company use to accomplish this goal?",
      "correct_answer": "VPC endpoint",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "VPN connection",
        "Internet gateway",
        "NAT gateway"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 605"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants an AWS service that can automate software deployment in Amazon EC2 instances and on-premises instances.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CodeDeploy",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CodeCommit",
        "AWS CodeBuild",
        "AWS CodePipeline"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 606"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS services are serverless? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Fargate",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Managed Streaming for Apache Kafka",
        "Amazon EMR",
        "Amazon EC2"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Amazon S3",
        "code": "Question 607"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to continuously improve processes and procedures to deliver business value.\n\nWhich pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework does this goal represent?",
      "correct_answer": "Operational excellence",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Performance efficiency",
        "Reliability",
        "Sustainability"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 608"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following is a customer responsibility according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Implement multi-factor authentication (MFA) for IAM user accounts.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Apply security patches for Amazon S3 infrastructure devices.",
        "Provide physical security for AWS datacenters.",
        "Install operating system updates on Lambda@Edge."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 609"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service should a company use to organize, characterize, and search large numbers of images?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Rekognition",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Transcribe",
        "Amazon Aurora",
        "Amazon QuickSight"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 610"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to monitor for misconfigured security groups that are allowing unrestricted access to specific ports.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Trusted Advisor",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "AWS Health Dashboard"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 611"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service is always available free of charge to users?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Athena",
        "AWS Secrets Manager",
        "Amazon ElastiCache"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 612"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to run some of its workloads on premises to comply with regulatory guidelines. The company wants to use the AWS Cloud to run workloads that are not required to be on premises. The company also wants to be able to use the same API calls for the on-premises workloads and the cloud workloads.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Outposts",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Dedicated Hosts",
        "Availability Zones",
        "AWS Wavelength"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 613"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is the recommended use case for Amazon EC2 On-Demand Instances?",
      "correct_answer": "An unpredictable workload that does not require a long-term commitment",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A steady-state workload that requires a particular EC2 instance configuration for a long period of time",
        "A workload that can be interrupted for a project that requires the lowest possible cost",
        "A workload that is expected to run for longer than 1 year"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 614"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to use an AWS networking solution that can act as a centralized gateway between multiple VPCs and on-premises networks.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Transit Gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Gateway VPC endpoint",
        "AWS Direct Connect",
        "AWS PrivateLink"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 615"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "An administrator observed that multiple AWS resources were deleted yesterday.\n\nWhich AWS service will help identify the cause and determine which user deleted the resources?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudTrail",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "Amazon GuardDuty",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 616"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "To assist companies with Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI DSS) compliance in the cloud, AWS provides:",
      "correct_answer": "an AWS Attestation of Compliance (AOC) report for specific AWS services.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "physical Inspections of data centers by appointment.",
        "required PCI compliance certifications for any application running on AWS.",
        "professional PCI compliance services."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 617"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "In which situations should a company create an IAM user instead of an IAM role?",
      "correct_answer": "When the company creates AWS access credentials for individuals",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "When an application that runs on Amazon EC2 instances requires access to other AWS services",
        "When the company creates an application that runs on a mobile phone that makes requests to AWS",
        "When the company needs to add users to IAM groups",
        "When users are authenticated in the corporate network and want to be able to use AWS without having to sign in a second time"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 618"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company hosts a web application on AWS. The company has improved the availability of its application by provisioning multiple Amazon EC2 instances. The company wants to distribute its traffic across the EC2 instances while providing a single point of contact to the web clients.\n\nWhich AWS service can distribute the traffic to multiple EC2 instances as targets?",
      "correct_answer": "Application Load Balancer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "VPC endpoints",
        "NAT gateway",
        "Internet gateway"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 619"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is the total volume of data that can be stored in Amazon S3?",
      "correct_answer": "Virtually unlimited",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "10 PB",
        "50 PB",
        "100 PB"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 620"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which design principle is related to the reliability pillar according to the AWS Well-Architected Framework?",
      "correct_answer": "Test recovery procedures",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Experiment more often",
        "Go global in minutes",
        "Analyze and attribute to expenditure"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 621"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service is a key-value database that provides sub-millisecond latency on a large scale?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Aurora",
        "Amazon DocumentDB (with MongoDB compatibility)",
        "Amazon Neptune"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 622"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company stores data in an Amazon S3 bucket.\n\nWhich task is the responsibility of AWS?",
      "correct_answer": "Protect the infrastructure that supports S3 storage.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Configure an S3 Lifecycle policy.",
        "Activate S3 Versioning.",
        "Configure S3 bucket policies."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 623"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to transfer a virtual Windows Server 2022 that is currently running in its own data center to AWS. The company wants to automatically convert the existing server to run directly on AWS infrastructure instead of visualized hardware.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Application Migration Service",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS DataSync",
        "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)",
        "AWS Application Discovery Service"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 624"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service is a fully managed NoSQL database service?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon DynamoDB",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon RDS",
        "Amazon Redshift",
        "Amazon Aurora"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 625"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company deployed an application in multiple AWS Regions around the world. The company wants to improve the application’s performance and availability.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Global Accelerator",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon DataZone",
        "AWS Cloud Map",
        "AWS Auto Scaling"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 626"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate its on-premises SQL Server database to the AWS Cloud. The company wants AWS to handle the day-to-day administration of the database.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet the company's requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon RDS",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon EC2 for Microsoft SQL Server",
        "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "Amazon Aurora"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 627"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs stateless network filtering for its VPC.\n\nWhich AWS service, tool, or feature will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Network access control list (ACL)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS PrivateLink",
        "Security group",
        "AWS WAF"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 628"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which option is an advantage of AWS Cloud computing that minimizes variable costs?",
      "correct_answer": "Economies of scale",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "High availability",
        "Global reach",
        "Agility"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 629"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate its server-based applications to the AWS Cloud. The company wants to determine the total cost of ownership for its compute resources that will be hosted on the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich combination of AWS services or tools will meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Pricing Calculator",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Support Center",
        "AWS Application Discovery Service",
        "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Migration Evaluator",
        "code": "Question 630"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has data lakes designed for high performance computing (HPC) workloads.\n\nWhich Amazon EC2 instance type should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Compute optimized instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "General purpose instances",
        "Memory optimized instances",
        "Storage optimized instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 631"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which benefits does a company gain when the company moves from on-premises IT architecture to the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Reduced or eliminated tasks for hardware troubleshooting, capacity planning, and procurement",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Elimination of the need for trained IT staff",
        "Automatic security configuration of all applications that are migrated to the cloud",
        "Elimination of the need for disaster recovery planning"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Faster deployment of new features and applications",
        "code": "Question 632"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is deploying a machine learning (ML) research project that will require a lot of compute power over several months. The ML processing jobs do not need to run at specific times.\n\nWhich Amazon EC2 instance purchasing option will meet these requirements at the lowest cost?",
      "correct_answer": "Spot Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Reserved Instances",
        "Dedicated Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 633"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to migrate to the AWS Cloud. The company is conducting organizational transformation and wants to become more responsive to customer inquiries and feedback.\n\nWhich task should the company perform to meet these requirements, according to the AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF)? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Realign teams to focus on products and value streams.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Create new value propositions with new products and services.",
        "Use a new data and analytics platform to create actionable insights.",
        "Migrate and modernize legacy infrastructure."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Use agile methods to rapidly iterate and evolve.",
        "code": "Question 634"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company that is planning to migrate to the AWS Cloud is based in an isolated area that has limited internet connectivity. The company needs to perform local data processing on premises. The company needs a solution that can operate without a stable internet connection.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Snowball Edge",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon S3",
        "AWS Storage Gateway",
        "AWS Backup"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 635"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to build graph queries for real-time fraud pattern detection.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Neptune",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "Amazon Timestream",
        "Amazon Forecast"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 636"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate to the AWS Cloud. The company needs the ability to acquire resources when the resources are necessary. The company also needs the ability to release those resources when the resources are no longer necessary.\n\nWhich architecture concept of the AWS Cloud meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Elasticity",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Availability",
        "Reliability",
        "Durability"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 637"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to deploy a web application as a containerized application. The company wants to use a managed service that can automatically create container images from source code and deploy the containerized application.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS App Runner",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Elastic Beanstalk",
        "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)",
        "Amazon EC2"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 638"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has moved all its infrastructure to the AWS Cloud. To plan ahead for each quarter, the finance team wants to track the cost and usage data of all resources from previous months. The finance team wants to automatically generate reports that contains the data.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature should the finance team use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Budgets",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Detective",
        "AWS Pricing Calculator",
        "AWS Savings Plans"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 639"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF) perspective focuses on real-time insights and answers questions about strategy?",
      "correct_answer": "Business",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Operations",
        "People",
        "Platform"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 640"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate critical on-premises production systems to Amazon EC2 instances. The production instances will be used for at least 3 years. The company wants a pricing option that will minimize cost.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Reserved Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Spot Instances",
        "AWS Free Tier"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 641"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS Well-Architected Framework concept represents a system's ability to remain functional when the system encounters operational problems?",
      "correct_answer": "Durability",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Consistency",
        "Elasticity",
        "Latency"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 642"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework focuses on the ability to recover automatically from service interruptions?",
      "correct_answer": "Reliability",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security",
        "Performance efficiency",
        "Operational excellence"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 643"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS services or features provide disaster recovery solutions for Amazon EC2 instances? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "EC2 Amazon Machine Images (AMIs)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "EC2 Reserved Instances",
        "AWS Shield",
        "Amazon GuardDuty"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS) snapshots",
        "code": "Question 644"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has multiple SQL-based databases located in a data center. The company needs to migrate all database servers to the AWS Cloud to reduce the cost of operating physical servers.\n\nWhich AWS service or resource will meet these requirements with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon RDS",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon EC2 instances",
        "Amazon DynamoDB",
        "OpenSearch"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 645"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to build, train, and deploy machine learning (ML) models.\n\nWhich AWS service can the company use to meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon SageMaker",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Personalize",
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon Forecast"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 646"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or tool provides recommendations to help users get rightsized Amazon EC2 instances based on historical workload usage data?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Compute Optimizer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Pricing Calculator",
        "AWS App Runner",
        "AWS Systems Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 647"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to explore and analyze data in Amazon S3 by using a programming language.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Athena",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Kendra",
        "Amazon Comprehend",
        "Amazon SageMaker"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 648"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to run an application on Amazon EC2 instances without interruption.\n\nWhich EC2 instance purchasing option will meet this requirement MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "Standard Reserved Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Convertible Reserved Instances",
        "On-Demand Instances",
        "Spot Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 649"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants a fully managed service that centralizes and automates data protection across AWS services and hybrid workloads.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Backup",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Artifact",
        "AWS Batch",
        "AWS Shield"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 650"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company plans to migrate its application from on premises to the AWS Cloud. The company needs to gather usage and configuration data for the application components.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Application Discovery Service",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)",
        "AWS Transfer Family",
        "AWS Global Accelerator"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 651"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which design principle aligns with performance efficiency pillar of the AWS Well-Architected Framework?",
      "correct_answer": "Using serverless architectures",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Scaling horizontally",
        "Measuring the cost of workloads",
        "Using managed services"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 652"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to provide low latency to its users around the world.\n\nWhich feature of the AWS Cloud meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Global infrastructure",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Pay as-you-go pricing",
        "Managed services",
        "Economy of scale"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 653"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which type of workload should a company run on Amazon EC2 Spot Instances?",
      "correct_answer": "A workload that can be interrupted and can control costs",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A steady-state workload that requires a particular EC2 instance configuration for a long period of time",
        "A steady-state workload that does not require a long-term commitment",
        "A workload that cannot be interrupted and can control costs"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 654"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service provides command line access to AWS tools and resources directly from a web browser?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudShell",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CloudHSM",
        "Amazon WorkSpaces",
        "AWS Cloud Map"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 655"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has multiple AWS accounts. The company needs to receive a consolidated bill from AWS and must centrally manage security and compliance.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature should the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Organizations",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Cost and Usage Report",
        "AWS Config",
        "AWS Security Hub"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 656"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "For which use case are Amazon EC2 On-Demand Instances MOST cost-effective?",
      "correct_answer": "An instance in continual use for 1 month to conduct quality assurance tests",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Compute-intensive video transcoding that can be restarted if necessary",
        "An instance that runs a web server that will run for 1 year",
        "An instance that runs a database that will run for 3 years"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 657"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has developed a new In-house application. The company does not have a way to determine or predict the usage demand that the application will create.\n\nWhich AWS Cloud computing benefit is the company seeking?",
      "correct_answer": "Scalable and high performance",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Easy to use",
        "Cost-effective",
        "Secure"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 658"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS offering can analyze a company’s AWS environment to discover security vulnerabilities on Amazon EC2 instances?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Inspector",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Macie",
        "AWS Shield Standard",
        "Security groups"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 659"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company plans to onboard new employees that will be working remotely. The company needs to set up Windows virtual desktops to create a working environment for the new employees. The employees must be able access the working environment from anywhere and by using their computer or a web browser.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Workspaces",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Dedicated Hosts",
        "AWS Global Accelerator",
        "Amazon CloudFront"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 660"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to visualize and manage AWS Cloud costs and usage for a specific period of time.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Cost Explorer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Consolidated billing",
        "AWS Organizations",
        "AWS Budgets"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 661"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service supports MySQL database engines?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon RDS",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Dynamo DВ",
        "Amazon DocumentDB (with MongoDB compatibility)",
        "Amazon ElastiCache"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 662"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company purchased Amazon EC2 Standard Reserved Instances (RIs) for a workload in the AWS Cloud. The company needs to move part of the workload to an instance family that does not match the instance family of these Standard RIs.\n\nHow can the company take advantage of the Standard RIs that it no longer needs?",
      "correct_answer": "Sell the Standard RIs on the Amazon EC2 Reserved Instance Marketplace",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Contact the AWS Support team, and ask the team to sell the Standard RIs",
        "Sell the Standard RIs as a third-party seller on the AWS Marketplace",
        "Convert the Standard RIs to Savings Plans"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 663"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is releasing a business-critical application. Before the release, the company needs strategic planning assistance from AWS. During the release, the company needs AWS infrastructure event management and real-time support.\n\nWhat should the company do to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Sign up for AWS Enterprise Support",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Access AWS Trusted Advisor",
        "Contact the AWS Partner Network (APN)",
        "Contact AWS Professional Services"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 664"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to improve employee productivity by providing a way for employees to search for questions and retrieve specific answers. The company wants to use a single intelligent search interface.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Kendra",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Connect",
        "Amazon Lex",
        "Amazon Comprehend"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 665"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is running and managing its own Docker environment on Amazon EC2 instances. The company wants an alternative to help manage cluster size, scheduling, and environment maintenance.\n\nWhich AWS service meets these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Fargate",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Lambda",
        "Amazon RDS",
        "Amazon Athena"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 666"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A network engineer needs to build a hybrid cloud architecture connecting on-premises networks to the AWS Cloud using AWS Direct Connect. The company has a few VPCs in a single AWS Region and expects to increase the number of VPCs to hundreds over time.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature should the engineer use to simplify and scale this connectivity as the VPCs increase in number?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Transit Gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "VPC endpoints",
        "Amazon Route 53",
        "AWS Secrets Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 667"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants an Amazon S3 solution that provides access to object storage within single-digit milliseconds.\n\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "S3 Express One Zone",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "S3 Standard",
        "S3 Glacier Flexible Retrieval",
        "S3 Glacier Instant Retrieval"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 668"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company runs an uninterruptible Amazon EC2 workload on AWS 24 hours a day, 7 days a week. The company will require the same instance family and instance type to run the workload for the next 12 months.\n\nWhich combination of purchasing options should the company choose to MOST optimize costs? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Standard Reserved Instance",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Convertible Reserved Instance",
        "Compute Savings Plan",
        "Spot Instance"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "All Upfront payment",
        "code": "Question 669"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to run its application's code without having to provision and manage servers.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Lambda",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Glue",
        "AWS CodeDeploy",
        "Amazon CodeGuru"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 670"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is planning to migrate to the AWS Cloud. The company needs to understand the existing on-premises usage and configuration. The company does not want to replicate its workloads to AWS, yet.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Application Discovery Service",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Application Migration Service",
        "Cloud Migration Factory",
        "AWS Transfer Family"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 671"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to allow its employees to work remotely from home. The company's employees use Windows or Linux desktops. The company's employees need access from anywhere and at anytime by using any supported devices.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Workspaces",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon AppStream 2.0",
        "Amazon Keyspaces (for Apache Cassandra)",
        "AWS Cloud9"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 672"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to test a new application.\n\nWhich AWS principle will help the company test the application?",
      "correct_answer": "Scale up and down when needed without any long-term commitments.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Make long-term commitments in exchange for a cost discount.",
        "Have total control over the application infrastructure.",
        "Manage all of the maintenance tasks associated with the cloud."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 673"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company plans to launch an ecommerce website that contains many images for a product catalog. The company wants to keep the cost of running the website within a specific budget.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool should the company use to monitor the ongoing costs of the website?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Cost Explorer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS SDKs",
        "EC2 Image Builder",
        "AWS CloudFormation"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 674"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has deployed several public applications behind Application Load Balancers. The company wants to improve the performance of the applications.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Global Accelerator",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Connect",
        "Amazon ElastiCache",
        "Amazon CloudWatch"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 675"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has an on-premises application. The application has processing times of less than 5 minutes and is invoked only a few times each day. The company wants to move the application to the AWS Cloud.\n\nWhich AWS service will support this application MOST cost-effectively?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Lambda",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic Container Service (Amazon ECS)",
        "Amazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (Amazon EKS)",
        "Amazon EC2"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 676"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company is learning about the perspectives of the AWS Cloud Adoption Framework (AWS CAF).\n\nWhich perspective of the AWS CAF addresses the strategy management capability?",
      "correct_answer": "Business perspective",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "People perspective",
        "Governance perspective",
        "Operations perspective"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 677"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to assess its operational readiness. It also wants to identify and mitigate any operational risks ahead of a new product launch.\n\nWhich AWS Support plan offers guidance and support for this kind of event at no additional charge?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Enterprise Support",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Business Support",
        "AWS Basic Support",
        "AWS Developer Support"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 678"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to consolidate its call centers to improve the customer voice and chat experience with call center agents.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Connect",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Simple Notification Service (Amazon SNS)",
        "AWS Support Center",
        "Amazon Cognito"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 679"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to provision uninterruptible Amazon EC2 instances, when needed, and pay for compute capacity by the second.\n\nWhich EC2 instance purchasing option will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "On-Demand Instances",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reserved Instances",
        "Spot Instances",
        "Dedicated Instances"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 680"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service can migrate Amazon EC2 instances from one AWS Region to another?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Application Migration Service",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Database Migration Service (AWS DMS)",
        "AWS DataSync",
        "AWS Migration Hub"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 681"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to block SQL injection attacks.\n\nWhich AWS service or feature provides this functionality?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS WAF",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Network ACLs",
        "Security groups",
        "AWS Trusted Advisor"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 682"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to run its application on Amazon EC2 instances. The company needs to keep the application on-premises to meet a compliance requirement.\n\nWhich AWS offering will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Outposts",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Dedicated Instances",
        "Amazon CloudFront",
        "AWS Fargate"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 683"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to connect its supported AWS services and VPCs. The company does not want to expose its internal traffic to the public internet.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS PrivateLink",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "Amazon Connect",
        "AWS Internet Gateway"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 684"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service can manage permissions for AWS resources by using policies?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "Amazon Detective",
        "Amazon GuardDuty"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 685"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company needs to run some of its workload in the AWS Cloud. The company needs to keep some of the workload in its own on-site data center due to compliance reasons.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Outposts",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWSConfig",
        "Amazon Lightsail",
        "Amazon Connect"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 686"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to deploy an application that stores data in a relational database. The company wants database tasks, such as automated backups and database snapshots, to be managed by AWS.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon RDS",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon DocumentDB",
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)",
        "Amazon S3"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 687"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company that operates on-premises servers decides to start a new line of business. The company determines that additional servers are required for the new workloads.\n\nWhich advantage of cloud computing can help the company to provision additional infrastructure as quickly as possible?",
      "correct_answer": "Increase speed and agility",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Benefit from massive economies of scale",
        "Trade fixed expense for variable expense",
        "Go global in minutes"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 688"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to establish a schedule for rotating database user credentials.\n\nWhich AWS service will support this requirement with the LEAST amount of operational overhead?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Secrets Manager",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Systems Manager",
        "AWS License Manager",
        "AWS Managed Services"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 689"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature can be used to create a private connection between an on-premises workload and an AWS Cloud workload?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Direct Connect",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Route 53",
        "Amazon Macie",
        "AWS PrivateLink"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 690"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service is used to provide encryption for Amazon EBS?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS KMS",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Certificate Manager",
        "AWS Systems Manager",
        "AWS Config"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 691"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to manage its AWS Cloud resources through a web interface.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Management Console",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CLI",
        "AWS SDK",
        "AWS Cloud9"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 692"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following are advantages of the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "High economies of scale",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Trade variable expenses for capital expenses",
        "Focus on managing hardware infrastructure",
        "Overprovision to ensure capacity"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "Launch globally in minutes",
        "code": "Question 693"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS Cloud benefit is shown by an architecture’s ability to withstand failures with minimal downtime?",
      "correct_answer": "High availability",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Agility",
        "Elasticity",
        "Scalability"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 694"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A developer needs to maintain a development environment infrastructure and a production environment infrastructure in a repeatable fashion.\n\nWhich AWS service should the developer use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS CloudFormation",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Ground Station",
        "AWS Shield",
        "AWS IoT Device Defender"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 695"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which task is the customer’s responsibility, according to the AWS shared responsibility model?",
      "correct_answer": "Configure firewalls and networks.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Maintain the security of the AWS Cloud.",
        "Patch the operating system of Amazon RDS instances.",
        "Implement physical and environmental controls."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 696"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to run a NoSQL database on Amazon EC2 instances.\n\nWhich task is the responsibility of AWS in this scenario?",
      "correct_answer": "Patch the physical infrastructure that hosts the EC2 instances.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Update the guest operating system of the EC2 instances.",
        "Maintain high availability at the database layer.",
        "Configure the security group firewall."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 697"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service helps deliver highly available applications with fast failover for multi-Region and Multi-AZ architectures?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Global Accelerator",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS WAF",
        "AWS Shield",
        "AWS Direct Connect"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 698"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company has a set of ecommerce applications. The applications need to be able to send messages to each other.\n\nWhich AWS service meets this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Simple Queue Service (Amazon SQS)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Auto Scaling",
        "Elastic Load Balancing",
        "Amazon Kinesis Data Streams"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 699"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What are the benefits of consolidated billing for AWS Cloud services? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "Volume discounts",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "A minimal additional fee for use",
        "Installment payment options",
        "Custom cost and usage budget creation"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "One bill for multiple accounts",
        "code": "Question 700"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A user wants to review all Amazon S3 buckets with ACLs and S3 bucket policies in the S3 console.\n\nWhich AWS service or resource will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Access Analyzer for S3",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "S3 Multi-Region Access Points",
        "S3 Storage Lens",
        "AWS IAM Identity Center (AWS Single Sign-On)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 701"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What is the best resource for a user to find compliance-related information and reports about AWS?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Artifact",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Marketplace",
        "Amazon Inspector",
        "AWS Support"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 702"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service enables companies to deploy an application close to end users?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon CloudFront",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Auto Scaling",
        "AWS AppSync",
        "Amazon Route 53"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 703"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or feature improves network performance by sending traffic through the AWS worldwide network infrastructure?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Global Accelerator",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Route table",
        "AWS Transit Gateway",
        "Amazon VPC"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 704"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service provides highly durable object storage?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon S3",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Elastic File System (Amazon EFS)",
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)",
        "Amazon FSx"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 705"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which responsibility belongs to AWS when a company hosts its databases on Amazon EC2 instances?",
      "correct_answer": "Operating system installations",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Database backups",
        "Database software patches",
        "Operating system patches"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 706"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following are advantages of moving to the AWS Cloud? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "The ability to use the pay-as-you-go model.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The ability to turn over the responsibility for all security to AWS.",
        "The ability to have full control over the physical infrastructure.",
        "No longer worrying about users access controls."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "No longer having to guess what capacity will be required.",
        "code": "Question 707"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS services or tools can identify rightsizing opportunities for Amazon EC2 instances? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Cost Explorer",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS Billing Conductor",
        "Amazon CodeGuru",
        "Amazon SageMaker"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS Compute Optimizer",
        "code": "Question 708"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service is a hybrid cloud storage service that provides on-premises users access to virtually unlimited cloud storage?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Storage Gateway",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS DataSync",
        "Amazon S3 Glacier",
        "Amazon Elastic Block Store (Amazon EBS)"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 709"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company plans to migrate to AWS and wants to create cost estimates for its AWS use cases.\n\nWhich AWS service or tool can the company use to meet these requirements?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Pricing Calculator",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon CloudWatch",
        "AWS Cost Explorer",
        "AWS Budgets"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 710"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which tool should a developer use to integrate AWS service features directly into an application?",
      "correct_answer": "AWS Software Development Kit",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS CodeDeploy",
        "AWS Lambda",
        "AWS Batch"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 711"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which of the following is a recommended design principle of the AWS Well-Architected Framework?",
      "correct_answer": "Learn to improve from operational failures.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Reduce downtime by making infrastructure changes infrequently and in large increments.",
        "Invest the time to configure infrastructure manually.",
        "Use monolithic application design for centralization."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 712"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Using AWS Identity and Access Management (IAM) to grant access only to the resources needed to perform a task is a concept known as:",
      "correct_answer": "least privilege access.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "restricted access.",
        "as-needed access.",
        "token access."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 713"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which AWS service or tool can be used to set up a firewall to control traffic going into and coming out of an Amazon VPC subnet?",
      "correct_answer": "Network ACL",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Security group",
        "AWS WAF",
        "AWS Firewall Manager"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 714"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to operate a data warehouse to analyze data without managing the data warehouse infrastructure.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "Amazon Redshift Serverless",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Amazon Aurora",
        "AWS Lambda",
        "Amazon RDS"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 715"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "How does AWS Cloud computing help businesses reduce costs? (Choose two.)",
      "correct_answer": "AWS enables capacity to be adjusted on demand.",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "AWS charges the same prices for services in every AWS Region.",
        "AWS offers discounts for Amazon EC2 instances that remain idle for more than 1 week.",
        "AWS does not charge for data sent from the AWS Cloud to the internet."
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "correct_variants": "AWS eliminates many of the costs of building and maintaining on-premises data centers.",
        "code": "Question 716"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "A company wants to grant users in one AWS account access to resources in another AWS account. The users do not currently have permission to access the resources.\n\nWhich AWS service will meet this requirement?",
      "correct_answer": "IAM role",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "IAM group",
        "IAM tag",
        "IAM Access Analyzer"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 717"
      }
    },
    {
      "category": "Aws Practitioner Sample Full",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which task is the responsibility of AWS when using AWS services?",
      "correct_answer": "Maintenance of physical and environmental controls",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Management of IAM user permissions",
        "Creation of security group rules for outbound access",
        "Application of Amazon EC2 operating system patches"
      ],
      "metadata": {
        "code": "Question 718"
      }
    }
  ]
}